SHORTLY.
HE WAS HOSPITALIZED A FEW WEEKS
AGO FOR A PROCEDURE TO RELIEVE
PRESSURE ON HIS BRAIN WHICH WAS
SUCCESSFUL.
AND OF COURSE AS WE LEARN MORE,
WE WILL GET THAT TO YOU.
BUT AGAIN HE DOES LOOK FORWARD
TO RETURNING HOME SOON.
THANKS FOR WATCHING US.
ANDERSON STARTS NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THE START OF A WEEK FILLED WITH
THINGS WE'VE SIMPLY NEVER SEEN
BEFORE INCLUDING IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS WITH THE TARGET
REFUSING TO TAKE PART AND THAT
IS NOT ALL.
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE IS
OUT WITH A WITNESS LIST OF DAY
ONE OF PROCEEDINGS.
ALSO LATE TODAY MEMBERS OF THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE GOT
A PREVIEW OF THE MAJORITY REPORT
ON THE TESTIMONY THAT THEY'VE
HEARD AND HOW REPUBLICANS PUT
OUT A 123-PAGE REBUTTAL.
IT IS SHARPLY AT ODDS WITH
TESTIMONY SO FAR AS WELL AS WITH
THE PRESIDENT'S OWN WORDS.
PLUS THE REPUBLICAN SENATOR JOHN
KENNEDY OF LOUISIANA IS
REPEATING RUSSIAN TALKING POINTS
IN DEFENSE OF THE PRESIDENT.
AGAIN EVEN AFTER BEING TOLD THEY
ARE RUSSIAN TALKING POINTS BY
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS AND
HEARING THIS FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN FORMER EXPERT IN
THE FIELD.
>> SOME OF YOU ON THIS COMMITTEE
APPEAR TO BELIEVE THAT RUSSIA
AND ITS SECURITY SERVICES DOES
NOT CONDUCT A CAMPAIGN AGAINST
OUR COUNTRY AND THAT PERHAPS
SOMEHOW FOR SOME REASON UKRAINE
DID.
THIS IS A FICTIONAL NARRATIVE
PERPETRATED AND PROPAGATED BY
THE RUSSIAN SECURITY SERVICES
THEMSELVES.
>> WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT
TONIGHT.
AND LISA PAGE BREAKING HER
SILENCE.
TALKING ABOUT BEING ACCUSED OF
TREASON BY THE LEADER OF THE
FREE WORLD.
AND IF THAT WEREN'T ENOUGH OR
BECAUSE IT IS TOO MUCH THE
RIDICULIST COMES BACK.
>>> AND ONCE AGAIN NOW HIDING
BEHIND A STONEWALL, THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL LATE YESTERDAY IN
A LETTER TO CHAIRMAN JERRY
NADLER CALLED HIS COMMITTEE
PROCEEDINGS BASELESS AND HIGHLY
PARTISAN AND SAYING ACCORDINGLY
UNDER THE CURRENT CIRCUMSTANCES
WE DO NOT INTEND TO PARTICIPATE
IN YOUR WEDNESDAY HEARING.
THE LETTER HOLDS OPEN THE
POSSIBILITY OF PARTICIPATION IN
FUTURE HEARINGS BUT TO BE REAL,
WE'VE HEARD THAT SONG BEFORE.
WHETHER IT IS ABOUT TESTIFYING
INTO THE IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY OR
RELEASING TAXES OR TALKING TO
THE MUELLER INVESTIGATION OR
HAVING TOP OFFICIALS COOPERATE
WITH THE UKRAINE PROBE, THE
PRESIDENT SINGS THE SAME TUNE
WITH THE EXACT SAME LYRICS
BEFORE DOING THE EXACT OPPOSITE.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO SPEAK.
I WOULD LOVE TO.
NOBODY WANTS TO SPEAK MORE THAN
ME.
>> I'D LIFE TO HAVE MIC GO UP
FRANKLY.
>> I'LL RELEASE MY RETURNS.
I HAVE NO PROBLEM WITH IT.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO SPEAK.
I WOULD LOVE TO GO.
NOTHING I WANT TO DO MORE.
>> BUT THE LEGAL PEOPLE SAY YOU
COULD DO IT NOW --
>> BILL --
>> WOULD YOU BE WILLING TO SPEAK
UNDER OATH TO GIVE YOUR VERSION
OF --
>> 100%.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO TALK TO
MUELLER?
>> I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT
ACTUALLY.
>> LET HER RELEASE HER EMAILS
AND I'LL RELEASE MY TAX RETURNS
IMMEDIATELY.
>> I LIKE TO HAVE THE PEOPLE GO
UP.
EXCEPT ONE THING.
IT VALIDATES A CORRUPT
INVESTIGATION.
>> LOVE TO BUT -- YOU LEFT A POT
ON THE STOVE AND HAVE A TERM
PAPER TO WRITE AND ULTIMATELY
THE ANSWER IS NO IF HE SAID SO
UP FRONT WOULD BE HONEST.
AT THIS POINT NOVEL.
THIS EVENING THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED A WORD SALAD ON THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY ENDING WITH
SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED.
CAN WE GO TO SUPREME COURT TO
STOP.
JIM ACOSTA IS TRAVELING WITH THE
PRESIDENT IN LONDON WHERE THAT
TWEET ORIGINATED AND WHERE HE IS
MEETING WITH NATO ALLIES.
JIM, CLEARLY HE'S FOCUSED ON
WHAT IS HAPPENING AT HOME EVEN
THOUGH HE'S OVER THERE.
>> Reporter: DEFINITELY.
AS THE PRESIDENT LANDED HE DID
TWEET OUT HIS SUPPORT TO THAT
REPUBLICAN PREBUTTAL OR REBUTTAL
OR WHATEVER YOU WANT TO CALL IT
TO THE HOUSE DEMOCRATS
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE REPORT ON
WHAT HAPPENED WITH UKRAINE AND
IN ADDITION THE PRESIDENT WAS
LATCHING ON TO THE COMMENTS MADE
BY THE UKRAINIAN PRESIDENT TO
"TIME" MAGAZINE AND THE
PRESIDENT SAID THAT HE FELT LIKE
HE WAS TREATED LIKE A BEGAR IN
DEALING WITH THE WHITE HOUSE TO
TRY TO GET THE MILITARY AID AND
WENT ON TO SAY THE PRESIDENT OF
UKRAINE HAS SAID I DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING WRONG.
THAT IS NOT WHAT HE SAID.
IN ADDITION HE'S ACCUSING
DEMOCRATS OF TRYING TO COMMIT
SABOTAGE BECAUSE THEY'RE HOLDING
THIS HEARING ON WEDNESDAY AS
HE'S MEETING WITH NATO LEADERS
HERE IN LONDON.
WOULD YOU SAY IT IS ON HIS MIND
AND UNDER HIS SKIN.
>> AND TALK ABOUT WHAT YOU'VE
LEARNED ABOUT THE WHITE HOUSE
PARTICIPATION OR LACK THEREOF
AND THEY ARE NOT COOPERATING ON
WEDNESDAY.
>> Reporter: RIGHT.
THEY ARE NOT THERE ON WEDNESDAY.
THE PRESIDENT WON'T BE THERE ON
WEDNESDAY.
HE'LL BE HERE IN LONDON.
BUT ANDERSON, I TALKED TO A
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIAL WHO SAID AT
THIS POINT THE DEMOCRATS ARE
COMING NOWHERE NEAR MEETING
THEIR DEMANDS WHEN IT COMES TO
THIS CRITERIA THAT THEY'VE LAID
OUT THAT WOULD ENSURE WHITE
HOUSE PARTICIPATION.
ANDERSON, ONE OF THOSE CRITERIA
WOULD BE WHETHER OR NOT
REPUBLICANS COULD BE ABLE TO
CALL WITNESSES THAT THEY WANT TO
SEE TESTIFY WHICH WOULD INCLUDE
THE WHISTLE-BLOWER WHO STARTED
ALL OF THIS.
THAT IS A NONSTARTER FOR
DEMOCRATS.
IT IS OBVIOUSLY NOT GOING TO
HAPPEN.
AND SO ANDERSON, AT THIS POINT,
THE WHITE HOUSE IS NOT CLOSED
THE DOOR ON PARTICIPATING IN THE
HOUSE IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS
BUT IT IS OPEN JUST A CRACK AT
THIS POINT.
WHAT THEY WOULD RATHER SEE IS
THE WHOLE PROCESS MOVE OVER TO
THE SENATE WHERE THE REPUBLICANS
ARE IN CHARGE AND CAN SET THE
RULES MUCH MORE SO THAN WHAT
THEY ARE DOING IN THE HOUSE
RIGHT NOW.
BUT CLEARLY THE PRESIDENT IS IN
NO MOOD TO COOPERATE AND A LOT
OF DEMOCRATS ARE SAYING, LOOK,
WHY WOULD THEY COOPERATE AT THIS
POINT.
THAT WOULD UNDERMINE WHAT THE
REPUBLICANS AND WHAT THE
PRESIDENT THEY'VE SAID ALL ALONG
WHICH IS THAT THIS IMPEACHMENT
PROCEEDING IS A HOAX AND NOT
LEGITIMATE BY PARTICIPATING THEY
WOULD ADD LEGITIMACY TO THE
PROCESS.
>> AND AGAIN TO SET THE
TIMETABLE, THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE, THEY'RE EXPECTED TO
VOTE ON THE REPORT TOMORROW.
THE REPUBLICAN SPONSOR THE
REBUTTAL, THAT IS OUT TONIGHT.
AND PROCEEDINGS IN THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE THAT BEGIN ON
WEDNESDAY WITHOUT PRESIDENTIAL
COOPERATION SO THERE IS A LOT TO
TALK ABOUT WITH OUR FIRST GUEST
CONGRESSWOMAN AND INTELLIGENCE
MEMBER JACKIE SPEIER.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
THIS REPORT FROM REPUBLICANS,
NOW THEY ARE ARGUING THAT THE
PRESSURE THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
PUT INTO THE DEMOCRATIC RIVALS
STEM FROM A QUOTE DEEP-SEATED
GENUINE AND REASONABLE
SKEPTICISM OF UKRAINE DUE TO THE
HISTORY OF PERVASIVE CORRUPTION.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THAT?
>> I THINK IT'S POPPYCOCK.
AND I THINK IT IS ONCE AGAIN AN
EFFORT BY THE PRESIDENT AND ALL
OF THE MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE AND
SENATE ON THE REPUBLICAN SIDE TO
TRY AND WEAVE SAY FALSEHOOD INTO
A TRUEISM.
IT WAS VERY CLEAR WHAT THE
PRESIDENT WANTED.
AND CERTAINLY THE HEARINGS WE
HAD SHOWED HOW MUCH TIME AND
ENERGY THE TRES AMIGOS, SONDLAND
AND PERRY AND VOLKER HAD TO TAP
DANCE AROUND THE MEETINGS WITH
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE BECAUSE
THIS INVESTIGATION WAS CRITICAL
TO THEM GETTING AID OR GETTING A
MEETING AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
AND IT IS VERY TRUE THAT THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
KNEW ABOUT THE WHISTLE-BLOWER IN
AUGUST.
AND SO HIS LIFTING THE HOLD ON
THE AID IN SEPTEMBER WAS MORE
RELATED TO THE FACT THAT THERE
WAS A WHISTLE-BLOWER COMPLAINT
AND THAT THE INSPECTOR GENERAL
HAD IDENTIFIED IT TO THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE ALTHOUGH
HE COULDN'T TELL US WHAT THE
WHISTLE-BLOWER COMPLAINT WAS
ABOUT.
>> THE REBUTTAL ALSO -- JUST
COMPLETELY IGNORES A LOT OF THE
EVIDENCE THAT WITNESSES
TESTIFIED TO UNDER OATH.
AND IT ESSENTIALLY -- THEY COULD
HAVE ARGUED WELL, YES, IT WASN'T
IDEAL FOR THE PRESIDENT TO
MENTION THE BIDENS IN THAT CALL,
THE CALL WASN'T GREAT, IT WASN'T
PERFECT.
BUT IT IS NOT IMPEACHABLE BUT
THEY WENT LOCK STEP WITH THE
PRESIDENT DEMANDING THAT THEY --
THEY'RE DOING EXACTLY WHAT THE
PRESIDENT DEMANDED.
>> AMBASSADOR SONDLAND SAT IN
THAT HEARING ROOM AND SAID, YES,
THERE WAS A QUID PRO QUO.
THAT WAS THEIR WITNESS.
THE APPOINTMENT BY THE PRESIDENT
OF MR. SONDLAND TO HIS POST AND
HE'S SAYING THERE WAS A QUID PRO
QUO.
SONDLAND ALSO SAID THE ONLY
THING THE PRESIDENT IS
INTERESTING IN IS SOMETHING THAT
WILL BENEFIT HIMSELF.
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT UKRAINE.
SO THAT'S PRETTY DAMNING.
AND YET THE REPUBLICANS FIND A
WAY TO TWIST THAT INTO SOMETHING
THAT IS ONCE AGAIN A FALSEHOOD.
AND THEY SAY -- AND THE
PRESIDENT DOES THIS TOO -- IF
YOU SAY SOMETHING FALSE OFTEN
ENOUGH, IT BECOMES TRUE IN THEIR
MINDS.
>> THE REPUBLICAN REPORT, IT IS
COMING OUT JUST AS THE DEMOCRATS
ON THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE ARE FINALIZING THEIR
OWN REPORT EXPECTED TO DRAW
PROBABLY THE EXACT OPPOSITE
CONCLUSION THE REPUBLICANS.
SO WHAT ARE AMERICANS WHO ARE
WATCHING THIS AT HOME SUPPOSED
TO BELIEVE WHEN YOU HAVE TWO
COMPETING REPORTS FROM CONGRESS
THAT DRAW COMPLETELY CONDUCTORY
CONCLUSIONS?
>> WELL LIKE BARR BEFORE THE
SUMMARY CAME OUT, THE
REPUBLICANS ARE PUTTING OUT THE
REBUTTAL BEFORE THE ACTUAL
DOCUMENT COMES OUT FROM THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
IT IS INTENDED TO CONFUSE THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC.
SO THAT THEY THROW UP THEIR
HANDS AND SAY, I DON'T EVEN WANT
TO DEAL WITH THIS.
AND THEIR EFFECTIVE TO A CERTAIN
POINT BUT FOR PERSONS WHO FEEL
STRONGLY THAT OUR DEMOCRACY IS
AT RISK HERE, THEY'RE LOOKING AT
THIS AND REALIZING THAT THIS IS
QUITE DANGEROUS AND THAT IS WHY
YOU SAW THAT THERE WAS AN
INCREASE IN SUPPORT FOR
IMPEACHMENT BY INDEPENDENTS
AFTER WE HELD THE HEARINGS BY
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE AND
HAD ALL OF THOSE 12 WITNESSES
COME BEFORE US.
>> IT IS KIND OF CREEPY THAT
REPUBLICANS IN LOCKSTEP WOULD BE
TO WILLING TO ESSENTIALLY TRY TO
MUDDY THE WATERS BEFORE THIS
COMMITTEE REPORT COMES OUT.
YOU WOULD THINK THERE WOULD BE A
WAY TO HAVE JUST ONE COMMITTEE
REPORT THAT HAS SOME DISSENSION
IN IT WITHOUT TRYING TO JUST
BASICALLY DESTROY SWORN
TESTIMONY.
>> WELL, BECAUSE THE REPUBLICANS
AREN'T ACTING INDEPENDENT OF THE
PRESIDENT.
THEY ARE BASICALLY TAKING HIS
TALKING POINTS AND MOUTHING THEM
AND MUCH LIKE DEVIN NUNES WAS
TRYING TO CREATE SOME FALSEHOOD
BY RACING OVER TO THE WHITE
HOUSE WITH THIS INFORMATION AND
RACING BACK WHEN, IN FACT, IT
WAS AT THE WHITE HOUSE THE WHOLE
TIME SHOWS YOU THAT FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING THIS IS BEEN
ORCHESTRATED BY THE PRESIDENT
AND THE WHITE HOUSE.
AND THEY ARE JUST FOLLOWING
ORDERS.
AND YOU MAY ASK WELL WHY ARE
THEY DOING IT?
BECAUSE THEY CARE MORE ABOUT
BEING RE-ELECTED THAN THEY DO
ABOUT THE STATE OF THE COUNTRY.
AND WHEN OUR NATIONAL SECURITY
IS AT RISK, AS IT IS NOW, WHEN
THE PRESIDENT CAN WITHHOLD AID
LIKE HEID DID TO UKRAINE, AGAIN
DOING THE BIDDING FOR RUSSIA,
IT'S QUITE SERIOUS.
>> THE INQUIRYOW MOVES FROM
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE TO
THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
JUDICIARY IS VERY DIFFERENT
PLACE THAN INTEL.
SOME OF THE PRESIDENT'S MOST PER
FOESHS DEFENDER LIKE GOHMERT AND
GAETZ ALL SERVE ON JUDICIARY,
HOW CONCERNS ARE YOU ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENS THERE?
>> I THINK WHAT WILL HAPPEN
THERE IS WHAT HAPPENED IN THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
YOU'LL HAVE EXPERTS COME FORWARD
AND HAVE CONSTITUTIONAL SCHOLARS
TALK ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT THIS
IS AN IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE AND
HOW YOU WOULD MOVE FORWARD WITH
IMPEACHMENT.
WE DO HAVE THE FACTS IN FRONT OF
US.
WE HAVE A WHISTLE-BLOWER
COMPLAINT THAT THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF CORROBORATED WITH THE
SUMMARY OF THE PHONE CALL THAT
ESTABLISHES THAT THERE WAS
BRIBERY.
AND SO AT THIS POINT THE
REPUBLICANS WILL MAKE ALL OF THE
NOISE THAT THEY ARE ABLE TO MAKE
BUT I THINK THE FACTS SPEAK FOR
THEMSELVES.
AND I FEEL THAT IT'S INCUMBENT
ON US TO MAKE SURE THAT THE LAW
IS FOLLOWED HERE AND NOT THE LAW
OF DONALD TRUMP.
>> CONGRESSWOMAN SPEIER, I
APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, SPEAKING OF
CONSTITUTIONAL SCHOLARS FROM ONE
OF THE TOP LAWYERS AND AUTHOR OF
A BOOK ON ITEM NEAT KATYAL JOINS
US.
AND A WOMAN WHO SAID THIS ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT, MY HEART DROPS TO
MY STOMACH WHEN I REALIZE HE'S
TWEETED ABOUT ME AGAIN.
LISA PAGE WHOSE TEXT MESSAGES
BELITTLING SPARKED ONGOING
ATTACKS FROM THE PRESIDENT.
SHE'S SPEAKING OUT.
She wanted to move someplace
warm.
But he wanted snow for the
holidays.
So we built a snow globe.
I'll get that later.
Dylan!
But the one thing we could both
agree on was getting GEICO
to help with homeowners
insurance.
What?
Switching and saving was
really easy!
I love you!
What?
Sweetie! Hands off the glass.
Ugh!!
Call GEICO and see how easy
saving on homeowners
and condo insurance can be.
I love her!
Create Your Own Ultimate Feast
is back at Red Lobster.
With new creations
to choose from;
like rich, butter-poached
Maine Lobster
and crispy Crab-Stuffed
Shrimp Rangoon.
How will you pick just 4 of 10?
It won't be easy.
Better hurry in.
Before we talk about
tax-smart investing, what's new?
-Audrey's expecting...
-Twins!
♪♪
We'd be closer to the twins.
Change in plans.
At Fidelity, a change in plans
is always part of the plan.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
The holidays are
here and we want to
keep you connected
to those you love,
with the new iPhone 11.
Hurry into T-Mobile today,
to get up to four
iPhone 11's ON US.
Only at T-Mobile.
♪♪
Experience the power of
sanctuary
at the Lincoln Wish List Sales
Event.
Sign and drive off in a new
Lincoln with zero down,
zero due at signing,
and a complimentary first
month's payment.
The zip code you're born into
can determine your future.
Your school.
Your job.
Your dreams.
Your problems.
(Indistinct shouting)
But at the Y,
we create opportunities
for everyone,
no matter who you are
or where you're from.
For a better us,
donate to your local Y today.
>>> WE TALKED ABOUT IT BEFORE
THE BREAK WITH JACKIE SPEIER,
DEMOCRATS ARE TAKING ISSUE WITH
THE REPUBLICAN REBUTTAL OR THE
PRE-BUTTAL TO THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE NOW
COMPLETED UKRAINE REPORT.
SHE CALLED IT POPPYCOCK.
ADAM SCHIFF ALSO WEIGHING IN
CALLING THE GOP EFFORT INTENDED
FOR AN AUDIENCE OF ONE.
MEANING THE PRESIDENT.
SAYING IT IGNORES THE EVIDENCE
PRESENTED OF IMPEACHABLE
WRONGDOING BY THE PRESIDENT.
AND REPUBLICANS FOR THEIR PART
WRITING THE DEMOCRAT'S
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY IS NOT
OUTGROWTH OF SERIOUS MISCONDUCT
BUT IT IS A CAMPAIGN TO UP END
OUR POLITICAL SYSTEM AND THE
DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO IMPEACH
THE PRESIDENT BASED ON THE
ASSUMPTIONS OF UNELECTED
BUREAUCRATS WHO DISAGREED WITH
THE POLICIES AND PROCESSES.
LET'S GET PERSPECTIVE FROM NEAL
KATYAL AND JUST OUT WITH A BOOK
"IMPEACH, THE CASE AGAINST
DONALD TRUMP."
THE REPUBLICAN'S PREBUTTAL
REPORT SAID THERE IS NO EVIDENCE
OF EXTORTION OR HIGH CRIME OR
MISDEMEANOR.
YOUR BOOK SAYS THE OPPOSITE THIS
IS SIMPLE STRAIGHTFORWARD CASE
OF A CORE IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE.
>> EXACTLY.
SO, ANDERSON, I WROTE THE BOOK
AS A SIMPLE GUIDE FOR AMERICANS
TO UNDERSTAND WHAT IS GOING ON.
AND IT BEGINS WE ASKING THE
QUESTION WHY IS IMPEACHMENT IN
THE CONSTITUTION AND A LOT OF
OUR FOUNDERS LIKE ELDRIDGE GARY
SAID IT SHOULDN'T BE IN THERE AT
ALL BECAUSE WE HAVE REELECTION
CAMPAIGNS AND THAT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH TO CHECK A PRESIDENT AND
OTHERS LIKE MADISON AND HAMILTON
SAID WHAT IF YOU HAVE A
PRESIDENT WHO IS BEHOLDEN TO A
FOREIGN POWER OR IF YOU HAVE A
PRESIDENT THAT TRIES TO
INTERFERE WITH THE REELECTION.
THAT IS THE INSTANCE OF OF O OU
FOUNDING FOR WHAT IS AN
IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE.
SO I DON'T QUITE UNDERSTAND THE
REPUBLICANS' REPORT ON TALKING
POINTS TO SAY THERE IS ZERO
EVIDENCE OF THIS.
THE PRESIDENT'S OWN TRANSCRIPT
OR FAKE TRANSCRIPT OR PARTIAL
TRANSCRIPT SAID EXACTLY THAT.
AND THE MOST IMPORTANT THING FOR
EVERYONE TO UNDERSTAND IS THIS
IS NOT ABOUT IMPEACHING A
PRESIDENT.
BECAUSE PEOPLE HAVE POLICY
DIFFERENCES.
FOR ME, I'M AGHAST AT THE
PRESIDENT'S SEPARATION POLICY
AND I FIND IT IMMORAL BUT THAT
IS NOT IMPEACHABLE.
AND IT IS HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS SAND AS THE BOOK
EXPLAINS THIS UKRAINE SITUATION
IS THAT.
>> WHAT IS A HIGH CRIME OR
MISDEMEANOR.
>> SO OUR FOUNDERS USED THE
PHRASE TREASON BRIBERY OR OTHER
HIGH CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS.
SO BRIBERY WE KNOW IS ONE OF
THEM.
AND THAT IS EXACTLY -- WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS ALLEGED TO HAVE
DONE HERE.
>> AND YOU THINK THIS IS A CASE
OF BRIBERY?
>> I DO.
THAT IS ONE OF THE THREE
ARTICLES ALREADY PROVEN BY THE
HEARINGS THAT WE'VE HAD AND THE
TRANSCRIPT RELEASED.
THE PRESIDENT WAS SAYING, LOOK
I'LL GIVE YOU THIS GOODY, THIS
AID THAT THE TAXPAYERS HAVE
APPROPRIATED AND I'M HOLDING UP,
BUT IN EXCHANGE, YOU'VE GOT TO
DO SOMETHING FOR ME FIRST.
AND THE SIMPLEST WAY TO
UNDERSTAND, ANDERSON, WHAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS ASKING FOR IS
THIS -- HE WAS TRYING TO CHEAT
IN THE 2020 ELECTION.
HE WAS TRYING TO GET A LEG UP
UPON HIS POLITICAL RIVAL BY
HAVING THEM ANNOUNCE THAT THEY
WERE DOING AN INVESTIGATION INTO
JOSEPH BIDEN, THE VICE
PRESIDENT.
NOW THAT IS JUST -- I MEAN, THE
REPUBLICAN DEFENSE THAT WE HEARD
TODAY IN THIS 120 PAGE REPORT IS
OH, NO, THE PRESIDENT CARED
ABOUT CORRUPTION.
THAT IS WHAT HE WAS WORRIED
ABOUT.
BUT IF YOU -- HE WAS CONVINCED
UKRAINE WAS CORRUPT.
IF YOU ARE CONVINCED UKRAINE IS
CORRUPT THEN WHY DO YOU ASK THE
UKRAINE GOVERNMENT TO
INVESTIGATE A UNITED STATES
CITIZEN.
IT JUST DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE
AT ALL.
WHAT I THINK EVERYONE KNOWS AND
WHAT WAS APPARENT IN THE LAST
TWO WEEKS OF HEARINGS IS THAT
THIS WAS NOT ABOUT CORRUPTION,
IT WAS ABOUT ONE SIMPLE THING,
THE PRESIDENT WANTED THEM TO
ANNOUNCE AN INVESTIGATION.
NOT EVEN DO IT, THE WAY THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
INVESTIGATIONS ARE DONE WHICH IS
IN SECRET.
BUT ANNOUNCE AN INVESTIGATION.
>> WE SHOULD EXPLAIN THAT ONCE
ONE SAW ALL OF THE TESTIMONY,
NOT ONLY OF AMBASSADOR
YOVANOVITCH BUT OTHERS IN THE
EMBASSY, THE U.S. POLICY WAS AN
ANTI-CORRUPTION POLICY IN
UKRAINE.
SO IT IS NOT AS IF PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS RAISING FOR THE FIRST
TIME THE IDEA OF FIGHTING
CORRUPTION IN UKRAINE.
THIS IS BEEN U.S. POLICY AND IT
IS SOMETHING THAT THE EMBASSY
WAS ALREADY DOING, TO THE BEST
THEY COULD OR MAKING EFFORTS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
NOBODY DISPUTES THE IDEA THAT
UKRAINE HAS CORRUPTION ISSUES.
BUT THE PRESIDENT'S OWN
ADMINISTRATION CERTIFIED JUST
WEEKS BEFORE THAT UKRAINE WASN'T
SO CORRUPT THAT THE AID COULDN'T
FLOW SO THEY SIGNED OFF ON THAT.
AND THEN THE PRESIDENT TRIED TO
CUT FUNDING FOR CORRUPTION
EFFORTS, ANTI-CORRUPTION EFFORTS
IN UKRAINE.
SO BASICALLY THEY'RE LEFT WITH
THE STORY THEY'RE TRYING TO
FIGHT CORRUPTION WHEN THEY HAVE
NO EXAMPLE ANYWHERE ELSE IN THE
WORLD OF THE PRESIDENT CARING
ABOUT CORRUPTION.
THIS IS THE ONE THING AND IT
JUST HAPPENED TO BE MAGICALLY
THIS INVOLVES HIS CHIEF
POLITICAL RIVAL JOE BIDEN.
>> WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THE WHITE
HOUSE STRATEGY, A., ITS
EFFECTIVENESS AND, B., LEGALITY
IN TERMS OF NOT COOPERATING AT
ALL, NO DOCUMENTS FROM THE STATE
DEPARTMENT FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
OTHER THAN THAT ROUGH TRANSCRIPT
WHICH THEY RELEASED E-- RELEASE
EARLY ON.
>> I DEDICATED MY LIFE TO THE
STUDY OF THE CONSTITUTION AND I
DIDN'T KNOW THAT THE PRESIDENT'S
STRATEGY HERE WAS A THING.
I DIDN'T THINK IT WAS POSSIBLE.
I MEAN, THE IDEA THAT A
PRESIDENT ON HIS OWN CAN
UNILATERALLY SAY I'M NOT GOING
TO BOTHER COOPERATING WITH AN
IMPEACHMENT INVESTIGATION, THAT
IS THE ESSENCE OF CONSTITUTIONAL
ARROGANCE AND THE DESTRUCTION OF
OUR SEPARATION OF POWERS.
I THINK IT IS AN IMPEACHABLE
OFFENSE JUST THE WAY THE
PRESIDENT HAS ACTED TOWARD THIS
IMPEACHMENT INVESTIGATION.
AND WE KNOW THIS BECAUSE
YESTERDAY THE PRESIDENT'S
LAWYER, THE WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL
SENT A LETTER TO CONGRESS SAYING
THAT THIS IS A RIDICULOUS
INVESTIGATION INVOLVING AND
SAYING THAT PRESIDENTS IN THE
PAST HAVE CLAIMED EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE TO NOT COOPERATE
INCLUDING HE NAMES CLINTON.
CLINTON NEVER DID THAT.
CLINTON NEVER ASSERTED EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE OVER THE IMPEACHMENT
INVESTIGATION.
AND INDEED PAST PRESIDENTS LIKE
POLK SAID IN 1846 SAID EXECUTIVE
PRIVILEGE HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
THIS.
IMPEACHMENT IS ALL ABOUT GETTING
THE TRUTH OUT TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE AND ALL OF THE
INFORMATION.
THIS PRESIDENT IS AFRAID OF THE
TRUTH COMING OUT IN CONGRESS.
AND SO HE'S TRIED TO GAG EVERY
EXECUTIVE BRANCH EMPLOYEE, EVERY
DOCUMENT, EVERY PHONE CALL,
EVERYTHING FROM BEING GIVEN TO
THE CONGRESS.
I CAN'T THINK OF SOMETHING THAT
IS MORE DESTRUCTIVE TO OUR
CONSTITUTION.
>> NEAL KATYAL, THANK YOU AGAIN
THE BOOK IS "IMPEACH, THE CASE
AGAINST DONALD TRUMP."
>>> FORMER FBI LAWYER LISA PAGE
AFTER TEXT MESSAGES CRITICIZING
HIM BECAME PUBLIC BREAKS HER
SILENCE.
SEE WHAT SHE'S SAYING NOW AND
HOW THE PRESIDENT IS ALREADY
REACTING.
THAT IS NEXT.
TOM STEYER: Wall Street Banks
took advantage
of millions of Americans during
the recession.
So, my wife Kat and I took
action.
We started a non-profit
community bank
with a simple theory -
give people a fair deal and real
economic power.
Invest in the community,
in businesses owned by women and
people of color,
in affordable housing.
The difference between words
and actions matters.
That's a lesson politicians
in Washington could
use right now.
I'm Tom Steyer, and I
approve this message.
I looove travel.
Italy!
Yaaaaass.
With the United
Explorer Card,
I get rewarded
wherever I go.
Going out for a bite.
Rewarded!
Going new places.
Anytime.
Rewarded!
Getting more
for getting away.
Rewarded!
Learn more at The Explorer Card
dot com.
and get...
Rewarded!
>>> AS WE MENTIONED AT THE TOP
OF THE PROGRAM, LISA PAGE IS
BREAKER HER SILENCE TWO YEARS
AFTER THE PUBLIC DISCLOSURE OF
THE HIGHLY CRITICAL TEXT
MESSAGES EXPRESSING MUTUAL
DISLIKE OF PRESIDENT TRUMP
BETWEEN HER AND AGENT PETER
STROEZAC.
PAGE SAID I'M DONE BEING QUIET.
PRESIDENT TRUMP LATE TODAY
TWEETING, WHEN LISA PAGE, T THE
LOVER OF PETER STRZOK TALKS
ABOUT BEING CRUSHED AND HOW
INNOCENT IS ASK HER TO READ THE
INSURANCE POLICY TEXT TO HER
JUST IN CASE HILLARY LOSES AND
HE TWEETED HE ALSO WHY WERE THE
LOVERS TEXT MESSAGES SCRUBBED
AFTER HE LEFT MUELLER.
WHERE ARE THEY, LISA?
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON IT FROM 360'S
RANDI KAYE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE MOMENT
LISA PAGE REALIZED SHE'D HAD
ENOUGH.
>> I LOVE YOU PETER.
I LOVE YOU TOO LISA.
LISA I LOVE YOU.
LISA.
LISA, I LOVE YOU LISA.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES MIMICKING A
SEXUALLY AROUSED LISA PAGE THEN
TEXTING HER LOVER FBI AGENT
PETER STRZOK.
THE TWO WERE HAVING AN AFFAIR
WHILE STRZOK WAS LEADING THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE 2016
ELECTION.
PAGE SPOKE WITH "THE DAILY
BEAST" IN HER FIRST PUBLIC
INTERVIEW SINCE THOUSANDS OF THE
COUPLE'S PRIVATE TEXT MESSAGES
WERE MADE PUBLIC.
SAYING THE PRESIDENT'S DEMEANING
FAKE ORGASM WAS THE STRAW THAT
BROKE THE CAMEL'S BACK CALLING
IT A REPREHENSIBLE, DEGRADING
STUNT.
FOR TWO YEARS TRUMP HAS BEEN ON
A TERROR AGAINST PAGE AND STRZOK
GIVEN T THE ANTI-TRUMP COMMENTS
REVEALED IN THEIR TEXT MESSAGES.
IN AUGUST OF 2016 PAGE WROTE,
TRUMP'S NOT EVER GOING TO BECOME
PRESIDENT, RIGHT?
RIGHT?
STRZOK ANSWERS NO, NO, HE
WOULDN'T.
WE'LL STOP IT.
AND AFTER TRUMP WON THE WHITE
HOUSE STRZOK TEXTED OMG, I'M SO
DEPRESSED PAGE RESPONDED I DON'T
KNOW IF I CAN EAT, VERY
NAUSEOUS.
AND THERE IS NO EVIDENCE AS
TRUMP AND HIS ALLIES SUGGESTED
THAT PAGE AND STRZOK WERE PART
OF A CONSPIRACY TO BRING DOWN
TRUMP'S PRESIDENCY.
PAGE TOLD "THE DAILY BEAST" SHE
DOESN'T USE SOCIAL MEDIA THAT
HER FRIENDS ALERT HER TO THE
PRESIDENT'S DIGS.
IN AUGUST LAST YEAR THE
PRESIDENT TWEETED, WILL THE FBI
EVER RECOVER ITS ONCE STELLAR
REPUTATION, SO BADLY DAMAGED BY
COMEY, McCABE, PETER S. AND HIS
LOVER THE LOVELY LISA PAGE.
ADDING, THE GREAT MEN AND WOMEN
OF THE FBI HAVE BEEN HURT BY
THESE CLOWNS SAND LOSERS.
IN THIS TWEET A MONTH EARLIER,
HE REFERS TO LISA PAGE NOT AS AN
FBI LAWYER, BUT AS AN FBI LOVER.
PAGE TOLD "THE DAILY BEAST" IT
HAD BEEN SO HARD NOT TO DEFEND
MYSELF, TO LET PEOPLE WHO HATE
ME CONTROL THE NARRATIVE.
IT IS LIKE BEING PUNCHED IN THE
GUT.
MY HEART DROPS TO MY STOMACH
WHEN I REALIZE HE HAS TWEETED
ABOUT ME AGAIN.
HE IS DEMEANING HER CAREER AND
CALLING IT SICKENING AND
ACCUSING PAGE OF TREASON WHICH
IS PUNISHABLE BY DEATH.
SHE TOLD THE ZALY BEAST IT IS
INTIMIDATING INSISTING SHE
DIDN'T COMMIT ANY CRIME AND
EXPLAINS THE PRESIDENT IS STILL
SOMEBODY IN A POSITION TO
ACTUALLY DO SOMETHING ABOUT
THAT.
TO TRY TO FURTHER DESTROY MY
LIFE.
LISA PAGE WHO LEFT THE FBI LAST
YEAR SAID ALL SHE WANTS IS HER
LIFE BACK.
BUT THAT IS UNLIKELY TO HAPPEN
ANY TIME SOON.
NEXT WEEK THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT WILL BE
RELEASED.
DETAILING WHETHER TRUMP WAS
UNFAIRLY TARGETED BY THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY IN THE
RUSSIA PROBE.
RANDI KAYE, CNN, PALM BEACH,
FLORIDA.
>>> PERSPECTIVE FROM CNN
POLITICAL ANALYST KIRSTEN POWERS
AND SUSAN HENNESSEY AND LEGAL
NAULTS AND ALSO A FRIEND OF LISA
PAGE.
SUSAN, I KNOW YOU DON'T SPEAK
FOR LISA PAGE BUT IN YOUR
OPINION HOW IMPORTANT IS IT FOR
HER TO FINALLY BE SPEAKING OUT?
>> I THINK IT IS INCREDIBLY
IMPORTANT FOR HER TO BE SPEAKING
OUT FOR A COUPLE OF REASONS.
ONE, I THINK IT IS IMPORTANT
THAT PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THE HUGE
PERSONAL TOLL THAT THE PRESIDENT
DEGRADING DEMEANING DISGUSTING
ATTACKS TAKE ON PEOPLE.
THAT THESE ARE REAL PEOPLE.
SOME PEOPLE WHO HAVE SERVED OUR
COUNTRY OVER A PERIOD OF DECADES
AND TO HAVE HIM ACT LIKE THIS IN
PUBLIC, IT HAS A REAL COST AND
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO UNDERSTAND
THAT.
AND I THINK IT IS SIGNIFICANT
THAT PAGE IS TELLING HER STORY
NOW.
ABOUT WHAT DOJ DID ABOUT THEIR
INVOLVEMENT IN ESSENTIALLY
SELECTIVELY LEAKING TEXT
MESSAGES UNDER CIRCUMSTANCES
THAT CERTAINLY RAISED THE
APPEARANCE THAT THEY WERE NOT
DOING SO BECAUSE IT WAS IN THE
PUBLIC INTEREST BUT INSTEAD THAT
THIS WAS DOJ SENIOR OFFICIALS
AND DOJ SPOKESPERSON ATTEMPTING
TO GIVE THE PRESIDENT FODDER TO
PICK UP THIS FALSE AND MALICIOUS
NARRATIVE AND REALLY ATTEMPT TO
DESTROY THESE PEOPLE'S LIVES.
>> KIRSTEN, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
THIS?
SHE'S REMAINED SILENT FOR YEARS
AS RANDI POINTED OUT IN HER
PIECE AND IN THE INTERVIEW SHE
TALKED ABOUT THE FINAL STRAW WAS
PRESIDENT TRUMP AT THAT OCTOBER
RALLY SEEMINGLY SORT OF -- WELL
READING THE TEXT AS HE DID.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
>> WELL, I MEAN, I THINK THAT
WHAT SHE DID, THE TEXT I THINK
WERE INAPPROPRIATE.
BUT NOTHING THAT SHE DID MERITS
WHAT HAPPENED TO HER.
SO ESPECIALLY BECAUSE THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL FOUND THAT
THERE WASN'T ANY BIAS.
SHE DIDN'T -- IS THERE WAS
NOTHING IN HER WORK THAT WOULD
SUGGEST THAT SHE WAS DOING
ANYTHING -- AND IN FACT ON THE
HILLARY CLINTON INVESTIGATION
SHE WAS MORE AGGRESSIVE THAN
SOME OF THE OTHER PEOPLE IN
TERMS OF PURSUING CLINTON.
SO IT DOESN'T SEEM TO HAVE
IMPACTED HER WORK.
AND SO PEOPLE ARE JUST SORT OF
SELECTIVELY CHOOSING THE TEXT
WHICH ARE JUST HER EXPRESSING
HER PERSONAL OPINIONS.
THEY ARE IN APPROPRIATE BUT IT
DOESN'T GIVE THE PRESIDENT THE
RIGHT TO BULLY HER WHICH IS WHAT
HE IS DOING.
HE IS DESTROYING THIS WOMAN'S
LIFE.
AND SHE'S STILL WITH HER
HUSBAND, I GATHER.
SHE HAS CHILDREN.
SHE HAS EVERY RIGHT TO GET ON
WITH HER LIFE.
SHE HAD AN AFFAIR.
THAT IS A PRIVATE ISSUE.
AND CERTAINLY PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
IN NO POSITION TO BE SITTING IN
JUDGMENT OF THAT.
>> SUSAN, DO YOU THINK THAT PAGE
HAS BEEN PARTICULARLY TARGETED
BY THE PRESIDENT BECAUSE SHE'S A
WOMAN?
>> I DO.
I THINK IT IS SORT OF
INDISPUTABLE THERE IS THIS CLEAR
MISOGYNISTIC UNDERTONE THAT HE
SPEAKS ABOUT HER IN OVERTLY
SEXUALIZE TERMS AND DISCUSSING
HER PHYSICAL APPEARANCE AND
DOESN'T DISCUSS OTHER
INDIVIDUALS THE SAME WAY AND I
DO THINK IT IS QUITE CLEAR THAT
THE PRESIDENT IS TARGETING HER
FOR A PARTICULAR TYPE OF
DEBASING DEGRADING COMMENTS THAT
IN PART BECAUSE SHE'S A WOMAN.
LET'S KEEP IN MIND, THIS IS A
SERIOUS SEASONED NATIONAL
SECURITY PROFESSIONAL.
THIS IS SOMEBODY WHO HAS A LOT
OF SUBSTANCE AND A SERIOUS
PERSON AND THE ONLY WAY THE
PRESIDENT REFERRED TO HER AS THE
LOVELY LISA PAGE, THE LOVER.
HE REALLY DOES TRY TO SORT OF
DEGRADE HER AND DEMEAN HER AND
THAT IS A TREND WE'VE SEEN
HIM -- THAT IS A PATTERN WE'VE
SEEN FROM THE PRESIDENT WITH
REGARDS TO ANY WOMAN WHO REALLY
WOULD DARE TO SPEAK OUT AGAINST
HIM OR CHALLENGE HIM IN ANY WAY.
>> KIRSTEN, DO YOU AGREE WITH
THAT?
DO YOU SEE A WAY HE SPEAKS ABOUT
WOMEN THAT IS DIFFERENT?
BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY HE DEGRADES
MANY PEOPLE.
BUT MALE AND FEMALE.
DOES HE SPEAK ABOUT WOMEN IN A
DIFFERENT WAY THAT YOU NOTICE?
>> YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK THAT HE -- PEOPLE CAN
SAY OH, HE'S AN EQUAL
OPPORTUNITY OFFENDER BECAUSE HE
ATTACKS MEN BUT SUSAN IS RIGHT
THERE IS A WAY THAT HE ATTACKS
WOMEN THAT IS DIFFERENT, THAT
TENDS TO BE GENDERED IN THE WAY
THAT HE DOES IT.
AND THIS IS SO DISPROPORTIONATE
TO WHAT HAPPENED ALSO.
THERE IS SO MANY TWEETS ABOUT
THIS WOMAN WHO HAS A FAMILY AND
A LIFE AND A CAREER AND THE GLEE
THAT HE HAS, NOT JUST WITH HER
BUT WITH OTHER PEOPLE AND IN
TRYING TO DESTROY PEOPLE IS SO
TROUBLING.
AND THERE WAS A TIME WHEN WE
WOULD SAY THIS IS UNPRESIDENTIAL
BUT PEOPLE DON'T SEEM TO CARE
ANY MORE.
HIS SUPPORTERS DON'T CARE HOW
UNPRESIDENTIAL THIS IS AND HOW
INDECENT IT IS.
THIS IS NOT HOW WE SHOULD TREAT
PEOPLE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS SAIDS IT
PRESIDENTIAL BECAUSE THE
PRESIDENT DOES IT SO THEREFORE
THIS IS NOW PRESIDENTIAL.
>> YEAH.
WELL, I WOULD SAY WE HAVE A LOT
OF OTHER PRESIDENTS AND SO WE
DON'T CHANGE THE -- OUR ENTIRE
STANDARD BASED ON ONE PERSON'S
BEHAVIOR.
I WOULD LOOK AT THE HISTORY OF
HOW PEOPLE HAVE TYPICALLY
BEHAVED AND THIS IS UNTHINKABLE.
ABSOLUTELY UNTHINKABLE OF ANY
OTHER PRESIDENT DOING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS.
>> KIRSTEN POWERS SUSAN
HENNESSEY, APPRECIATE IT.
>>> JUST AHEAD, POPULAR DEFENSE
OF PRESIDENT TRUMP JUST GONE UP
IN SMOKE ACCORDING TO A NEW
REPORT, I'LL TALKING TO FORMER
REPUBLICAN SENATOR AND
CONGRESSMAN WHO ALSO SERVED AS
DEFENSE SECRETARY ABOUT HOW HIS
PARTY HAS COME TO EMBRACE
CONSPIRACY THEORIES UNDER THIS
PRESIDENT.
♪♪
I'm a Verizon engineer,
and I'm part of the team
building the most powerful
5G experience for America.
It's 5G Ultra Wideband--
--for massive capacity--
--and ultra-fast speeds.
Almost 2 gigs
here in Minneapolis.
That's 25 times faster
than today's network
in New York City.
So people from
Midtown Manhattan--
--to Downtown Denver--
--can experience
what our 5G can deliver.
(woman)
And if Verizon 5G can deliver
performance like this
in these places...
It's pretty crazy.
...just imagine
what it can do for you.
♪♪
It's time to make
mopping history.
Introducing the new
Braava jet m6 robot mop.
With an adjustable precision jet
spray and advanced pad system
Braava jet breaks up messes
and gets deep in corners.
Braava jet.
Only from iRobot.
>>> POLITICO IS REPORTING THAT
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE FOUND
TO EVIDENCE SO SUPPORT A KEY
CLAIM BY THE PRESIDENT'S TOP
DEFENDERS ON IMPEACHMENT.
THE CLAIM WHICH IS ALWAYS
UNFOUNDED IS THAT IT WASN'T JUST
INDIVIDUAL UKRAINIANS OPPOSED TO
TRUMP OR HIS POLICIES IT WAS A
TOP DOWN EFFORT JUST LIKE WITH
RUSSIA.
HERE IS JOHN KENNEDY WHO ALREADY
HAD TO WALK BACK A SEPARATE
UKRAINIAN CONSPIRACY THEORY
MAKING THIS OTHER CLAIM OVER THE
WEEKEND.
>> I THINK BOTH RUSSIA AND
UKRAINE MEDDLED IN THE 2016
ELECTION.
>> THE FACT THAT RUSSIA WAS SO
AGGRESSIVE DOES NOT EXCLUDE THE
FACT THAT PRESIDENT POROSHENKO
ACTIVELY WORKED FOR SECRETARY
CLINTON.
>> AGAIN, POLITICO REPORTS THAT
THE SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE FOUND NO EVIDENCE THE
UKRAINE LEADERS DIRECTED ANY
EFFORT TOWARD CANDIDATE TRUMP
AND SENATOR KENNEDY WAS ASKED IF
HE ATTENDED A RECENT BRIEFING
FOR INTELLIGENCE SENATOR THAT
RUSSIA IS USING CONSPIRACY
THEORIES AND NO, HE DID NOT
ATTEND.
WE HAVE SECRETARY COHEN.
AS A FRESHMAN SENATOR AND YOU
BROKE WITH REPUBLICANS AND
PLAYED A CRUCIAL ROLE IN THE
DELIBERATIONS ON IMPEACHING
RICHARD NIXON AND WHEN YOU SEE
WHAT IS HAPPENING TODAY WHEN
REPUBLICANS BUY INTO CONSPIRACY
THEORIES TO BACK THE PRESIDENT,
WHAT GOES THROUGH YOUR MIND ON
WHERE THE REPUBLICAN PARTY IS AT
LEAST IN THE HOUSE.
>> WELL IT IS DISAPPOINTING.
I GO BACK 40 YEARS AND LOOK AT
THE MEMBERS OF THE COMMITTEE,
THERE WERE GREAT DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN THE REPUBLICANS AND THE
DEMOCRATS.
BUT THERE WERE REPUBLICANS ON
THE COMMITTEE WHO WERE WILLING
TO LISTEN TO THE FACTS.
AND TO FOLLOW WHERE THE FACTS
WOULD LEAD.
AND THEY LED TO THE IMPEACHMENT
OF RICHARD NIXON ON ABUSE OF
POWER AND OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
THERE WAS ANOTHER OBSTRUCTION OF
CONGRESS AS WELL.
I SAW THE SAME KIND OF
REPUBLICAN SPIRIT OF FOLLOWING
THE LAW DURING IRAN CONTRA.
ONCE AGAIN THE FACTS REALLY
MATTERED.
AND NOW IT SEEMS THAT FACTS
DON'T REALLY MATTER.
THAT THEY HAVE THE, QUOTE,
ALTERNATIVE FACT MANTRA THAT IS
RECITED REPEATEDLY.
THERE IS ONLY ONE SET OF FACTS.
YOU COULD HAVE DIFFERENT
OPINIONS ABOUT WHAT THE FACTS
MEAN.
BUT ONLY ONE SET.
AND NOW I SEE AS THE EQUIVALENT
OF SORT OF PEPPER SPRAY BEING
USED TO BLIND THE EYES OF THE
PEOPLE FROM SEEING WHAT THE
FACTS ARE.
I SAW NO EVIDENCE PRESENTED
DURING ANY OF THE COMMITTEE
HEARINGS AND I BELIEVE THAT IS
THE CASE WITH THE SENATE
INVESTIGATION AS WELL THAT
INDICATED THAT UKRAINE HAD ANY
ORGANIZED ATTEMPT TO INTERFERE.
WHAT I DO REMEMBER IS PRESIDENT
CLINTON WHEN HE WAS CANDIDATE --
TRUMP, RATHER, WHEN HE SAID
RUSSIA, ARE YOU LISTENING?
THEY WERE LISTENING.
FOUR HOURS AFTER HE MADE THAT
SPEECH, THE GRU GOT INVOLVED IN
ATTACKING THE DEMOCRATIC
HEADQUARTERS AND THEIR CAMPAIGN.
NOW WITH THE QUESTION OF
UKRAINE, YOU BETTER BE LISTENING
AND THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT TOOK
PLACE HERE.
QUID PRO QUO PEOPLE ARE TIRED OF
HEARING IT.
BUT BASICALLY IT IS SAYING THAT
THE PRESIDENT IN ESSENCE WAS
SAYING I HAVE SOMETHING THAT YOU
NEED.
YOU HAVE SOMETHING THAT I WANT.
LET'S MAKE A DEAL.
YOU GO FIRST.
THAT IS THE ESSENCE OF WHAT HAS
TAKEN PLACE WITH UKRAINE.
AND SO THOSE ARE THE FACTS.
AND I DON'T CARE WHAT OTHERS SAY
THAT THE UKRAINIANS WERE SOMEHOW
INVOLVED OR BIDEN'S SON WAS
SOMEHOW INVOLVED, THE FACTS ARE
CLEAR THAT THE PRESIDENT INVITED
ANOTHER COUNTRY TO PARTICIPATE
IN OUR ELECTOR SYSTEM.
THAT TO ME IS AN IMPEACHABLE
OFFENSE.
>> AND YOU'RE THE FORMER
SECRETARY OF DEFENSE.
WHAT DOES THIS SAY ABOUT THE
STATE OF THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
WHEN THEY CLAIM THERE WAS
INTERFERENCE IN THE ELECTION
WHICH IS A RUSSIAN CONSPIRACY
THEORY.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE SENATORS AND
CONGRESS PEOPLE IN WATERGATE, I
IMAGINE THOSE REPUBLICANS WHO
YOU SAID WERE LISTENING TO THE
FACTS, THEY MUST HAVE BEEN
FACING PRESSURE IN THEIR HOME
DISTRICTS BY PEOPLE WHO
SUPPORTED NIXON AND DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE NIXON GO DOWN.
HOW WERE THEY ABLE TO MUSTER THE
COURAGE TO LISTEN TO FACTS WHEN
THESE FOLKS DON'T SEEM TO BE?
>> WELL IT WAS A DIFFERENT WORLD
THEN.
WE DIDN'T HAVE SOCIAL MEDIA.
WE DIDN'T HAVE ONE NETWORK
DEVOTED TO DEFENDING THE
PRESIDENT.
SO IT WAS A DIFFERENT WORLD.
BUT NONETHELESS, THEY FELT
COMPELLED TO RISE ABOVE THEIR
OWN PARTY INTEREST AND PUT THE
COUNTRY FIRST.
AND THAT IS REALLY WHAT IS AT
STAKE HERE.
THIS IS ABOUT, YES, ABOUT TRUMP
AND THE IMPEACHMENT OF TRUMP.
BUT REALLY WHAT IS AT STAKE IS
THE RULE OF LAW.
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID
THE RULES DON'T APPLY TO HIM.
THAT HE CAN'T BE CHARGED WITH
ANYTHING.
THAT HE CAN'T EVEN BE
INVESTIGATED.
SO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT ONE MAN
RULE.
THAT IS NOT DEMOCRACY.
THAT IS SOMETHING CLOSER TO
AUTOCRACY OR CERTAINLY TO A
DICTATORSHIP.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE ONCE THEY LISTEN TO ALL
OF THE FACTS WILL SAY THAT IS A
STANDARD WE WANT.
NO RULES APPLY TO ANY PRESIDENT
GOING FORWARD.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE SUPPORT THAT.
I THINK IT IS INCOUPLE BENT UPON
THE DEMOCRATS BECAUSE THE
REPUBLICANS ARE NOT GOING TO
JOIN IN, INCUMBENT TO MAKE THE
CASE THAT WE DON'T WANT TO THROW
AWAY ALL THAT WE HAVE
ACCUMULATED OVER THE YEARS, THE
RULE OF LAW SEPARATES US FROM
THE LAW OF RULE.
THE LAW OF THE JUNGLE.
OF MIGHT MAKES RIGHT.
AND IF WE SUCCUMB TO THE NOTION
THAT THE PRESIDENT IS ABOVE THE
LAW, THEN I THINK WE ARE
SACRIFICING THE DEMOCRATIC
SYSTEM AND AMERICA WILL NOT BE
THE COUNTRY WE THOUGHT IT IS OR
SHOULD BE.
>> SECRETARY, THAT IS OMINOUS.
I APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
>> MY PLEASURE.
>>> STILL AHEAD, SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
THE RIDICULIST.
HOW DEVOTED PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
TO IMAGES OF -- GUESS WHO?
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
BE RIGHT BACK.
[Sneezing]
♪♪
You don't want to
cancel your plans.
[Sneezing]
Cancel your cold.
The 1-pill power of Advil
Multi-Symptom Cold & Flu
knocks out your worst symptoms.
Cancel your cold,
not your plans.
Advil Multi-Symptom
Cold & Flu.
The holidays are
here and we want to
keep you connected
to those you love,
with the new iPhone 11.
Hurry into T-Mobile today,
to get up to four
iPhone 11's ON US.
Only at T-Mobile.
♪♪
Hi Honey, we got in early.
Yeah, and we brought Steve and
Mark.
♪♪
Experience the power of
sanctuary
at the Lincoln Wish List Sales
Event.
Sign and drive off in a new
Lincoln with zero down,
zero due at signing,
and a complimentary first
month's payment.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
TIME TO CHECK IN WITH CHRIS TO
SEE WHAT HE'S WORKING ON FOR
"CUOMO PRIME TIME."
>> WE ARE GOING TO TRY TO GET
INSIDE THE FACTS THAT SHOW THE
OBVIOUS, THAT THIS PRESIDENT IS
PEDDLING CONSPIRACY THEORIES TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE JUST AS A
CYA.
THIS STUFF ABOUT UKRAINE ISN'T
NEW, IT'S NEVER BEEN REAL AND
NEW REPORTING OF WHO CAME TO
EXACTLY THAT CONCLUSION?
SENATE REPUBLICANS, THAT THE GOP
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH RIGHT
BEFORE THIS PROCESS.
WHY?
>> WE'LL WATCH CHRIS EIGHT
MINUTES FROM NOW.
COMING UP, SOMETHING TO MAKE US
ALL SMILE AT THE END OF THE DAY,
THE RIDICULIST IS NEXT.
D
Be The Match uses the
power of the Cisco Network
to match donors with
patients faster than ever,
saving lives like Max's.
Me and Dylan are DNA twins.
♪ ♪ ♪
Dylan's like my brother.
Cisco. The bridge to possible.
Like you,
my hands are
everything to me.
But I was diagnosed with
Dupuytren's contracture.
And it got to the point
where things I took
for granted
got tougher to do.
Thought surgery
was my only option.
Turns out I was wrong.
So when a hand specialist told
me about nonsurgical treatments,
it was a total
game changer.
Like you, my hands have
a lot more to do.
Learn more at
FactsOnHand.com today.
(Beep)
Like you, my hands have
a lot more to do.
The ups and downs
of frequent mood swings
can plummet you
to extreme lows.
(Crying)
Lift you to intense highs.
(Muffled arguing)
Or, make you feel
both at once.
Overwhelmed by
bipolar I symptoms?
Ask about VRAYLAR.
Some medications only treat
the lows or the highs.
VRAYLAR effectively
treats depression,
acute manic and mixed
episodes of bipolar I.
Full-spectrum relief
of all symptoms.
With just one pill,
once a day.
Elderly patients with
dementia-related psychosis
have an increased risk
of death or stroke.
Call your doctor
about unusual changes
in behavior or
suicidal thoughts.
Antidepressants
can increase these
in children and young adults.
Report fever, stiff
muscles, or confusion,
which may mean
a life-threatening reaction,
or uncontrollable
muscle movements,
may be permanent.
Side effects may not appear
for several weeks.
Metabolic changes may occur.
Movement dysfunction,
restlessness, sleepiness,
stomach issues are
common side effects.
When bipolar I overwhelms,
VRAYLAR helps smooth
the ups and downs.
[Farmers bell]
♪
(Burke)
A "Rock and Wreck."
Seen it. Covered it.
At Farmers Insurance,
we know a thing or two
because we've seen
a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
.
>>> TONIGHT NOT SINCE NARCISSEUS
HAS A GUY BEEN SO IN LOVE WITH
HIS OWN IMAGE THAN PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
TODAY THE PRESIDENT TWEETED --
ACTUALLY, IT WAS MORE LIKE A
YELL.
IS THERE A YELL TWEET?
I'LL GO WITH 2TWELL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP FOUND TIME TODAY
TO RETWEET A PORTRAIT OF
HIMSELF.
THE PORTRAIT IS VERY GOOD, AN
ARTIST WHO SPENT 70 HOURS
DRAWING ONLY WITH BALL POINT
PEN.
HE'S FROM NIGERIA, WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID PEOPLE
THERE ONLY LIVE IN HUTS.
MAYBE SOON EVERYONE WHO WANTS A
VISA TO AMERICA WILL HAVE TO
DRAW A PICTURE OF OUR PRESIDENT
OR OF STEPHEN MILLER.
MUCH HAVE BEEN MADE OF DICTATORS
AND AUTHORITARIAN FIGURES.
DAYS AFTER ATTACKING MARIA
YOVANOVITCH FOR NOT HANGING UP
HIS PORTRAIT IN THE U.S.
EMBASSY, WHICH IS NOT AT ALL
WHAT HAPPENED, THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED THIS PHOTOSHOPPED IMAGE
OF HIM AS ROCKY, WHICH IS
TOTALLY WHAT HIS CHEST LOOKS
LIKE.
HE IS JACKED AND HE'S RIPPED
I'VE SEEP THE PHOTOS OF HIM
PLAYING TENNIS.
BY THE WAY, DO NOT GOOGLE TRUMP
JUST DON'T.
IT LIKE "THE RING," LIKE THAT
MOVIE, YOU CAN'T UNSEE IT.
ANYWAY, IT WAS JUST LAST
MONTH -- YEAH, I PUT ON MY
GLASSES MID RIDICULIST.
IT WAS JUST LAST MONTH THAT A
JUDGE ORDERED MR. TRUMP'S DEFUNT
SO-CALLED FOUND ACE TO PAY $2
MILLION TO CHARITIES AS PART OF
A SETTLEMENT WITH NEW YORK
ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE
BECAUSE THEY HAD DO SHADY
THINGS, INCLUDING USING FUNDS TO
BUY TWO GIANT PORTRAITS OF
DONALD TRUMP.
THAT'S ONE OF HI
I BELIEVE THAT'S THE ARTIST ON
THE OTHER SIDE.
THE ALLEGED CHARITY SUPPOSEDLY
PAID $10,000 FOR THAT PORTRAIT
AND HUNG IT AT THE PRESIDENT'S
DO
DORAL, FLORIDA GOLF COURSE.
AND THERE'S THIS PHONY "TIME"
MAGAZINE COVER.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THE IDEA
DIDN'T COME TO THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF.
I KNOW TRUMP DOES HAVE A FAKE
MASTER PIECE BY THE FRENCH
ARTIST RENOIR HANGING IN HIS NEW
YORK APARTMENT.
IT'S A BAD COPY OF THE PAINTING
"TWO SISTERS."
THE REAL ONE, WHICH IS WORTH
PROBABLY IN THE RANGE OF $100
MILLION IS IN THE ART INSTITUTE
OF CHICAGO.
MR. TRUMP HAS IN THE PAST
INSISTED HIS PHONY RENOIR IS THE
REAL DEAL, WHICH MAY TELL YOU
SOMETHING ABOUT HOW HE VIEWS THE
ENTIRE DEAL MAKING PROCESS.
MAYBE THE PRESIDENT'S INTEREST
OF SEEING HIS OWN FACE ON TV AND
IN MAGAZINES WILL LESSEN IN THE
COMING YEARS BUT HOW MANY
BILLIONAIRES TURNED PRESIDENTS
EGOS HAVE SHRUNK OVER TIME?
SO MAKE A PICTURE OF THE
PRESIDENT AND IT MIGHT GET YOU A
CAMEO ON THE RIDICULIST.
NOW I TURN IT OVER TO CHRIS
CUOMO.
>> THANK YOU, ANDERSON.
I AM CHRIS CUOMO AND THIS IS
"PRIME TIME."
WE HAVE TWO NEW PIECES OF REPORT
TAG REVEAL THAT REPUBLICANS WERE
WELL AWARE OF THIS UKRAINE
NONSENSE AND THEY LOOKED INTO IT
IN THEIR SENATE INTEL COMMITTEE.
WHAT WERE THE RESULTS?
WE HAVE THEM.
AND WE'RE GOING TO DIG INTO A
TROUBLING QUESTION TONIGHT.
DID THIS CALL THAT THE PRESIDENT
CLAIMS VINDICATES HIM WITH EU
AMBASSADOR SONDLAND, DID IT EVER
HAPPEN?
WHY THAT'S A REAL QUESTION.
AND A DEMOCRATIC SENATOR WITH A
STATE OF PLAY IN THE SENATE BEEP
HAVE A REPUBLICAN MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS TO ASK IF HE OKAY WITH
WHAT THE PRESIDENT SELLING TO
THIS COUNTRY?
IT'S A BIG WEEK.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, LET'S GET AFTER
IT.
>>> ONE SIDE NOTE, THE HOUSE
INTEL IMPEACHMENT REPORT IS
COMPLETE.
HOW CAN THAT BE A SIDE NOTE?
IT ALL ABOUT A THE STATE OF PLAY
FOR THE PRESIDENT.
THAT'S BEING AHEAD OF TOMORROW'S
BIG VOTE AND WE'LL START GOING
TO THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE AND
SEE WHAT HAPPENS THERE.
THE GOP VERSION IS OUT AS WELL.
THE TWO REPORTS LITERALLY BARE
IN RESEMBLANCE TO EACH OTHER.
ONE SET OF FACTS, TWO REALITIES.
FIRST WE HAVE BREAKING NEWS THAT
WILL HELP UNDERSTAND THE FACTS
IN THIS SITUATION JUST DROPPING
ON OUR WATCH.
IT TAKES US INTO THE PAST OF THE
SENATE INTEL COMMITTEE.
AS YOU MAY KNOW, RUN BY
REPUBLICANS.
HERE WHAT'S CNN'S JAKE TAPPER
CAN CONFIRM FOR US.
THAT PANEL, AGAIN, LED BY
REPUBLICANS, LOOKED INTO
ALLEGATIONS THAT UKRAINE
INTERFERED IN THE 2016 ELECTION.
WAIT, THEY DID?
BECAUSE THEY'RE SAYING IT JUST
HAPPENED.
I KNOW.
THAT'S WHY IN MATTERS.
THEY LOOKED AT IT WAY BACK IN
2017, IN 2017.
WHAT DID THEY FIND?
NO EVIDENCE TO SUPPORT THE
CLAIMS.
WELL, THE DNC LADY THAT'S GOT
THE SAME NAME AS THE TACO
BELL -- YES, CHALUPA.
YES, THEY LOOKED INTO IT.
THE BLACK BOOK THAT'S FAKE --
AND THAT NAME BROUGHT UP AGAIN
AND AGAIN BY NUNEZ AND ALL THOSE
OTHER CLOWNS AND DEFENDERS
DURING THE HEARINGS, THEY LOOKED
INTO IT.
THEY FOUND NOTHING.
THAT IS KNOWN BY THE SAME PEOPLE
WHO ARE PRETENDING THEY'RE REAL
QUESTIONS NOW.
WHY?
NOW THAT'S A QUESTION WORTH
GETTING AFTER RIGHT NOW.
LET'S PUT IT TO GOP CONGRESSMAN
RANDY WEBER.
I HOPE YOU HAD A GOOD
THANKSGIVING.
>> THANK YOU, CHRIS.
WE DID.
I HOPE YOU DID, TOO.
>> NOW, I AM NOT BLAMING YOU FOR
THIS.
I ASKED SENATOR KENNEDY TO COME
ON THE SHOW.
HE CAME ON LAST WEEK TO CLARIFY
HIS COMMENTS, HE THEN SEEMED TO
WALK BACKWARDS.
HE'S INVITED WHENEVER.
HOWEVER, YOU DO NOT BELIEVE THE
COMMENTS BY SENATOR BURR ARE
WRONG, RIGHT?
>> NOW, YOU'RE SAYING RUSSIA OR
UKRAINE, CHRIS?
>> I'M SAYING RUSSIA BECAUSE I'M
SPEAKING ABOUT FACT HERE.
RUSSIA DID IT.
BURR SAID IT IN HIS COMMITTEE,
THE INTEL COMMITTEE SAID IT.
EVERYONE WHO HAS LOOKED AT IT
HAS SAID IT.
DO YOU AGREE WITH THAT?
>> OF COURSE THAT'S WHAT-T THEY
SAY THEY FOUND.
THAT'S A POINT OF CONTENTION.
>> IT'S NOT A POINT OF
CONTENTION.
>> THE FACT THAT THERE IS
LEFTOVER INTEREST IN WHAT
HAPPENED ON HOW THE RUSSIANS AND
UKRAINIANS DID IT.
>> NO, NO UKRAINE.
>> I GET THAT.
>> YOU JUST ADDED THEM.
DOESN'T ADD THEM.
BECAUSE THEY HAVE NOTHING TO DO
WITH IT.
>> WHAT I'M SAYING IS THE
PRESIDENT THINKS THAT THEY DID.
HE DOESN'T TRUST THE GOVERNMENT
OF UKRAINE AND THAT'S PART AND
PARCEL TO EVERYTHING HE'S BEEN
DO
DOING.
>> DOES HE TRUST REPUBLICANS?
>> I'M SORRY?
>> DOES THE PRESIDENT TRUST
REPUBLICANS?
>> YEAH.
>> HE'S GOING TO TRUST
REPUBLICANS FOR THE MOST PART,
ABSOLUTELY HE'S GOING TO, THOSE
WHO STAND BY HIS SIDE AND AREN'T
AFRAID OF ALL THE VITRIOL AIMED
AT HIM.
>> DO YOU THINK HE --
>> YOU SAID I