THANKS FOR BEING WITH US
TONIGHT.
SEE YOU TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT FROM NEW YORK.
[♪♪♪]
TRISH: THE RELEASE OF THE
HOROWITZ REPORT INTO THE MISUSE
OF FBI RESOURCES TO SPY ON AN
INNOCENT AMERICAN.
THE IMPEACHMENT EFFORT IS
GETTING DESPERA..
IT'S THE BEGINNING OF THE END
FOR THE DEMS.
BUT THEY ARE KNEE DEEP IN A
TOTAL SCHIFF STORM TO SIGHT.
GOOD EVENING.
AS WE BATTLE A SNOWSTORM IN THE
NORTHEAST, WASHINGTON IS
BATTLING A SCHIFF STORM OF ITS
OWN MAKING.
THE PRESIDENT IS REFUSING TO
TESTIFY IN THIS ROUND.
WHY SHOULD HE?
WHY WOULD HE?
GIVEN THE BIAS, CONJECTURE AND
LACK OF NEUTRALITY IN COVERING
THIS IMPEACHMENT ORDEAL, HE
WOULD HAVE TO BE CRAZY TO STEP
FOOT IN THEIR COURTROOM.
IF ONLY TO LOOK AT THE
MAINSTREAM MEDIA'S RESPONSE TO
THE PRESIDENT TRAVELING TO
AFGHANISTAN TO VISIT THE TROOPS.
NEWS WEEK TWEETED THAT HE'S
GOLFING AND TWEETING.
THAT'S WHAT HE WAS DOING.
THERE YOU HAVE IT.
HE WENT TO SEE OUR TROOPS.
HE WENT TO THANK THEM FOR ALL
THEIR HARD WORK.
THE FACT THAT THEY ARE RISKING
THEIR LIVES EVERY DAY TO PROTECT
ALL OF US SO WE CAN HAVE THE
FREEDOMS WE HAVE.
IT'S INTERPRETATION VERSUS
REALITY.
THIS IS ALL WE HAVE GOTTEN FOR
NEARLY THREE STRAIGHT YEARS FROM
BOTH THE MEDIA AND THE LEFT.
THEY SAY HE HAS DONE A HORRIBLE
JOB AS PRESIDENT.
BUT THE REALITY IS OUR STOCK
MARKET IS AT A RECORD HIGH.
UNEMPLOYMENT IS AT A RECORD LOW.
YOU WONDER WHY THE PRESIDENT
REFUSED TO FEED THE BEAST.
WHY TESTIFY WHEN ANYTHING AND
EVERYTHING YOU SAY WILL BE FOR
CERTAIN USED AGAINST YOU.
THERE IS NO BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT
WHEN IT COMES TO HIM.
ALL THE MORE REASON FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO REVOKE BLOOMBERG'S'
JOURNALIST CREDENTIALS.
I USED TO WORK THERE AT
BLOOMBERG AND I USED TO LIKE TO
THINK THE PLACE WAS FAIR.
GRANTED I KNEW OF IT HAD TO
BIASES.
BUT TO SAY YOU WILL NOT COVER
ONE SIDE OF THE STORY AS A NEWS
ORGANIZATION?
THAT'S PATHETIC.
YET IT'S ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF THIS
DANGEROUS PATH OUR COUNTRY IS
TAKING AS THE LEFT TRIES TO
LIMIT OUR FIRST AMENDMENT.
SO KUDOS, KUDOS TO THE PRESIDENT
TO NOT PARTAKE IN THAT.
BUT LET'S GET BACK TO THE TRIP
HE TOOK TO AFGHANISTAN.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THAT.
I WAS CURIOUS.W
HOW MANY TIMES DID PRESIDENT
OBAMA VISIT OUR TROOPS ON
THANKSGIVING?
THE ANSWER ZERO.
BUT HE DID VISIT TROOPS IN
AFGHANISTAN ON MEMORIAL DAY,
DURING HANUKKAH AND AROUND
EASTER TIME.
WHEN HE DID GO, HOW DID THE
MEDIA REACT?
>> MORE THAN 3,500U.S. TROOPS
STOOD DMEARG A BAGRAM AIRFIELD
HANGAR.
>> IT TAKES A LONG TRIP TO GO TO
AFGHANISTAN.
PROPS TO THE PRESIDENT FOR GOING
TO AFGHANISTAN.
I WANT YOU TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
YOU JUST SAW, THEIR REACTION TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND COMPARE THAT
TO WHAT WE SAW THIS PAST HOLIDAY
WEEKEND WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
WENT TO AFGHANISTAN.
>> TODAY'S SURPRISE COMES AS THE
PRESIDENT FACES BLISTERING
CRITICISM.
>> IT FIRST TRIP COMES AMONG
GROWING TENSIONS.
>> THE IMPEACHMENT BATTLE IS
GOING ON.
THE PRESIDENT IS UNDER ATTACK IN
ALL SORTS OF WAYS.
ARE WE GOING TO SEE MORE
OVERSEAS TRIPS GIVEN THESE
PHOTO-OP SCENARIOS?
TRISH: THE GUY CAN'T GET A
BREAK.
YOU DO SOMETHING GOOD, THEY
ATTACK YOU.
THAT'S ALL THEY ARE CAPABLE OF.
NEWSFLASH, THAT DOES NOT AND
WILL NOT RESONATE WITH EVERYDAY
AMERICANS.
WE WANT A PRESIDENT WHO DOES HIS
JOB.
MEDIA BE DAMNED.
JOINING US, PENNSYLVANIA
CONGRESSMAN, GUY RUSHENTHAL.
HE'S THANKING OUR TROOPS IN
AFGHANISTAN OVER THANKSGIVING,
AND THEY CAN'T GIVE HIM PROPS
FOR THAT.
>> I SAW THE VIDEO AND THE
TROOPS WERE THRILLED TO HAVE HIM
THERE AND IT LOOKED LIKE THE
PRESIDENT WAS ENJOYING HIS TIME
THERE.
TRISH: I GUESS IT DOESN'T MEAN
ANYTHING TO THE LEFT OR THE MY
YEAH.
IT BRINGS US -- LEFT OR THE
MEDIA.
IT BRINGS US BACK TO THE SCHIFF
SHOW.
IT'S GOING TO MOVE TOWARD THE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE.
>> WEDNESDAY JERRY NADLER WILL
HOLD A HEARING AND BRING IN SOME
LEFT-WING COLLEGE PROFESSORS AND
TRY TO PUT THIS VENEER ON THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS TO MAKE
IT LOOK LIKE IT'S ACADEMIC AND
IMPARTIAL AND A LEGAL
PROCEEDING.
HE'S NOT GOING TO FOOL ANYBODY.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE KNOW THIS IS
A POLITICAL ATTACK JOB TO UNDO
THE WILL OF THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
IN THE 2016 ELECTION.
TRISH: IT'S ALMOST AS IF THEY
ARE DOING IT TO THEMSELVES.
IT'S OVER.
YOU LOOK AT POLL AFTER POLL, YOU
LOOK AT INDEPENDENT.
THEY ARE SICK OF IT.
THEY SEE THROUGH IT.
AND YET THEY ARE DIGGING THEIR
OWN DRIVE.
MAYBE THEY HAVE A CHANCE TO TALK
TO SOME OF THEIR CONSTITUENTS.
>> WHAT'S HAPPENING IS THE
DEMOCRATS HAVE BACKED THEMSELVES
INTO A CORNER BECAUSE NANCY
PELOSI CEDED LEADERSHIP OF THIS
PARTY TO AOC AND THE FAR LEFT
FRESHMEN.
THIS IS NOT THE PARTY OF JFK.
THIS IS NOT YOUR GRANDFATHER'S
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
FOR STARTERS I'M NOT SURE IF
NANCY PELOSI HAS THE VOTES TO
GET AN IMPEACHMENT VOTE.
I'M NOT SURE SHE CAN DO IT.
SO IF THAT HAPPENS SHE LOOKS
WEAK.
IF SHE DO MOVE FORWARD WITH
IMPEACHMENT THIS WILL BLOW BACK
ON THEM AND THEY WILL LOSE
GROUND IN THOSE BATTLEGROUND
DISTRICTS.
THOSE ARE DISTRICTS THE
DEMOCRATS HOLD THAT TRUMP WON.
FOR YOU TO EXPLAIN YOU VOTED TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT --
TRISH: IT WON'T FLY.
YOU MENTIONED THE SQUAD LID BY
AOC AND ILHAN OMAR.
MY COLLEAGUE LAURA INGRAHAM
LIKES TO SAY HIT SQUAD.
WE HAVE SOUND OF ILHAN OMAR
LIKENING THE PRESIDENT TO A MOB
BOSS.
>> I USE EXAMPLES WHERE YOU HAVE
MOB BOSSES WHO COMMITTED
ATROCITY AFTER ATROCITY.
WE GOT THEM ON ONE CASE AND THEY
GET TO SERVE TIME.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU ARE
ARTFULLY MAKING A COMPARISON ON
THE LEGAL LESS DENT TO THIS
PRESIDENT AND AL CAPONE WITHOUT
SAYING AL CAPONE.
>> THAT'S RICH.
THE FAR LEFT DEMOCRATS ARE
TRYING TO BASE THIS ENTIRE
ARGUMENT ON THE QUID PRO QUO
THEORY.
YOU CANNOT MAKE THE ARGUMENT
THAT ZELENSKY KNEW THERE WAS A
QUID PRO QUO.
HE DID NOT KNOW THE SAID WAS
UNDER REVIEW.
SO FOR THEM TO PROSECUTE THIS
CASE WHEN THE FACTS AREN'T
THERE.
I WAS A PROSECUTOR IN THE NAVY.
I WAS A DEFENSE ATTORNEY.
I WAS A DISTRICT JUDGE FOR A
PERIOD OF TIME.
I WOULD NOT WANT TO PROSECUTE
THIS CASE AND I WOULD NOT ALLOW
THIS CASE TO GO TO TRIAL BECAUSE
THE EVIDENCE ISN'T THERE TO
SUPPORT WHAT WE WOULD CALL THE
ELEMENTS OF THE CASE.
MEXICO'S HUGS, NOT BULLETS
CARTEL POLICY NOT PANNING OUT.
[GUNSHOTS] VIDEO CAPTURING AN
ARMED CONVOY OF MEXICAN CARTEL.
TOM HOMAN SAYS IT'S TIME TO
LABEL THESE VICIOUS CARTELS FOR
WHAT THEY ARE.
THEY ARE TERRORISTS.
A VIDEO FROM CAMPUS REFORM.
FAR LEFT STUDENTS CALLING
CHARLIE KIRK A FASTIST AND
RACIST.
THEY DON'T HAVE EVIDENCE OF
THIS.
>> WHAT IS CHARLIE SAID IN
PARTICULAR THAT YOU DISAGREE
WITH.
>> I HAVEN'T HEARD [BLEEP]
TRISH: CHARLIE KIRK IS HERE.
HE WILL RESPOND TO ALL OF IT.
IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR AGAIN.
YOU GUESSED IT.
AS IF THEY COULDN'T GO LOWER.
IT'S TIME FOR THE LIBERAL MEDIA
TO CRITICIZE THE FIRST LADY'S
CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS.
(chime)
(Shaq)
Magenta?
I hate cartridges!
Not magenta!
Not magenta.
I'm not going back
to the store.
Magenta!
Cartridges are so...
(buzzer)
(VO)
The Epson EcoTank.
No more cartridges.
It comes with an incredible
amount of ink
that can save you
a lot of frustration.
♪♪
The Epson EcoTank.
Just fill and chill!
Available at...
Do you have concerns about mild
memory loss related to aging?
Prevagen is the number one
pharmacist-recommended
memory support brand.
You can find it in the vitamin
aisle in stores everywhere.
Prevagen. Healthier brain.
Better life.
TRISH: CARTER PAGE WAS
DELIBERATELY SPIED UPON TO
DETERMINE WHAT THE THREAT OF
DONALD TRUMP WAS IN 2016.
HE'S KNOT NOW CALLING OUT THE
FBI FOR USING AN ORWELLIAN
OVERREACH.
REFERENCING GEORGE ORWELL WHO
WROTE THE BOOK "1984" WHERE
PEOPLE ARE SUBJECTED TO A BRUTE
CAL DRACONIAN CONTROL.
THINK ABOUT CHINA TODAY.
AND IN THIS CASE, CARTER PANEL
IS INSISTING THE FBI IS ACTING
IN AN ORWELLIAN WAY WITH AN
ORWELLIAN OVERREACH BECAUSE IT
WILL NOT ALLOW HIM TO SEE AN
EARLY REPORT OF THEIST G. REPORT
WHICH APPARENTLY THE I.G. FELT
COMFORTABLE SHOWING TO CNN AND
THE "NEW YORK TIMES."
SO WHY NOT SHOW CARTER PAGE.
HE'S WORRIED THERE IS DAMAGING
INFORMATION ABOUT HIM AND HE
WANTS A HEAD UP ON IT.
THIS SAME GROUP DESCRIBES HIM AS
A QUOTE AGENT OF A FOREIGN POWER
IN THE FISA APPLICATION.
HOW HOW CAN HE TRUST THEM.
IS HE RIGHT?
JOINING ME, REPUBLICAN JAY
SOMEBODY CHAFFETZ.
I WANT TO KNOW WHAT YOU THINK
ABOUT CARTER.
DOES HE HAVE A POINT THERE?
HAVE THEY GOTTEN ORWELLIAN WITH
THIS OVERREACH?
DO THEY OWE HIM THE COURTESY
SAYING THIS WAYS WE SAID ABOUT
YOU?
>> THE INSPECTOR GENERAL, IT'S
COMMON PRACTICE, WILL SHOW
SNIPPETS OF AN INVESTIGATIVE
REPORT TO COOPERATE YOUIVE
WITNESSES.
SO I DON'T KNOW TO WHAT DEGREE
THEY ARE ALLOWING THIS OUT.
I DO NOT BELIEVE THE I.G.
ALLOWED THE "NEW YORK TIMES" OR
"THE WASHINGTON POST" OR ANY
OTHER MEDIA OUTFIT TO GET THIS
OUT THERE.
I THINK THAT HAS BEEN SPIN.
PART OF IT IS SPIN.
DEEP IN SOME OF THOSE ARTICLES
THEY SAID WE HAVEN'T READ THE
FULL REPORT.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN IT, IT'S NOT
COMPLETE.
THEY HAVE DISCLAIMERS TO IT.
BUT THE DICE POINT IF YOU ARE
CARTER PAGE IS, THEY GOT THESE
APPLICATIONS, THEY DID I FILE
THEM FOR A LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
BUT CARTER PAGE NEVER GOT
CHARGED WITH ANYTHING.
AND REALLY, YOU KNOW, IT DRIVES
THE QUESTION, WHAT WAS THE
PREDICATE TO SPY AND CONTINUE
SPYING ON DONALD TRUMP'S
CAMPAIGN.
CARTER PANEL WAS NOT AN INTEGRAL
PART OF THE CAMPAIGN, BUT IT WAS
THE WAY TO GET INTO THE TENT AND
START TO LOOK AROUND.
TRISH: I DON'T CARE, YOU CAN
DESPISE DONALD TRUMP.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IF THEY CAN DO IT TO HIM, THEY
CAN DO IT TO ANYONE.
THEY CAN DO IT TO YOUR
CANDIDATE, TOO, NEXT TIME.
THERE IS SOMETHING AT STAKE HERE
AS A COUNTRY IN TERMS OF WHAT WE
STAND FOR.
>> THAT'S WHY IT'S DISGUSTING
AND DISAPPOINTING THAT THE
DEMOCRATS ARE NOT OVERLY
CONCERNED ABOUT THIS AT ALL.
YOU WOULD THINK THE ABUSE OF
POLICE POWERS TO SPY ON A
POLITICAL CAMPAIGN WOULD BE
SOMETHING THAT WOULD GET SOME
ATTENTION FROM SOME THE
DEMOCRATS.
I.G. HOROWITZ, THE INSPECTOR
GENERAL PUT OUT FOUR REPORT
NAMING THE DIRECTOR OF THE FBI,
THE DEPUTY DIRECTOR OF THE FBI,
ALL OF THESE PEOPLE RUING FOR
PROSECUTION OR DISCIPLINE, AND
THE DEMOCRATS ARE YAWNING LIKE
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
BUT IT COULD EASILY HAPPEN TO
THEM IF THEY DON'T CLEAN UP THE
UPPER ECHELON AT THE FBI.
TRISH: THERE ARE MORE LEAKS
COMING OUT TONIGHT.
ATTORNEY GENERAL BILL BARR IS
DISPUTING INSPECTOR GENERAL
MICHAEL HOROWITZ'S REPORT THAT
REVEALS THE FBI WAS SOMEHOW
JUSTIFIED IN OPENING A PROBE
INTO PRESIDENT TRUMP'S 2016
CAMPAIGN.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT'S THE CASE.
BUT APPARENTLY THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL BARR IS READY TO DISPUTE
THAT.
THAT HE DOESN'T AGREE WITH IT.
UNCONFIRMED REPORTS COMING FROM
"THE WASHINGTON POST."
YOUR THOUGHTS ON THAT.
>> THE INSPECTOR GENERAL WILL
WRITE A REPORT.
BUT WHERE THE RUBBER MEETS THE
ROAD IS WITH DURHAM.
WHETHER A RECOMMENDATION HAPPENS
OR DOESN'T HAPPEN FOR
MR. HOROWITZ IS UP TO THE
PROSECUTOR.
SO ULTIMATELY ATTORNEY GENERAL
BARR GETS TO DO WHAT HE WANT AND
IT WILL BE DURHAM THAT CAN BRING
CHARGES.
TRISH: THE LEFT WILL ACCUSE
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR OF BEING
POLITICAL AND DOING WHATEVER THE
PRESIDENT WANTS.
WHAT'S YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH HOW
ATTORNEYS GENERAL USUALLY
OPERATE.
>> GIVEN THE HISTORY OF ATTORNEY
GENERAL BARR, HE HAS IMPECCABLE
CREDENTIALS.
HE'S NOT IN THIS TO STEPPING
STONE TO ANY OTHER JOB OR SOME
COOL NEW BUSINESS CARD.
I THINK HE'S SERIOUSLY
INTERESTED IN SEEING JUSTICE
APPLIED EQUALLY.
I HAVE THE UTMOST CONFIDENCE IN
THE INSPECTOR GENERAL AND ALSO
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
AND WHETHER OR NOT TO BRING
CHARGES IS ULTIMATELY HIS
DECISION.
TRISH: LISA PAGE IS SPEAKING
OUT.
SHE SAYS BASICALLY THE WHOLE
THING IS LIKE BEING PUNCHED IN
THE GUT.
SHE SAYS MY HEART DROPPED TO MY
STOMACH WHEN I HEARD THAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS TWEETING ABOUT ME
AGAIN.
IS SHE PLAYING VICTIM CARD?
THIS IS THE WOMAN WHO SEEMED TO
HAVE AN AGENDA AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT.
>> LOOK, YOU HAVE THE HEAD OF
COUNTER-INTELLIGENCE, WHICH IS A
PRETTY SIGNIFICANT JOB IN THIS
COUNTRYW IN PETER STRZOK AND
HAVING A LOVE AWARE WITH THE
SENIOR OFFICIAL IN THE FBI.
THEY PUT OUT MORE THAN 10,000
TEXTS.
PEOPLE CAN READ IT FOR
THEMSELVES.
BUT TO PLAY THE VICTIM CARD AND
BLAME DONALD TRUMP RECEIVE BE
DAYS BEFORE THE REPORT COMES
OUT.
THAT'S PRECIOUS, ISN'T IT.
TRISH: QUICKLY BEFORE I LET YOU
GO.
I KNOW YOU HAD YOUR OWN PROBLEMS
WITH THE DEEP 8.
WHAT DO YOU THINK TRANSPIRED IN
2016?
I THINK THE HIGHEST ECHELON OF
OUR INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
THOUGHT HILLARY CLINTON WAS
GOING TO WIN, THEY WANTED HER TO
WIN.
THEY DID NOT WANT DONALD TRUMP.
BUT THANK GOODNESS DONALD TRUMP
WON BECAUSE HE'S CLEANING OUT
THIS DEEP STATE AND HE NEED TO
DO MORE IF WE'LL REGAIN
CONFIDENCE IN THE INTELLIGENCE
AGENCY AND THE UPPER ECHELONS OF
THE FBI.
TRISH: IT'S THAT TIME OF YEAR
AGAIN FOR THE MEDIA TO CRITICIZE
OUR FIRST LADY'S BEAUTIFUL
CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS.
>> IT GOES MORE TO THE TERRITORY
OF THESE PEOPLE SHOULDN'T BE
ALLOWED TO LIVE.
TRISH: COMING UP, CHARLIE KIRK
IS HERE TO RESPOND TO THAT
STUDENT.
THE HUGS NOT BULLETS POLICY IS
NOT HAVING THE EFFECT MEXICO
WOULD LIKE.
[GUNFIRE]
TRISH: FORMER TRUMP ACTING
I.C.E. DIRECTOR TOM HOMAN SAYS
IT'S TIME WE LABEL THE MEXICAN
CARTELS AS THE TERRORISTS THEY
ARE.
>> I'M NOT CALLING ON YOU, SIR.
THIS IS MY TIME.
>> HAVE YOU EVER HELD A DECEASED
CHILD IN YOUR ARM.
>> YES, I HELD A 5-YEAR-OLD
DECEASED  BOY IN MY ARMS.
And, when you open a new
Fidelity brokerage account,
your cash is automatically
invested at a great rate --
that's 21 times more
than Schwab's.
Plus, Fidelity's leading
price improvement on trades
saved investors hundreds of
millions of dollars last year.
That's why Fidelity continues
to lead the industry in value
while our competition
continues to talk.
♪ Talk ♪
Fidelity.
♪♪
Experience the power of
sanctuary
at the Lincoln Wish List Sales
Event.
Sign and drive off in a new
Lincoln with zero down,
zero due at signing,
and a complimentary first
month's payment.
When I lost my sight,
My biggest fear was
losing my independence.
Mmm... Good.
So I've spent my life
developing technology
to help the visually impaired.
We are so good.
We built a guide that
uses IBM Watson...
to help the blind.
It is already working
in cities like Tokyo.
My dream is to help millions
more people like me.
Be brilliant.
Be the diamond
you are.
Find dazzling deals
on diamonds and more
at the Zales Cyber Monday Sale.
Get 30-50% off everything,
plus extended
Black Friday specials,
including this
stunning 7-carat
diamond bracelet.
Exclusively at Zales,
the Diamond Store.
including this
stunning 7-carat
diamond bracelet.
Most people think of Verizon
as a reliable
phone company.
(woman)
But to businesses,
we're a reliable partner.
We keep companies ready
for what's next.
(man)
We weave security
into their business.
Virtualize their operations.
(woman)
And build AI
customer experiences.
We also keep them ready
for the next big opportunity.
Like 5G.
Almost all the Fortune 500
partner with us.
(woman)
When it comes to
digital transformation...
Verizon keeps business ready.
♪♪
1 in 5 people you meet wear
dentures.
Yeah. That many!
But right now, is not the time
to talk about it.
So when you're ready, search
'my denture care'.
Poligrip and Polident. Fixed.
Fresh. And just between us.
Cologuard: colon cancer
screening for people 50
and older at average risk.
I've heard a lot of excuses
to avoid screening for
colon cancer.
I'm not worried.
It doesn't run in my family.
I can do it next year.
No rush.
Cologuard is the noninvasive
option
that finds 92% of colon cancers.
You just get the kit in the
mail, go to the bathroom,
collect your sample, then ship
it to the lab.
There's no excuse for waiting.
Get screened.
Ask your doctor if Cologuard is
right for you.
Covered by Medicare and most
major insurers.
I'm your 70lb St. Bernard puppy,
and my lack of impulse control,
is about to become your problem.
Ahh no, come on.
I saw you eating poop earlier.
Hey!
My focus is on the road,
and that's saving me cash with
Drivewise.
Who's the dummy now?
Whoof!
So get Allstate where good
drivers save 40%
for avoiding mayhem, like me.
Sorry!
He's a baby!
TRISH: A SOURCE TELLING FOX U.S.
ATTORNEY GENERAL WILLIAM BARR IS
HEADING TO MEXICO THIS WEEK TO
TALK ABOUT THE MEXICAN CARTEL
TERROR ORGANIZATIONS.
ONCE IT'S BEEN DECLARED AND
KNOWN A COUNTRY IS HARBORING
TERROR ORGANIZATIONS.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PENALTIES
MEXICO WILL HAVE TO EXPERIENCE.
I WANT YOU TO SEE THIS VIDEO.
THERE WAS A SHOOTOUT THIS
WEEKEND.
LOOK AT ALL THOSE BULLET HOLES
IN THAT BUILDING.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
IT'S HORRIFIC.
IT TRULY IS A BLOODY MASSACRE
WHAT HAPPENED.
22 PEOPLE DIED.
FOUR POLICE OFFICERS.
22 PEOPLE DEAD.
ALL KILLED IN THIS MASSIVE SHOOT
OUTRIGHT THERE AT OUR BORDER.
IT COMES ON THE HEELS OF
AMERICAN WOMEN AND CHILDREN
SLAUGHTERED RECENTLY AT THE
BORDER.
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH.
THESE PEOPLE ARE OUR NEIGHBORS.
IF WE CANNOT MANAGE -- IF THEY
CANNOT MANAGE THEIR OWN
NEIGHBORHOOD, IF THEY DON'T WANT
TO MANAGE THEIR OWN
NEIGHBORHOOD, THEN YOU KNOW
WHAT?
WE HAVE GOT TO FIND A WAY TO
INSEASONNIVIZE THEM TO --
INCENTIVIZE THEM TO DO IT
THEMSELVES FINANCIALLY.
YOU DON'T WANT TO CALL THEM
TERROR ORGANIZATIONS?
THAT'S WHAT THEY ARE.
THEY ARE DESTROYING YOUR
COUNTRY, MEXICO AND WE DON'T
WANT THEM DESTROYING OURS.
JOINING ME, FORMER I.C.E.
DIRECTOR, TOM HOMAN.
WALK US THROUGH WHY YOU THINK
THEY REALLY ARE THESE CARTELS
TERROR ORGANIZATIONS.
WE SAW THE VIDEO FROM THE
WEEKEND.
WE SAW THE VIDEO OF THE FOUR
WOMEN AND CHILDREN KILLED AT THE
BORDERED.
BUT AGAIN, IN YOUR VIEW, GIVEN
ALL OF YOUR WORK HISTORY, HOW DO
THEY OPERATE LIKE TERRORIST
ORGANIZATIONS?
>> A COUPLE THINGS.
FIRST OF ALL, I THINK THE
PRESIDENT IS RIGHT LABELING THEM
TERRORIST GROUPS.
THEY ARE A CLEAR AND PRESENT
DANGER TO THIS COUNTRY.
JUST UNDER 3,000 PEOPLE WERE
KILLED LAST YEAR FROM
TERRORISTS.
BUT 60,000 AMERICANS WERE MURDER
BY THE DRUGS THE CARTELS ARE
SMAUGLEING ACROSS THE BORDER.
IT'S A THREAT TO HUMAN LIFE.
THE CARTELS DON'T RESPECT
BORDERS.
A VIOLENT MEXICO MEANS A VIOLENT
UNITED STATES.
WHAT WE NEED TO DO IS HELP
MEXICO WITH OUR EXPERTISE IN
FINANCIAL INVESTIGATIONS,ING
FRINGE FORENSICS, CHASE MONEY.
IF YOU TAKE THEIR MONEY, YOU
TAKE THEIR POWER.
THEN THEY CAN'T BUY OFF THE
MILITARY AND LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
THEY CAN'T PAY THEIR SOLDIERS.
MEXICO CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT US.
TRISH: I SEE THAT AS BEING
CRITICAL.
YOU MENTIONED THE MONEY.
YOU GO AFTER THEIR MONEY, YOU
ARE GOING AFTER THE HEART OF THE
ORGANIZATION.
WE CAN GO AFTER THEIR MONEY AND
FIGURE OUT HOW THEY ARE
TRANSFERRING THEIR MONEY.
YOU START SQUEEZING THAT, YOU
TART SQUEEZING THEM.
WHAT'S INTEREST BEING THIS, IT
REMINDS ME OF WHAT THE PRESIDENT
DID WHEN HE THREATENED TARIFFS
ON MEXICO IF THEY DIDN'T START
DOING MORE TO POLICE THE BORDER.
IF THEY WEREN'T WILLING TO KEEP
ASYLUM SEEKERS ON THEIR SIDE OF
THE BORDER.
THAT KIND OF INCENTIVE SORT OF
REVERSE INCENTIVE REALLY WORKED.
I WONDER IN THIS CASE IF MEXICO
IS HARBORING TERRORISTS WHAT
OTHER FINANCIAL PENALTIES CAN WE
LOOK AT TO MAKE MEMBERS COLMES
LIFE DIFFICULT TO INCENTIVIZE
THEM TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
>> I WOULD THINK THE PRESIDENT
OF MEXICO WILL COME TO HIS
SENSES.
THOUSANDS OF MEXICAN CITIZENS
HAVE BEEN ASSASSINATED BY THESE
CARTELS.
I SALUTE THE MEN AND WOMEN OF
LAW ENFORCEMENT WHO DIED
FIGHTING THESE CARTELS.
BUT A LOT OF LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
THE MILITARY ARE CORRUPT.
SO THE PRESIDENT HAS A HUGE
TASK.
BUT WE NEED TO REMEMBER THAT A
SAFER MEXICO IS A SAFE UNITED
STATES.
MY CONCERN IS THE MORE VIOLENCE
WE SEE IN MEXICO, IT'S GOING TO
AFFECT OUR IMMIGRATION POLICY.
SOME COURT JUDGE IN THE 9th
CIRCUIT SAYING MEXICO IS NO
LONGER A SAFE THIRD COUNTRY.
YOU CAN'T RETURN CENTRAL
AMERICANS BACK TO MEXICO.
IF THAT HAPPENS YOU WILL SEE THE
IMMIGRATION SURGE HAPPEN ALL
OVER AGAIN BECAUSE THEY CAN
ENTER THE UNITED STATES AND NOT
BE PLACED BACK IN MEXICO.
TRISH: TOM, ALWAYS GOOD TO SEE
YOU.
THANK YOU.
COMING UP.
FAR LEFT STUDENTS PROTESTING
CHARLIE KIRK, CALLING HIM A
FASTIST.
>> WHAT IS FASCISM.
>> RIGHT NOW I THINK ANY TRUMP
SUPPORTER IS OFFICIALLY A
FASTIST BECAUSE HE IS A TRAITOR
AT THIS POINT.
TRISH: CHARLIE KIRK WILL RESPOND
TO THAT AND TELL THAT STUDENT
WHAT A FASCIST IS.
TRISH: THE LONDON TERRORIST WAS
GIVEN A LIGHTER SENTENCE.
YOU WROTE ISRAEL HYPNOTIZED THE
WORLD.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW MY COMMENTS
WOULD BE OFFENSIVE TO
JEWISH-AMERICANS.
>> CAIR WAS FOUND AFTER 9/11
BECAUSE THEY RECOGNIZED SOME
PEOPLE DID SOMETHING.
Congress really democratized
Wall Street...
I wanted to have a firm that
wanted to get everybody in.
Because people couldn't access
Wall Street.
We wanted to be agents of
change.
For the better.
♪♪
(VO)
The moth without hope,
struggles in the spider's web.
With every attempt
to free itself,
it only becomes
more entangled.
Unaware that an exhilarating
escape is just within reach.
Defy the laws of human nature.
At the
Season of Audi Sales Event.
Ugh, another
electronic signature.
You have to print, walk,
sign, scan,
recycle, walk,
email yourself...
Really?
more walking, try again,
waiting, recycle,
walk, email yourself,
then get back to your day.
Or not.
This isn't working.
Introducing Samsung
Paperless Workflow Solutions.
With the Galaxy Tab S6,
you can sign digital
documents on-screen,
with a finger or your S Pen.
Samsung Business Solutions.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with.
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
I can't believe it.
That Sophie opened up a
wormhole through time?
(Speaking Japanese) Where am I?
(Woman Speaking French)
Are you crazy/nuts?
Cyclist: Pip! Pip!
(Woman Speaking French)
I'm here, look at me. It's
completely your fault.
(Man Speaking French)
OK? It's me. It's my fault?
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
(Pterodactyl screech)
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
TRISH: A HORRIFIC ATTACK ON THE
LONDON BRIDGE OVER THE WEEKEND.
AN ISLAMIC EXTREMIST WHO HATES
THE WEST AND HATES FREEDOM, AND
HATES EQUALITY.
THESE ATTACKS MUST STOP FOR
GOOD.
WE CAN STOP THEM SO LONG AS WE
ARE WILLING AND RECOGNIZE THE
REALITY THAT SOME PEOPLE WANT TO
KILL US BECAUSE WE LIVE IN A
FREE SOCIETY.
AS WE LEARN MORE DETAILS ABOUT
THIS BARBARIC ANIMAL WHO PRIDED
HEM SELF ON HIS ISLAMIC YOU
FAITH, IT'S CLEAR HE NEVER
SHOULD HAVE BEEN SET FREE FROM
JAIL.
THE LIBERAL ELITE GOT THEIR WAY.
HE WAS SET FREE EARLY.
AND HE ATTACKED AGAIN.
AND THE SAME THING COULD HAPPEN
HERE.
WE HAVE POLITICIANS PUSHING FOR
LENIENT SENTENCES FOR BRUTAL
TERRORISTS.
ILHAN OMAR CALLED FOR A SHORTER
SENTENCE OF A MAN CONVICTED OF
JOINING ISIS IN HER STATE.
BUT REMEMBER HERE IS HOW SHE
TALKS ABOUT TERROR.
>> CAIR WAS FOUNDED AFTER 9/11
BECAUSE THEY RECOGNIZED THAT
SOME PEOPLE DID SOMETHING.
AND THAT ALL OF US WERE STARTING
TO LOSE ACCESS TO OUR CIVIL
LIBERTIES.
TRISH: I GUESS WE SHOULDN'T BE
SURPRISED THAT SHE WANTS A
SHORTER SENTENCE FOR AN I.C.E.
TERRORIST.
JUST LIKE THOSE IN THE U.K. WANT
SHORTER SENTENCES FOR ISIS
TERRORISTS WHO GO OUT AND ATTACK
AGAIN.
JOINING ME, DR. ZUHDI JASSER.
I KNOW YOU SAID IT BEFORE AND I
WILL GET THIS OUT OF THE WAY.
THIS GUY IS NOT REPRESENTATIVE
OF YOUR FAITH.
THEY CORRUPT AND TAKEN ISLAM AND
THE IT INTO SOMETHING THAT IS
VIOLENT AND HORRIFIC.
BUT IN THE MEANTIME, THERE ARE
THOSE WHO WANT TO BURY THEIR
HEAD IN THE SAND AND PRETEND
LIKE THAT'S NOT HAPPENING.
PEOPLE IN THE U.K. WHO WANTED
THIS GUY OUT EARLY, THERE ARE
TWO PEOPLE THAT PAID THE PRICE
FOR THAT.
ILHAN OMAR WHO WANTS PEOPLE SET
FREE EARLY THAT HAVE BEEN
CONVICTED OF JOINING ISIS.
IS SHE BLIND TO REALITY OR IS
THERE SOMETHING WORSE GOING ON?
>> IT HAS TO DO WITH THE LENS IN
WHICH WE VIEW THERE IS.
WE ARE AT WAR.
IF YOU VIEW THIS AS A CRIME
PROBLEM AS MANY ON THE LEFT DO
OR VIEW THIS AS THE WEST PROBLEM
THAT SOMEHOW WE DESERVE THIS
WHICH IS HOW THE ISIS BRIDES
ATTORNEYS AND CAIR PROVIDES.
THEY SAY IT'S BECAUSE OF THE
ENVIRONMENT THEY GROUP IN.
THEY BLAME THE WEST AND BLAME
OTHERS.
ILHAN OMAR WHEN SHE WAS ON THE
STUMP FOR BERNIE SANDERS.
SHE SAID SHE JOINED BERNIE'S
CAMPAIGN BECAUSE HE WAS GOING TO
FIGHT AGAINST WESTERN
IMPERIALISM.
THE U.K. REALIZES THIS GUY WAS
NOT ONLY RELEASED EARLY, BUT HE
WAS TEACHING REHAB.
HE WAS ACTUALLY INVOLVED AT
CAMBRIDGE WITH A PROGRAM.
TWO OF THE PEOPLE HE KILLED WERE
PART OF THE FOLKS WERE LEARNING
FROM THIS FORMER RADICAL AND HE
WASN'T SO FORMER, WAS HE.
THE JIHADISTS ARE RADICALIZED BY
WEAKNESS.
THEY SEE THE OPPORTUNITY AND IT
BREEDS MORE.
THE ONLY WAY TO STOP IT IS TO
HAVE THEM REALIZE THEY WILL BE
MET WITH 30-40-YEAR SENTENCES.
OMAR'S LETTER TO THE JUDGE IN
SAN DIEGO WHERE SHE ASKED FOR A
LIGHTER SENTENCE IS EMBLEMATIC.
TRISH: WE ARE AT FAULT.
>> THAT'S THE LENS.
THE ONLY WAY TO DEFEAT THIS IS
TO ENGAGE ORGANIZATIONS LIKE OUR
MOVEMENT.
THAT WE ARE AGAINST THE
ISLAMISTS AND THEIR WORLD VIEW
AND THERE NEED TO BE A NATO
APPROACH.
IT INCLUDES THE U.K. WHO LETS
PRISONERS IN ITALIAN PRISONS
COME BACK AND COMMIT ACTS LIKE
THE TERROR ATTACK ON CHRISTMAS.
WE NEED A PAN-NATO APPROACH.
TRISH: IT'S AS THOUGH THE WHOLE
WESTERN WORLD IS TRIPPING OVER
ITSELF TO APOLOGIZE.
I GET IT, GERMANY HAS SOME STUFF
IT WILL NEVER BE DONE
APOLOGIZING FOR.
BUT TO SAY OKAY, EVERYBODY COME
HERE AND IT WILL BE THIS AND SEE
A AND YOU LOOK AT THE KNEE EVE F
SWEDEN.
THEY BRING PEOPLE INTO THEIR
COUNTRY THAT THEY CAN'T HANDLE
ECONOMICALLY OR SOCIALLY.
IT'S A MESS.
THESE PEOPLE DON'T REALLY --
THEY ARE NOT GELLING WELL WITH
OTHERS THERE, WITH THE
EUROPEANS, IN SOME CASES WITH
AMERICANS.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT AN EASY THING
TO SAY, AND NOBODY WANTS TO BE
UNKIND.
BUT IT'S ALSO REALITY.
HOW MUCH CAN YOU TAKE ON?
>> THERE IS NO MILITARY SOLUTION
ABROAD.
WHEN THEY ARE HERE WE NEED TO BE
STRIPPING THEM OF THEIR
CITIZENSHIP.
WE NEED TO LOOK AT VETTING
IMMIGRANTS MORE POWERFULLY
AGAINST RADICAL ISLAM AND
IDEOLOGIES INCOMPATIBLE WITH
WESTERN SOCIETY.
WHEN YOU ARE SAT WAR, SOLDIERS
DON'T GET REHABILITATED THAT ARE
TRYING TO DESTROY YOU AND
DESTROY YOUR COUNTRY.
THIS IS A LONG WAR AND WE ARE
IGNORANT TO WHERE ISLAM IS IN
ITS HISTORY.
WHETHER IT BE IRAN, TURKEY,
PAKISTAN, THE ISLAMIC REPUBLIC,
THEY ARE BREEDING THE MILITANTS
AND THE MEDIA IS PLAYING
DEFENSE.
AND WE NEED AN OFFENSE.
YOU DON'T DO AN OFFENSE BY
LETTING THEM OUT OF PRISON SAT
FIVE OR SIX YEARS.
TRISH: REMEMBER LAST YEAR WHEN
THE LIBERAL MEDIA CALLED THE
WHITE HOUSE CRANBERRY TREES
BLOOD TREES?
THIS YEAR THE MEDIA IS BACK.
FAR LEFT PROTESTERS AT CHARLIE
KIRK'S SPEECH.
>> THEY ARE FULL OF HATE AND
RACISM AND WE DON'T WANT THIS AT
OUR CAMPUS.
>> WHAT DID THEY SAY THAT IS
HATEFUL AND RACIST.
TRISH: YOU GOT ME THERE.
To the outside world,
you look good,
but you don't feel good.
With polycythemia vera,
PV, symptoms can change
so slowly over time
you might not notice.
But new or changing symptoms
can mean your PV is changing.
Let's change the way we see PV.
You track and discuss blood
counts with your doctor.
But it's just as vital
to discuss
changing symptoms as well.
Take notice and take action.
Discuss counts and symptoms
with your doctor.
Visit TakeActionPV.com
There's a company that's talked
to even more real people
Discuss counts and symptoms
than me: JD Power.
448,134 to be exact.
They answered 410 questions
in 8 categories
about vehicle quality.
And when they were done,
Chevy earned more J.D. Power
Quality Awards across
Cars, Trucks and SUVs than any
other brand
over the last four years.
So on behalf of Chevrolet,
I want to say
"Thank you, real people."
You're welcome.
We're gonna need a bigger room.
>> WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
>> I DON'T KNOW [BLEEP]
>> DON'T YOU THINK IF YOU ARE
GOING TO ATTACK A GUY LIKE THAT
YOU SHOULD HAVE SOME INSTANCES
OF SOMETHING HE SAID THAT ARE
OFFENSIVE AND RACIST.
WHAT DID THEY DO THAT'S FASTIST
AND RACIST.
>> THEY ARE SUPPORTIVE OF WHITE
SUPREMACIST DONALD TRUMP.
>> THESE PEOPLE SHOULDN'T BE
ALLOWED TO LIVE.
HE'S A TRAITOR AT THIS POINT.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY THAT'S
HATEFUL AND RACIST?
TRISH: UNBELIEVABLE, WOW.
THAT'S HATE DIRECT AT TURNING
POINT CHARLIE KIRK AS HE
ATTEMPTED TO LECTURE AT THE 8
UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA
ALONG WITH LARA TRUMP.
HE'S CALLED A RACIST BECAUSE
ANYONE WHO HAS A DIDN'T VIEW AND
FOREIGN POLICY -- YOU A
DIFFERENT VIEW ON FOREIGN SOME I
AND SUPPORT PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THEY DON'T THINK HE HAS A RIGHT
TO EXIST.
THEY SAY HE'S -- THEY SAY HE'S A
FASCIST.
CHARLIE KIRK AND TOMI LAHREN.
WHAT DO HAVE YOU TO SAY ABOUT
THAT.
PEOPLE CALLING YOU A FASCIST.
>> LITTLE DO THEY KNOW THAT WHEN
WE DO OUR CAMPUS EVENT AT
TURNING POINT U.S.A., ANYONE WHO
DISAGREES ARE ALLOWED TO COME TO
THE FRONT OF THE LINE AND ASK
ANY QUESTION THEY WANT.
BUT INSTEAD OF COMING IN TO HAVE
A CONVERSATION.
THEY WERE SCREAMING OUTSIDE
BECAUSE IT MADE THEM FEEL GOOD,
NOT BECAUSE IT DID GOOD.
THIS IS VIRTUE SIGNALING IN
REAL-TIME.
THE VFORT ADMINISTRATION OR
COLLEGE PROFESSORS WEREN'T OUT
ENCOURAGING THE STUDENT TO HAVE
MEANINGFUL CONVERSATION.
THEY COULDN'T SAY ONE THING I
BELIEVE.
IT'S JUST INYOU EBB DOUGH AND
OPEN-ENDED INSULTS AND THINGS
THAT ARE COMPLETELY FAKE AND
FALSE.
WHEN YOU DON'T TALK TO PEOPLE,
BAD THINGS START TO HAPPEN.
TRISH: THEY DIDN'T DO THEIR
RESEARCH.
THEY HAVE NO IDEA WHO YOU ARE
AND WHAT YOU STOOD FOR.
ALL THEY KNOW IS YOU SUPPORT THE
PRESIDENT SO YOU MUST BE A BAD
PERSON.
I AM ALL FOR BEING ABLE TO
PROTEST.
THAT'S OUR FIRST AMENDMENT.
GREAT, GO FOR IT.
BUT THE IDEA OF SHUTTING DOWN
SPEECH.
THEY ARE TAKING IT A STEP TOO
FAR.
IT'S ONE THING TO SAY WE DON'T
LIKE THEM AND WE DON'T LIKE WHAT
THEY STAND FOR.
IT WOULD BE NICE IF THEY KNEW
WHAT YOU STOOD FOR.
IT'S ANOTHER THING TO SAY THEY
DON'T HAVE A RIGHT TO EXIST
WHICH IS WHATE HEARD FROM ONE
OF THOSE PEOPLE THERE.
TO ME THAT'S EFFECTIVELY TURNING
US INTO A SOCIETY AND COUNTRY
THAT WE ARE NOT, AND I HOPE WE
NEVER WILL BE.
>> IT'S VERY CONCERNING.
IT'S ALMOST LAUGHABLE WHEN YOU
LOOK AT THE VIDEOS.
I THINK ANY REASONABLE PERSON
WOULD LOOK AT THAT AND SAY THIS
IS NOT COMPELLING EVIDENCE
ANYONE IS A RACIST OR FASCIST.
BUT THE BIGGEST PROBLEM WE HAVE
IS YOUNG PEOPLE PROTESTING FREE
SPEECH.
THEY ARE USING THEIR FREE SPEECH
TO PROTEST THE FREE SPEECH OF
OTHERS.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT RACISM,
FARB YOUISM, SOCIALISM, AND
COMMUNISM IS.
BUT THEY WILL CONTINUE TO DO IT
AND WE CAN'T LET THEM SILENCE
US.
IF THEY DO, THEY WIN.
TRISH: THE UNIVERSITY SHOULD BE
THE KIND OF PLACE WHERE YOU
THRIVE IN SPEECH AND LISTEN TO
ALL KIND OF SPEECH.
IT SHOULD BE -- YOU TALK ABOUT
SAFE SPACES ON UNIVERSITY
CAMPUSES.
A REAL SAFE SPACE SHOULD BE FOR
SPEECH WHERE YOU CAN HEAR ALL
THESE THINGS THROWN AROUND.
THEY SHOULD BE HEARD AND PEOPLE
SHOULD BE SABLE TO COMPUTE
DIFFERENT IDEA.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
IT'S SUPPOSE TO BE A MARKETPLACE
OF IDEAS WHERE YOU CAN HAVE
DEBATE AND DIALOGUE AND
DISCOURSE.
THE CAMPUSES HAVE BECOME ISLANDS
OF TOTALITARIANISM.
WHERE STUDENTS BELIEVE JUST
BECAUSE YOU DISAGREE WITH ME,
YOU MUST BE A BAD PERSON.
WE AS CONSERVATIVES BELIEVE THE
LEFT ARE WRONG.
AND YOU PLAY THAT OUT AND YOU
SEE THE KIND OF RAGE THAT THESE
PROTESTERS HAVE.
THEY NEVER MET ME.
THEY DON'T KNOW ME.
THEY DON'T KNOW ONE THING I EVER
SAID.
THINK DON'T KNOW THAT OUR
ORGANIZATION IS PROUDY ONE THAT
IS VERY DIVERSE AND HAVE MUCH ON
COLLEGE AND HIGH SCHOOL CAMPUSES
REPRESENTING STUDENTS ALL DIDN'T
BACKGROUND.
INSTEAD IT MAKES THEM FEEL GOOD
BECAUSE SOMEONE TOLD THEM I'M A
BAD PERSON.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS WITH NO
DIALOGUE AND DISCOURSE AND
DEBATE YOU ARE RAISING A
GENERATION OF PROTESTERS AND
ACTIVISTS NOT EDUCATING THE NEXT
GENERATION.
TRISH: I WOULD SAY, TOM TO
HURRICANES, THEY ARE MEAN ABOUT
IT.
I WILL TALK TO PEOPLE ON THE
LEFT THAT COME ON THESE
PROGRAMS, AND THEY SAY ONE THING
I ALWAYS SAY IS I GET TO A
CHANCE TO SPEAK ON FOX AND I'M
TREATED WITH RESPECT.
I AM LUKE OF COURSE, RIGHT?
WE BELIEVE IN DIALOGUE.
WE WANT ALL SIDE HEARD.
RESPECT IS SO IMPORTANT.
THERE IS NO RESPECT ON THE LEFT
FOR THE RIGHT.
AND THAT'S A SLIPPERY SLOPE,
TOMI.
>> OF COURSE IT IS.
THEY PUT THEMSELVES ON THIS
MORAL PEDESTAL WHERE THEY THINK
BECAUSE THEY ARE ON THE LEFT,
BECAUSE THEY CONSIDER THEMSELVES
SOMETHINGISTS, DEMOCRATIC
SOCIALISTS, BERNIE SANDERS
SUPPORTERS, THAT THEY STAND ON A
MORAL HIGH GROUND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO TO A
CHARLIE KIRK EVENT OR TOMI
LAHREN EVENT.
BUT OUR COLLEGE STUDENT HAVE TO
SIT THREW LIBERAL INDOCTRINATION
FOR THE CLASSES THEY ARE PAYING
FOR.
WE HAVE TO LISTEN TO ALL THE
THINGS WE DON'T WANT TO LISTEN
TO.
BUT THEY CAN'T STAND TO HAVE
PEOPLE LIKE US ON THEIR
CAMPUSES.
I HOPE THEY UNDERSTAND HOW
RIDICULOUS THEY LOOK AND ACT.
TRISH: KENNEDY JOINS US WITH
WHAT'S COMING UP ON HER SHOW AT
THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
HOW ARE THE BUGS.
KENNEDY: THEY WERE CRUNCHY AND
DELICIOUS.
JIMMY FAILLA AGREED THE BUGS
WERE BETTER ON THEIR OWN.
KAT SAID THE ANTS TASTE LIKE
ANTS.
AND CHARRY GASPARINO WOULDN'T GO
NEAR THEM.
WE'LL GO ON THE HOT MALARKEY
TOUR.
WE'LL GO ON JOE BIDEN'S FAILED
ADVENTURE.
IT'S GOING TO BE A GAFFE GIRAFFE
IN A SAFARI PARK.
TRISH: THANKS, KENNEDY.
THE LIBERAL MADE WHAT PROVING
HOW LOW THEY CAN GO CRITICIZING
THE FIRST LADY'S CHRISTMAS
DECORATIONS.
I'M GIVING IT BACK TO THE FAR
LEFT MEDIA.
THAT'S NEXT.
your cash is automatically
invested at a great rate.
That's why Fidelity
leads the industry in value
while our competition
continues to talk.
♪ Talk, talk ♪
(chime)
while our competition
continues to talk.
(Shaq)
Magenta?
I hate cartridges!
Not magenta!
Not magenta.
I'm not going back
to the store.
Magenta!
Cartridges are so...
(buzzer)
(VO)
The Epson EcoTank.
No more cartridges.
It comes with an incredible
amount of ink
that can save you
a lot of frustration.
♪♪
The Epson EcoTank.
Just fill and chill!
Available at...
My body is truly powerful.
I have the power to lower
my blood sugar and A1C.
Because I can still
make my own insulin.
And Trulicity activates
my body to release it
like it's supposed to.
Trulicity is for people
with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
Trulicity isn't for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity
if you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if you have an
allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects
may include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea or insulin
increases low blood sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting, belly pain,
and decreased appetite,
which lead to dehydration and
may worsen kidney problems.
I have it within me
to lower my A1C.
Ask your doctor about Trulicity.
>> ♪
♪ WOW, THAT'S AMAZING.
STUNNING, BEAUTIFUL DISPLAY OF
CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS AT THE
WHITE HOUSE THAT YOU WOULD NOT
KNOW IF YOU READ MAINSTREAM
MEDIA'S REPORT.
THE DAILY BEAT THREAT
CONTRIBUTES TO WRITE ABOUT THAT
A ASSURANCE.
SPIN.COM SAYS ONCE AGAIN MELANIA
TRUMP WHITE HOUSE CHRISTMAS IS
CREEPY AS HELL AND THEY WRITE
DEAR MELANIA, [BLEEP] UGLY.
YOU GET THE PICTURE.
THE WASHINGTON POST CRITICIZES
HER COAT CALLING IT RIDICULOUS.
I HAD NOT EVEN NOTICE THE COAT,
I THOUGHT SHE LOOKED REALLY
GREAT AND THE DECORATIONS ARE
REALLY AWESOME.
WHAT IS THE EXPRESSION I MOM
USED TO TELL ME, IF YOU DON'T
HAVE SOMETHING NICE TO SAY,
DON'T SAY IT AT ALL.
THE MEDIA COULD BE A LITTLE BIT
MORE CHARITABLE THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
THERE ARE CHRISTMAS DECORATIONS
FOR GOODNESS SAKES.
YOU KNOW WHAT, THEY ARE
ABSOLUTELY BEAUTIFUL.
TOMORROW NIGHT WE HAVE TENNESSEE
CONGRESSMAN MARK GREEN AND WE
WILL CONTINUE TO LOOK INTO THE
IMPEACHMENT ORDEAL, THE SHOW
MOVING ONTO JERRY NADLER AND
DON'T FORGET MATT HOROWITZ
REPORT COMING OUT THE COUNTDOWN
IS ON.
I'M GOING TO BRAVE THE SNOW ON
THE EAST COAST, SLUSH OUTSIDE.
KENNEDY IS NOW.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH TRISH.
BRENT ANDREWS VERY HORRIBLE
AWFUL BUDGET JUST GOT A WHOLE
LOT WORSE.
HIS ACCUSER VIRGINIA ROBERT SAT
DOWN WITH THE BBC AND DROPPED
MORE BOMBS THAN THE B-52S AND
THEIR LOVE SHACK.
THE QUESTION NOW WAS THE QUEEN'S
FAVORITE SON EVER SEE THE INSIDE
OF A COURTROOM.
RA FORMER CLOSE FRIEND OF JEFFRY
EPSTEIN HAS BEEN ON THE HOT SEAT
SAID SINCE HIS OWN INTERVIEW
LAST MONTH.
THEY STRIPPED ANY ROYAL DUTIES
AND KICKED HIM OUT OF THE
PALACE.
THAT IS COLD BLOODED.
IT'LL HAVE TO DO WITH A WOMAN
WHO CLAIMS EPSTEIN FORCED HER TO
HAVE WITH SEX WITH THE PRINTS
WHEN SHE WAS UNDER AGE.
HE TOOK MANY OF HIS SECRETS WITH
HIM BUT THE PRINCE'S CLAIMS ARE
GETTING HARDER AND HARDER TO
DEFEND OR BELIEVE.
THE GUY CLAIMED HE IS INNOCENT
BECAUSE HE CANNOT SWEAT.
A BUNCH OF PICTURES PICTURES OF
HIM SWEATING.
TONIGHT ON THE BBC HIS ACCUSER
SAID ALL OF THAT IS A TOTAL LIE.
>> HE ASKED ME TOO DANCE, HE IS
THE MOST HIDEOUS DANCER OF EVER
SEEN IN MY LIFE.
IT WAS HORRIBLE AND THIS GUY WAS
SWEATING ALL OVER ME LIKE HIS
SWEAT WAS RAINING BASICALLY
EVERYWHERE, I WAS GROSSED OUT
FROM THAT BUT I KNEW I HAD TO
KEEP HIM HAPPY BECAUSE THAT WAS
FOR JEFFREY WOULD EXPECT FROM A.
>> BARF, THAT IS AWFUL.
SHE CLAIMS SHE HAD WITH HIM
THREE TIMES IN TWO OF THOSE SHE
WAS A TEENAGER.
SHE SAID IT IS TIME FOR THE
PRINCE TO CONFESS.
>> HE KNOWS WHAT HAPPENED, I
KNOW WHAT HAPPENED AND THERE IS
ONLY ONE OF US TELLING THE TRUTH
AND I KNOW THAT IS ME.
KENNEDY: SNAP, BUCKINGHAM PALACE
RELEASED A STATEMENT, DENYING
PRINTING AND HER HAD ANY
ENCOUNTER WITH HIS ACCUSER AND
THE DUKE SYMPATHIZES WITH THOSE
AFFECTED AND WANT CLOSURE.
IT IS HIS HOPE IN TIME THEY ARE
WILLING TO HELP ANY AGENCY WITH
THEIR INVESTIGATION AS REQUIRED.
THE DUKE HAS STATED HE DID NOT
SEE ANY BEHAVIOR OF ASSORTMENT
THAT LED TO JEFFREY EPSTEIN
CONVICTION AND FAKE SUICIDE.
HE DEPLOYS ANY EXPLOITATION OF
ANY AND WHO MAY BE OR ENCOURAGE
ANY SUCH BEHAVIOR.
THE REST OF THE FAMILY FURIOUS
AT ANDREW AND RIGHTLY SO.
THEY ARE WORRIED THIS DISCUSSING
CRISIS COULD DESTROY THE
MONARCHY.
BUT WILL HE FACE REAL JUSTICE OR
WILL POWERFUL PEOPLE CONTINUE TO
PROTECT HIM, LET'S MEET MONDAY
NIGHT MANPOWER.
WASHINGTON EXAMINER INTO
CONTRIBUTOR, TYLER GRANT IS BACK
AND ALSO A FOX NEWS CONTRIBUTOR
JONAS.
>> AND WE HAVE SENIOR EDITOR AND
CELEBRATED AUTHOR OF PANIC
ATTACK ROBBIE SAUVE ALL COME
BACK.
ENOUGH OF THE TURKEY LET'S TALK
ABOUT PRINCE ANDREW.
THE QUEEN WAS REPORTEDLY FURIOUS
BECAUSE SHE SAID WHAT TO DO
DAMAGE CONTROL, A LITTLE
INTERVIEW WITH A VERY TOUGH
REPORTER AND PRIMETIME IS AND HE
EVISCERATED HIMSELF, HOW MUCH
WORSE DID HE GET WITH INTERVIEW.
>> IT GETS A LOT WORSE.
HE MADE HIMSELF LOOK TERRIBLE.
SHE IS VERY CREDIBLE AND WE WANT
TO BE CAREFUL BECAUSE AFTER YOU
SAY SHE DON'T AUTOMATICALLY
TRANSLATE, WE WOULD LOCK SOMEONE
UP BASED ON WHAT WE HEARD.
THAT IS THE OVERREACH THAT ME
TOO HAVE BOND.
THERE ARE PICTURES OF HIM WITH
EPSTEIN AND WE KNOW HE HAS A
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM.
I THINK IT'S VERY BAD FOR HIM,
YOU MENTIONED AND WOULD THERE BE
SOME KIND OF CRIMINAL ELEMENT, I
WOULD WANT TO PROCEED WITH THAT
VERY CAREFULLY BUT IT MAKES
SENSE FOR HIM TO STEP BACK FROM
ROYAL DUTIES.
>> I WOULD LOVE ROYAL DUTIES.
THAT IS GOOD EASY MONEY.
BUT WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT THE ONE
THING THAT WE HAVE SEEN,
ACCUSERS WHO COME OUT AND
STORIES ARE CONSISTENT BUT ALSO
GROW A LITTLE BIT MORE COMPLEX
AND SOMEONE LIKE VIRGINIA
ROBERTS WHO IS MUCH MORE STIFFER
US IN HER CLAIMS, ANDREW SAID
WELL I HAVE A MEDICAL CONDITION,
I CANNOT S