>> Martha: THAT'S THE STORY,
THANKS BRIAN.
WE WILL SEE YOU TOMORROW, AND
TUCKER CARLSON IS TAKING OVER
FROM D.C., RIGHT NOW.
♪ ♪
>> Tucker: GOOD EVENING AND
WELCOME TO "TUCKER CARLSON
TONIGHT."
THE UNITED STATES AS EVERY
FOURTH-GRADER LEARNS AS A
MERITOCRACY.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS THAT THE LEADERS ARE
NOT INHERITED THEIR POSITION,
OUR LEADERS ARE SELECTED ON THE
BASIS OF MERIT.
AND THEN UP THEY GO FROM THERE.
ONLY THE SMARTEST KIDS WE ARE
TOLD TO GET INTO YALE.
LIKE INCANDESCENT MINES LIKE
CORY BOOKER AND CHRIS CUOMO.
NERDS THEY CALL THEMSELVES WITH
FALSE MODESTY.
THE ORDINARY AMONG US MEANWHILE
GO TO RUTGERS.
IN THIS COUNTRY THE HARD TRUTH
IS, AND GET USED TO IT, PAL.
IS THE MOST IMPRESSIVE,
NATURALLY RISE TO THE TOP,
THAT'S WHAT THEY TELL US.
DO YOU STILL BELIEVE THAT OR,
ARE WE AND STARTING TO SUSPECT
THAT THE WHOLE MERITOCRACY
SPEECH MIGHT BE AN ELABORATE
JUSTIFICATION FOR KEEPING
MEDIOCRE PEOPLE IN CHARGE?
BEFORE YOU MAKE UP YOUR MIND ON
THE QUESTION, CONSIDER RUSSIA.
IT'S NOT THE NATION OF RUSSIA
THAT HASN'T CHANGED IN A WHILE,
RUSSIA IS STILL A COLD AND VODKA
SOAKED AND ONLY MARGINALLY
RELEVANT PLACE.
AND TO THEM, VERSUS THE MOST
SINGLE MOST IMPORTANT COUNTRY IN
THE WORLD.
AND, THAT HE STOPPED A U.S.
SENATOR IN HIS TRACKS AND ALL
BUT ACCUSED HIM OF SPYING FOR
RUSSIA.
WATCH THIS EXCHANGE.
>> IN DECEMBER 2018 A UKRAINIAN
COURT RULED THAT UKRAINIAN
OFFICIALS HAD VIOLATED UKRAINIAN
LAW BY MEDDLING IN OUR ELECTION.
THAT WAS REPORTED IN
"THE NEW YORK TIMES."
>> ACCORDING TO
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO, U.S. SENATORS WERE
BRIEFED THAT ACTUALLY THIS
ENTIRE EFFORT TO FRAME THE
UKRAINE FOR THE RUSSIAN MEDDLING
OF 2016, OF WHICH YOU JUST MADE
THIS CASE THAT THEY'VE DONE IT.
ACTUALLY, THIS IS AN EFFORT OF
PROPAGANDA AND THIS IS A RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE PROPAGANDA
CAMPAIGN.
AND THAT HELPS PEOPLE LIKE YOU
TO SAY THINGS ABOUT UKRAINE.
ARE YOU AT ALL CONCERNED THAT
YOU ARE DOING RUSSIA
INTELLIGENCE WORK HERE?
THE ONE WHILE G CHUCK, NOW THAT
YOU PUT IT THAT WAY.
THAT'S PRETTY FUNNY.
BUT WHAT'S FUNNIER OR WEIRDER
IS, WE NOW KNOW IT'S NOT REALLY
A STORY.
IT NEVER HAPPENED, THERE WAS NO
COLLUSION.
RUSSIA DIDN'T PACK OUR
DEMOCRACY.
THE WHOLE THING, AND THAT'S
UNEXPECTED DEFEAT IN THE LAST
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
AND THAT'S THE RUSSIA CONSPIRACY
THEORY.
THAT AND THAT CONSPIRACY THEORY
HAS DIED AND WAS KILLED IN FACT
BY ROBERT MUELLER.
AND THAT'S THE STEERING
INFORMATION OF THE PUBLIC AND
INFORMATIONAL.
PEOPLE LIKE THAT COULD BE
CONTRITE AND MAYBE EVEN HUMBLED
AFTER THE MUELLER REPORT CAME
OUT AND PROVED TO YEARS OF
HYPERVENTILATION WRONG.
BUT NO.
THEY ARE MORE OBSESSED WITH
RUSSIA THAN THEY HAVE EVER BEEN.
CHUCK TODD WENT FULL JOE
McCARTHY YESTERDAY.
>> THE FACT THAT RUSSIA WAS SO
AGGRESSIVE DID NOT EXCLUDE THE
FACT THAT PRESIDENT POROSCHENKO
ACTIVELY WORKED FOR
SECRETARY CLINTON.
NOW IF I'M WRONG -- MY GOODNESS.
SENATOR KENNEDY, YOU NOW HAVE
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UKRAINE
SAYING HE ACTIVELY WORKED FOR
THE DEMOCRATIC SENATOR.
YOU REAIZE THE ONLY OTHER
PERSON SETTLING THIS ARGUMENT
OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES IS
THIS MAN, VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> Tucker: VLADIMIR PUTIN.
ARE YOU NOW OR HAVE YOU EVER
BEEN UPON A VLADIMIR PUTIN?
YOU WOULD THINK -- THEY WOULD
SAY THINGS LIKE THAT OUT LOUD
BUT OF COURSE THEY NEVER DO.
NOT ONLY ARE THESE PEOPLE UNWISE
AND HYSTERICAL, THEY ARE ALSO
KIND OF DUMB.
AND BECAUSE SHIFTING MENTAL
GEARS IS HARD FOR DUMB PEOPLE,
PEOPLE ARE STILL PRETENDING THAT
RUSSIA COLLUSION IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT STORY THERE IS.
IT'S LIKE ROBERT MUELLER NEVER
DELIVERED HIS REPORT.
>> DONALD TRUMP TAKES -- HE'S
ACTING AS A RUSSIAN ASSET.
HE'S AMPLIFYING TALKING POINTS
PUT TOGETHER BY THE KREMLIN.
>> I CAN'T COME UP WITH A
POSSIBLE EXPLANATION FOR ALL OF
THESE ELECTED OFFICIALS SEEM TO
JUST WANT TO TURN OUR GOVERNMENT
OVER TO VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> THIS TIME THE ENEMY IS RUSSIA
WHICH SEEMS TO HAVE CONSUMED ONE
OF AMERICA'S GREAT POLITICAL
PARTIES.
>> THE CONSTITUTION IS A PIECE
OF PAPER THAT THEY WOULD RATHER
RIP UP OR CUT INTO SEGMENTS
RATHER THAN DEFEND THIS COUNTRY
AT ALL COSTS.
AND, THEY JOINED THE BAD GUYS IN
THE WORLD, AND THE REPUBLICANS
AT-LARGE SEEM TO BE OKAY WITH
IT.
>> THAT WAS LED BY A KREMLIN
ASSET.
THE WORDS OF BEEN EX-COMMUNIST
DICTATOR, RATHER THAN ANY PERSON
IN AMERICA.
WE ARE IN DANGER.
THIS IS REALLY IRRESPONSIBLE.
KEEP IN MIND THAT EVERYTHING WE
JUST PLAY DO AIRED IN THE PAST
TWO WEEKS.
IF YOU EXCLUDED DEBUNKED
CONSPIRACY THEORIES, COULD ANY
OF THESE PEOPLE ACTUALLY TELL
YOU WHY VLADIMIR PUTIN IS SO
BAD?
WHY IS HE SO BAD?
HE'S BAD.
TODD SAYS, SPEAK SLOWLY SO I CAN
UNDERSTAND.
WHAT MAKES VLADIMIR PUTIN WORSE
THAN A WHOLE LONG LIST OF
AMERICAN ALLIES?
LET'S TRY THE KING OF
SAUDI ARABIA FOR EXAMPLE WERE
THE PEOPLE WHO RUN THE EMIRATES.
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE ON THAT
PAYROLL.
WHY IS HE WORSE THAN THEM?
THEY COULDN'T ANSWER THAT.
FOR CHUCK TODD AND THE REST OF
THE DUMMIES, VLADIMIR PUTIN IS
ISN'T A REAL PERSON WITH COUNTRY
AND POLICE COMIC HE'S A LIVING
METAPHOR.
AND LET'S PUT HIS PICTURE ON THE
SCREEN.
CAN WE GET HIS PICTURE ON THE
SCREEN?
PLEASE.
THE IRONY OF COURSE IS THAT
PRUDENT FOR ALL HIS FAULTS DOES
NOT HATE AMERICA IS MUCH AS MANY
OF THESE PEOPLE DO.
THEY REALLY DISLIKE OUR COUNTRY.
AND THEY CALL OTHER PEOPLE
TRADERS?
BECAUSE THEY ARE MOUTHING THE
TALKING POINTS OF PRUDENT.
THESE ARE PEOPLE WHO DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT RUSSIA, WHO DON'T
SPEAK RUSSIAN.
WHO COULDN'T IDENTIFY THREE IN
RUSSIA.
THE REST OF THE WORLD IS NOT
QUITE THAT DUMB, AS DUMB AS THAT
MAY BE, IT'S NOT QUITE THAT
DUMB.
THE FRENCH PRESIDENT, HE HAS
CALLED NATO "BRAIN-DEAD" BECAUSE
NATO EXIST TO PROVIDE COMMON
DEFENSE AND YET IT HAS WITH THE
FALL OF THE SOVIET UNION IN
1991, NUCLEAR ENTITY.
IN THE UNITED STATES, HE HAS
SAID TO HAVE CLOSER
RELATIONSHIPS WITH RUSSIA, NOT
MORE HOSTILE ONES.
SO DOES THAT MAKE HIM A STOOGE
OF PRUDENT?
IS HE A PUPPET OF MOSCOW?
OR COULD HE JUST BE RATIONAL
LEADER, THE KIND THAT WE DON'T
HAVE LOOKING OUT FOR HIS
COUNTRY'S INTEREST.
RUSSIA IS NOT AMERICA'S MAIN --
AND THE UNITED STATES OUGHT TO
BE IN A RELATIONSHIP WITH RUSSIA
ALIGNED AGAINST CHINA.
CHINA IS CURRENTLY MURDERING
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF AMERICANS
EVERY YEAR WITH FENTANYL.
IT'S PUSHING OUR LIFE EXPECTANCY
DOWN.
THAT'S HOW PROFOUND A THREAT
THIS IS.
MANY OF OUR POLITICIANS RUN
INTERFERENCE.
IN CALIFORNIA, POLITICIANS
BOYCOTT, HE DENNAS THAT CHINA IS
A DICTATORSHIP AT ALL.
WATCH THIS.
>> CHINA IS DOING A LOT.
>> THEY ARE NOW MOVING GLANCE
AWAY FROM THE CITY'S, AND THE
COMMUNIST PARTY WANTS TO STAY IN
POWER AND CHINA AND THEY LISTEN
TO THE PUBLIC.
PUBLIC SAYS I CAN'T BRING
BREATHE THE AIR.
HE HAS TO SATISFY HIS
CONSTITUENTS OR HE'S NOT GOING
TO SURVIVE.
>> HE'S NOT A DICTATOR?
>> HE HAS A CONSTITUENCY TO
ANSWER TO.
>> Tucker: SPEAKING OF
STOOGES, THE DICTATOR IS NOT A
DICTATOR.
THAT IS PRIMA FACIE
DISQUALIFYING AND YET NO ONE HAS
EVEN NOTICED.
BLOOMBERG'S COMMENTS HAVE GOTTEN
NOT 1% OF ANYTHING RUSSIA
RELATED.
THOUGH THAT TAPE MAKES YOU
WONDER, MOST OF WASHINGTON IS
ALREADY IN THE TANK FOR CHINA.
THE EMPERORS ARE GONE, AND
CONGRESSMAN, IS IT ODD TO YOU
HAVING SERVE THIS COUNTRY FOR A
WHILE AND LIVED IN IT EVEN
LONGER, AND THEY DON'T AGREE
WITH DOING THE BIDDING OF
RUSSIA.
LIKE WHERE DID THIS COME FROM.
>> NOTHING SURPRISES ME WITH
SOME OF THE MAINSTREAM.
THIS AND MORE SANCTIONS ON
RUSSIA THAN EVER BEFORE AND THIS
WHITE HOUSE WHO GAVE THE UKRAINE
TANK BUSTING JAVELIN MISSILES
WHICH THE PREVIOUS WHITE HOUSE,
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
WOULDN'T DO AND SOMEHOW, THE
PRESIDENT IS SAYING THIS
WHITE HOUSE WILL HELP PRUDENT,
THAT'S THE MOST RIDICULOUS CLAIM
I'VE EVER HEARD.
AND I LOVED YOUR MONOLOGUE, I
THINK YOU NAILED IT EXACTLY
RIGHT.
>> Tucker: I SHOULD SAY FOR
THE RECORD THAT I'M TOTALLY
OPPOSED TO THESE SANCTIONS AND I
DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE AT WAR
WITH RUSSIA.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY TAKE THE SIDE
OF RUSSIA.
>> TELL ME WHY -- IT CAN'T BE
BOTH.
SO LOOK.
YOU HAVE -- THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION, HE SAID
PRESIDENT TRUMP -- I DON'T GET
THEIR LOGIC AT ALL BUT, I DON'T
GET MUCH OF WHAT THEY ARE DOING.
THEY'VE BEEN PUTTING THE NATION
THROUGH OVER THE LAST SEVERAL
MONTHS.
>> Tucker: WOULDN'T YOU
THINK -- THERE WOULD BE AT LEAST
A MOMENT WHERE PEOPLE SAY,
PROBABLY CONCEDE THAT WE WERE
WRONG.
WE COULD CONTINUE TO BOMBARD YOU
WITH ALLEGATIONS ABOUT RUSSIA.
>> YOU ARE NEVER GOING TO GET
THAT ESPECIALLY FROM FOLKS THAT
YOU HIGHLIGHT A NEW MONOLOGUE,
THEY JUST DOUBLE DOWN AND KEEP
PUSHING ON.
AND THAT'S WHAT YOU SEE FROM THE
DEMOCRATIC PARTY.
AND WHAT DID HE DO?
HE MOVED ON TO THE WHOLE UKRAINE
STORY THAT WE'VE NOW BEEN LIVING
THERE FOR THE PAST TWO MONTHS.
THEY NEVER BACKED UP AND
APOLOGIZED, THEY NEVER ADMITTED
THEY WERE WRONG, THEY KEPT
PRESSING FORWARD.
WHEN SHE CALLED THAT IMPOSTER
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
THEY'VE NEVER ACCEPTED THAT
FACT, AND THEY ARE OUT TO GET
THEM.
THEY GO FROM ONE THING TO THE
OTHER AND THEY NEVER APOLOGIZE
WHEN THEY ARE WRONG.
>> Tucker: THINGS ARE GETTING
RADICAL AND CRAZY.
JOHN DAVIS, COFOUNDER OF
"THE FEDERALIST" WHO HAS COVERED
THE RUSSIAN NONSENSE FROM DAY
ONE PRETTY ABLY.
HE JOINS US TONIGHT.
SO, MAYBE THIS IS AN UNKNOWABLE
QUESTION BUT WHAT IS THE
OBSESSION WITH RUSSIA?
WHAT KIND OF MIND FRAME WOULD
YOU NEED IN ORDER TO CONCLUDE
THAT RUSSIA WAS THE GREATEST
THREAT AMERICA FACES.
THAT SEEMS INSANE TO ME GIVEN
THE EVIDENCE.
>> I THINK IT IS A LITTLE BIT
INSANE AND I THINK IT GOES TO
THE FACT THAT AFTER THE 2016
ELECTION WHEN DONALD TRUMP BEAT
HILLARY CLINTON THERE WAS SOME
KIND OF PSYCHOTIC MENTAL BREAK
AMONG THE COLLECTIVE DEMOCRATIC
MIND WHERE THEY COULDN'T ACCEPT
THAT DONALD TRUMP HAD FAIRLY AND
SQUARELY BEATEN HILLARY CLINTON.
THEY CAME UP WITH SOME SORT OF
EXCUSE OR SOME RATIONALE TO
EXPLAIN HOW THE BIG BAD ORANGE
MAN COULD HAVE TAKEN DOWN THE
POLITICAL SAVIOR.
THEY COULDN'T ACCEPT THAT SHE
WAS UNPOPULAR SO THEY HAD TO
COME UP WITH SOME OF THESE
INCREASINGLY BIZARRE POLITICAL
THEORIES TO EXPLAIN THE FAILURE
BETWEEN HER AND TRUMP.
THE MORE DERANGED AND DELUSIONAL
THEY GET, IT'S A REAL PROBLEM.
AT SOME POINT I WISH THEY WOULD
SIT THEM DOWN AND TELL THEM THEY
COULD GET SOME HELP.
>> AMERICA NEEDS HELP I WOULD
SAY ASSEMBLING A COALITION TO
OPPOSE THE SINGLE MOST
AGGRESSIVE AND FASTEST GROWING
COUNTRY IN THE WORLD.
THE GREATEST THREAT TO US WHICH
IS CHINA.
WHY WOULDN'T WE ENLIST THEM?
>> HONESTLY I DON'T THINK A LOT
OF THESE PEOPLE CARE ABOUT
NATIONAL SECURITY.
IT'S ABSURD TO SAY, THEY MIGHT
BE RUN BY A MADMAN, BUT TO SAY
THEY ARE THE NUMBER ONE THREAT
IS ABSURD.
IT'S CLEARLY CHINA AND THEY ARE
TAKING OVER WIDE SWATHS OF THE
SEA OVER THERE.
THEY ARE BELLIGERENT TOWARD OUR
ALLIES AND THEY ARE STEALING OUR
GOODS AND OUR TRADEMARKS AND OUR
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY.
THEN THEY ARE RUSHING IN ILLEGAL
DRUGS AND OPIATES AND, IT'S
ABSURD THAT ANYONE WOULD EVER
LOOK AT RUSSIA OR ANY OTHER
COUNTRY FOR THAT MATTER.
WE ACTUALLY NEED A SINGLE
UNIFIED COHESIVE PLAN TO COUNTER
CHINA BECAUSE THEY ARE THE
THREATS IN THE NEXT ENTRY IN OUR
COUNTRY.
>> Tucker: THANKS FOR THAT
SEAN DAVIS.
RICHARD GOODSTEIN IS A ADVISOR
AND A FREQUENT GUEST TO OUR
SHOW.
JUST THE OTHER DAY, SOME OF OUR
FINANCE PLUTOCRATS WERE OVER IN
CHINA SUCKING UP TO XI JINPING
AND THE ELDERLY FASCIST
LEADERSHIP OF THAT COUNTRY WHICH
IS FLOODING OUR NATION WITH
DEADLY DRUGS.
NOBODY SAID ANYTHING ABOUT IT
WHICH WAS TOTALLY COOL.
>> THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS I
THINK THEY LOOK TO THE
GOVERNMENT TO BE THE ONES
WHETHER IT'S ABOUT FLOODING THE
FUNK COUNTRY WITH VENTS AND ALL
ARE OTHER THINGS AND I THINK
THEY LOOK TO THIS ADMINISTRATION
TO DO IT AND FRANKLY THEY ARE A
LITTLE WANTON IN THAT REGARD.
SO SHOULD THEY BE?
YEAH.
IF YOU ARE A BUSINESS PERSON AND
WANT TO BE A STAND UP, YOU
SHOULD SAY SOMETHING.
>> THIS IS NOT A SMALL ESOTERIC
THING, THIS IS LIKE THE HEAD OF
EVERY FUND IN NEW YORK.
EVERY PRIVATE EQUITY GUY, THEY
ARE ALL OVER THEY ARE DOING
THIS.
IF THEY ALL WENT TO IRAN
TOMORROW OR RUSSIA TOMORROW, DO
YOU THINK SOMEONE WOULD SAY
SOMETHING?
>> OBVIOUSLY EVERY PRIVATE
SECTOR ENTITY HAS A CERTAIN
MORAL THAT THEY WANT TO OBSERVE.
>> RUSSIA AND IRAN, NEITHER ONE
OF THEM HAS MURDERED, I DON'T
KNOW, 50,000 AMERICANS IN THE
LAST YEAR AND A CHINA WITH
FENTANYL.
THERE IS NO CALL FOR SANCTIONING
CHINA, WHY IS THAT I WONDER?
>> WE TALKED ABOUT FOR THE FIRST
15 MINUTES ABOUT HOW RUSSIA IS
KIND OF HARMLESS OR BETTER THAN
THAT.
AGAIN, BOOT AND MURDEROUS
JOURNALISTS AND BIRDERS
OPPONENTS, MURDERS PEOPLE IN THE
U.K. AND ATTACKS OUR DEMOCRACY.
SOMEHOW OR OTHER, IT'S LIKE BOYS
WILL BE BOYS.
ACTUALLY NO.
I DON'T THINK PEOPLE SEE IT THAT
WAY.
>> Tucker: I DON'T WANT TO
LIVE IN PUTIN'S RUSSIA, I DON'T.
I LIVE IN D.C. FOR A REASON,
BECAUSE I LIKE IT HERE.
SAUDI ARABIA HAS A MUCH GREATER
FOREIGN POLICY THAN RUSSIA EVER
HAS AND YET, HALF OF WASHINGTON
IS ON THE SAUDI PAYROLL.
AND NOBODY SAYS ANYTHING ABOUT
IT BECAUSE THEY ARE LYING
HYPOCRITES.
WHY SHOULDN'T SOMEONE SAY
SOMETHING?
>> I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE IN
THE PRIVATE SECTOR SAID
SOMETHING WHEN HE WAS HACKED UP.
THE FACT THAT THIS
ADMINISTRATION DIDN'T IS
SHAMEFUL.
>> Tucker: WHY DON'T WE SPEND
A FULL HOUR ON THE SHOW AND READ
SLOWLY A LIST OF THE NAMES OF
D.C. RESIDENTS, REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS WHO TAKES OUT A MONEY.
IF YOU HAD AT RUSSIA
INFLUENCING, THAT WOULD BE
FULL-BLOWN CRISIS.
>> THE PROBLEM IS, OUR PRESIDENT
SAYS HE TRUSTS PUTIN OVER OUR
INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES AND THAT'S
A PROBLEM.
HE SAYS I DON'T KNOW WHY RUSSIA
WOULD ATTACK OUR DEMOCRACY AND
THEN THEY SAY THINKING WE ARE
ALL SAY, THEY WOULDN'T.
SO WHEN NANCY PELOSI SAYS ALL
ROADS LEAD TO PRUDENT, SHE'S
ONTO SOMETHING.
>> DO YOU THINK RUSSIA IS A
BIGGER THREAT TO THE
UNITED STATES?
>> THE FACT IS, I DON'T THINK
CHINA IS OUT TO UNDERMINE OUR
DEMOCRACY BECAUSE THEY ARE NOT
AS OFFENDED BY OUR DEMOCRACY AS
PUTIN IS.
PUTIN AND CHINA -- SO WHO HACKS
MORE GOVERNMENT AGENCIES?
RUSSIA OR CHINA?
>> EXCEPT FOR THE FACT THAT
MUELLER AND THE COMMITTEE RUN BY
REPUBLICANS, RUSSIA IS THE ONE
TRYING TO UNDERMINE THE
DEMOCRACY.
I'M NOT SAYING CHINA IS
BLAMELESS --
>> Tucker: COULD IT BE BECAUSE
THEY HAVE OVERSEEN THE GREATEST
SELLOUT OF THE AMERICAS?
I WOULD SAY THAT RICHARD BURR IS
PART OF THE PROBLEM AND I WOULD
SAY MORE BROADLY THAT WHAT YOU
SEE IN THE PAST 20 YEARS AS A
SYSTEMATIC BETRAYAL OF AMERICA
BEGINNING WITH CHINA'S ADMISSION
INTO THE WTO WHERE OUR ENTIRE
DUCK INDUSTRIAL SECTOR
COLLAPSED.
A SMALL NUMBER OF PEOPLE GOT
RICH DOING IT AND THEY'VE NEVER
BEEN PUNISHED AND THEY SHOULD
BE.
IF IT INCLUDES REPUBLICAN
SENATORS, GOOD TO.
>> AND I'M SAYING EVERYONE IN
THE REPUBLICANS ESTABLISHMENT IS
POINTING FINGERS.
>> Tucker: BECAUSE THEY ARE
STUPID AND CORRUPT.
JOE BIDEN IS STILL PULLING AT
THE TOP OF THE DEMOCRATIC RACE,
WHY IS THAT?
SOME AMAZING AND BAFFLING
SICKNESS FROM JOE BIDEN WHICH
THANKFULLY ARE HILARIOUS.
DON'T MISS IT, WE WILL BE RIGHT
BACK.
>> Tucker: REMEMBER CORN POP?
ONE OF THE GREATEST STORIES OF
ALL TIME, JOE BIDEN STORY.
HE TOLD THE GROUP ABOUT BOOTING
A SMALL-TIME DELAWARE GANGSTER
FROM A WILMINGTON POOL.
THE WHOLE THING WAS SO WEIRD
THAT NOBODY NOTICED UNTIL JUST
THE OTHER DAY THAT BIDEN WAS
SAYING A LOT OF OTHER WEIRD
STUFF TOO AND EXACTLY THE SAME
TIME.
STUFF ABOUT HERE, FOR EXAMPLE.
>> AND BY THE WAY, YOU KNOW I
SIT ON THE STAND.
I GET HOT, I HAVE HAIRY LEGS.
THAT TURNED BLONDE IN THE SUN.
AND THE KIDS USED TO COME UP AND
REACH IN TO THE POOL AND RUB MY
LEG DOWN SO THEY COULD WASH THE
HAIR COME BACK UP AGAIN.
I LEARNED ABOUT ROACHES AND KIDS
SITTING ON MY LAP, AND I LOVE
KIDS JUMPING ON MY LAP.
>> I DON'T WANT TO FOCUS ON IT
TOO MUCH, AND BIDEN ALSO CLAIMED
HE WAS READY TO TAKE ON
KIM JONG UN THANKS TO THEIR MANY
PAST INTERACTIONS.
>> PUTIN HAS NO ILLUSIONS ABOUT
WHETHER I KNOW HIM OR NOT.
THE SAME WITH THE PRESIDENT OF
CHINA, XI JINPING.
WE SPEND A LOT OF TIME WITH
THESE FOLKS.
THEY KNOW, THEY KNOW.
AND THEY KNOW THAT I KNOW.
>> AND, IT'S NOT ON THIS PLANE
OF REALITY, AND MAYBE BIDEN IS
JUST GETTING OLD.
MAYBE THIS IS A NEW AVANT-GARDE
ART FORM.
NO MALARKEY.
THAT QUESTION AND OTHERS.
>> HE PAID SOME FANCY CONSULTANT
$30 MILLION.
THEY TRIED OUT IN THE EYEWASH
TOUR WHICH PULLED QUITE WELL
WITH AFRICAN-AMERICANS I
BELIEVE.
AND THAT THEY TRIED THE NO FAT
DOODLE TOUR AND THAT ACTUALLY
WORKED WELL WITH SOME FEMINIST.
THE FINAL ONE, I THINK THIS
WOULD HAVE BEEN THE ONE TO GO
TO.
THE NO COCKAMAMIE FIDDLE FINAL,
DAG NAB IT TOUR, WHICH
DOCUMENTED REALLY STRONGLY.
IT'S A CRITICAL CONSTITUENCY FOR
BIDEN IN IOWA.
WE TALK ABOUT THE MODERATE LANE,
THE SOCIALIST LANE, THE EVEN
MORE MODERATE LANE BUT THE HAIRY
LEG LANE HAS BEEN WIDE OPEN
SINCE BETO INSTAGRAM HIMSELF
SHAVING HIS LEGS BACK IN OUR
AUGUST, AND, THAT WAS AN OPENING
WITH THIS SOUP LEGGED CANDIDATE.
>> AND ITS ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
WEIRD ABOUT SITTING A 7-YEAR-OLD
BOY ON YOUR LAP AND INVITING YOU
HIM TO SMOOTH DOWN YOUR LEG HAIR
AND THEN WATCHING IT RISE AGAIN.
I BELIEVE IN FACT THAT
7-YEAR-OLD BOY WAS THE JUNIOR
LIFEGUARD AT THE POOL, YOUNG
KIM JONG UN.
AND THAT'S WHY HE IS TERRIFIED
OF BIDEN.
THIS IS LIKE THE MACRO POLITICAL
QUESTION HIS PRIMARY GOAL OF
GETTING THE NOMINATION FOR
WHATEVER PARTY HE BELONGS TO.
>> I THINK THE BALANCE HELPS
HIM.
IF WE HE WEREN'T CRAZY AND
TALKING GIBBERISH, WE WOULD BE
TALKING ABOUT HOW CORRUPT AND
SQUALID HE AND HIS FAMILY ARE.
AND HUNTER BUY IN AND WANTED TO
CHARGE THEM $40.
>> Tucker: I SHOULD LET MY
VIEWERS KNOW THAT NONE OF THIS
IS SCRIPTED.
I DON'T JUST THROW OUT WHATEVER
COMES OUT TO THE TOP OF MY HEAD
AND THOSE ARE YOUR RESPONSES.
>> IT'S LIKE A BIDEN CAMPAIGN
APPEARANCE.
MARK STEYN, THANK YOU.
>> DESPITE ALL THE TAPE WE JUST
PLAYED YOU, WHICH IS REAL,
JOE BIDEN REMAINS QUITE
COMPETITIVE IN THE DEMOCRATIC
RACE.
OVER THE WEEKEND IN
NORTH CAROLINA, PETE BUTTIGIEG
WHO IS APPARENTLY A MAYOR OF A
SMALL TOWN IN THE MIDWEST NODDED
ALONG WHILE A MEMBER OF THE
AUDIENCE EXPLAINED THAT ACTUALLY
THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS AN
ILLEGAL IMMIGRANT BECAUSE
AMERICA ITSELF IS A
CLAIMING
WHAT WAS TAKEN FROM THEM IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
WATCH MAYOR PETE'S HEAD NOD AS
THIS PERSON SPEAKS.
>> WHENEVER PEOPLE SAY WE CALL
PEOPLE ILLEGAL ALIENS AND ALL
THESE THINGS THAT ARE NOT HUMAN
OR CERTAINLY NOT CHRISTIAN, WHY
CAN'T WE JUST OWN IN AMERICA,
THE PEOPLE THAT ARE TRYING TO
COME FROM MEXICO HERE ARE COMING
BACK TO THE LAND WE STOLE.
WE HAVE TO HAVE SOME HYSTERICAL
COMIC HISTORICAL CLARITY.
>> Tucker: KEEP IN MIND THAT'S
ONE OF OUR CHRISTIAN LEADERS.
THE RADIO SHOW COMIC IN INDIANA,
ARE YOU SURPRISED BY THIS?
MAYOR PETE NODDING ALONG AND WHO
EVER THIS CHARACTER IS GOES ON
ABOUT ILLEGAL?
>> NO ONE WHO ACTUALLY LISTENS
TO PETE BUTTIGIEG IS SURPRISED.
HE IS A RADICAL AND HE IS LOCKED
UP IN POLICY WITH WARREN AND
SANDERS.
AND IT'S ONLY A QUESTION OF HOW
FAST PETE BUTTIGIEG WANTS TO GO.
HE ALSO COMES FROM THIS VERY
RADICAL PLACE.
THEY TRIED TO PING HIM AS A
CENTRIST AND A MODERATE, AND IF
YOU ARE NODDING ALONG WITH THE
IDEA THAT REVEREND BARBARA PUT
OUT THERE, THAT THE REASON AND
THAT IS A RADICAL, RADICAL
POSITION -- >> WHAT IS HE
SAYING, THE CONQUISTADORS AND
THEIR DESCENDANTS HAVE A
PROFOUND CLAIM ON TEXAS.
HE'S FIRST DESPERATE FOR THAT
BOAT, IS DESPERATE FOR THE BLACK
VOTE.
HE KNOWS HE HAS A PROBLEM.
THESE ARE TWO PEOPLE WHO ARE
VERY MUCH WHEN HE WAS MAYOR OF
SOUTH BEND, THERE WAS A PRO-LIFE
CENTER THAT WENT IN AND GOT
ZONING APPROVAL, AND HE VETOED
IT.
SO THIS IS VERY MUCH IN HIS
BELLY WITH TO TRY TO WAX
INTELLECTUAL AND BE LIKE HIM,
YOU BRING UP A VERY GOOD POINT
REVEREND BARBARA, WINDOW ACTUAL
POINT IS MADE AND CERTAINLY
THERE IS NO TRUTH INTO THE CLAIM
THAT HE'S MAKING.
THE ONE THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
GREAT TO SEE YOU TONIGHT.
ARE YOU READY FOR ANOTHER WAR?
JOHN KERRY'S WAR, THAT'S NEXT.
eg
different to veterans.
It means freedom.
It's the reason you chose to
serve our country.
So you'd have a safe place to
come home to,
and eventually, a home to call
your own.
A place to gather your troops
under one roof.
Your roof.
A place to mark time.
And relax with your commanding
officer.
A place to call home.
NewDay USA can help make that
happen
for veterans like you.
The NewDay Zero Down VA Home
Loan
lets you buy a home with no down
payment.
At NewDay, your service is your
down payment.
The NewDay Zero Down VA Home
Loan
is a real chance to own your
own home.
That's freedom.
That's NewDay USA.
>> Tucker: THE LEFT WANTS
POWER AS YOU KNOW, THAT'S A
GIVEN.
THAT'S THE WHOLE REASON FOR
EXISTING, REALLY.
THE PROBLEM IS FINDING A GOOD
EXCUSE FOR SEIZING POWER.
THESE DAYS THEIR FAVORITE
EXCUSES IS CLIMATE CHANGE.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT YOU ARE
WILLING TO PRECISELY DEFINE AND
FOR GOOD REASON.
THEY LAUNCHED AN ANTI-GLOBAL
WARMING COALITION CALLED WORLD
OF ZERO SAYING IT'S JUST AS
IMPORTANT AS BEATING
ADOLF HITLER, AND THE ONLY WAY
TO WIN THE WAR IS TO GET THE
LEFT TOTAL CONTROL OVER THE
ECONOMY, YOUR COUNTRY AND YOUR
LIFE.
OUR VOTERS ACTUALLY READY TO
GIVE UP POWER OVER THEIR OWN
LIFE TO JOHN KERRY AND FRIENDS?
A NEW POLL SUGGESTS MAYBE THEY
ARE NOT.
JUSTIN HASKINS' HEAD OF THE
EDITORIAL INSTITUTE.
GIVE US A SENSE OF THE PUBLIC'S
VIEW OF THIS.
JOHN KERRY AND OTHERS ARE
TOTALLY UNWILLING TO HAVE A
CONVERSATION ROOTED IN SCIENCE.
THEY SAID THEY SPEAK IN AIRY AND
HISTORICAL GENERALITIES.
WHAT DOES THE PUBLIC THINK OF
THAT?
>> WHAT WE FOUND IN OUR RECENT
POLL IS THAT LESS THAN HALF OF
ALL LIKELY VOTERS, ALL OF THE
EFFORTS IN ACADEMIA AND ALL OF
THE EFFORTS BY POLITICAL LOSERS
LIKE JOHN KERRY TO TRY TO
CONVINCE PEOPLE THAT THERE IS AN
X ESSENTIAL CLIMATE CHANGE
CRISIS HEADED OUR WAY 80 YEARS
INTO THE FUTURE OR 12 YEARS INTO
THE FUTURE IF YOU BELIEVE
ALEXANDRIA OCASIO-CORTEZ.
DESPITE HALF OF THAT UP LESS
THAN HALF OF LIKELY VOTERS SAY
THAT THEY BELIEVE THERE IS A
HUMAN CAUSED CLIMATE CHANGE
CRISIS AND IT'S MUCH LESS THAN
HALF OF INDEPENDENTS.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE THAT
DEMOCRATS NEED TO WIN.
I DON'T MEAN TO GIVE THEM
POLITICAL ADVICE BUT IF THEY
HAVE ANY CHANCE AT ALL OF
WINNING IN 2020, AND YET THEY
DON'T SEEM TO GET THAT MEMO.
>> Tucker: THIS IS A WORLD
WERE AGAINST CLIMATE CHANGE.
THE SINGLE LARGEST POLLUTER AND
ALL MATTER OF CO2 BY FAR IS
CHINA.
THIS DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE TO
ME, TRY TO UNRAVEL IT IF YOU
COULD.
>> JOHN KERRY SAID THEY NEED TO
MOBILIZE AN ARMY.
WHILE HERE'S WHAT YOU COULD DO
WITHOUT ARMY.
INVADE CHINA, INVADED INDIA.
BECAUSE THOSE ARE THE PEOPLE WHO
ARE PRODUCING SIGNIFICANTLY MORE
CO2 EMISSIONS THAN WE ARE HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
>> THEY ARE CAUSING A CLIMATE
CRISIS.
OF COURSE NOT.
>> Tucker: SO THEY ARE FOR
DECLARING WAR ON THEMSELVES BUT
NOT FOR THE PEOPLE CAUSING THE
CRISIS.
>> THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO, THEY
KNOW THAT CO2 EMISSIONS ARE
CAUSING NOT AND THEY DON'T
BELIEVE THAT IT IS.
THEY KNOW THAT THERE IS NOTHING
THEY CAN DO IN THE
UNITED STATES, ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING.
NOTHING THAT EUROPE CAN DO.
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
IT'S ALL IN THE HANDS OF CHINA,
INDIA AND COUNTRIES LIKE THAT
AND YET YOU NEVER HEAR
JOHN KERRY SPEAK A WORD ABOUT
THAT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT WITH THE
UNITED STATES HAS TO DO.
THEY WANT US TO COMMIT ECONOMIC
SUICIDE IN ORDER TO HAVE MORE
POLITICAL POWER.
THAT'S WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT.
>> YOU SOUND LIKE BLOOMBERG,
MAKING EXCUSES ABOUT THE FACT
THAT CHINA IS BUILDING A NEW
COAL POWER TO POWER PLANTS.
IT'S HONESTLY CONFUSING.
>> IT IS CONFUSING IF YOU ARE
TRYING TO APPROACH THIS WITH
LOGIC.
THIS ISN'T LOGICAL, IT'S ALL
ABOUT POWER AND CONTROL.
AND RIGHT NOW, CHINA IS NOT A
CONVENIENT ENEMY.
A CONVENIENT ENEMY IS RUSSIA.
IF RUSSIA WAS DOING ALL OF THIS
YOU CAN BET THAT NARRATIVE WOULD
BE COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
>> Tucker: VODKA MAKE AND
DOESN'T A LOT OF CO2.
CITIES ACROSS AMERICA ARE
GETTING DIRTIER AND MORE
DANGEROUS THANKS TO RADICAL
PROCLAIM, CRIMINAL PROSECUTORS.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
IT'S HAPPENING BECAUSE CERTAIN
PEOPLE ARE PAYING FOR IT.
WE WILL TELL YOU WHO THEY ARE
AND WHY, AFTER THE BREAK.
>> Tucker: IN CITIES ACROSS
THE COUNTRY LEFT-WING EXTREMISTS
ARE BECOMING OF ALL THINGS,
PROSECUTORS.
THEY ARE GETTING ELECTED ON AN
AGENDA THAT FAVORS CRIMINALS
OVER DECENT PEOPLE AND
UNDERMINES THE RULE OF LAW.
HOW IS THIS HAPPENING?
IS THERE SUDDENLY A GRASS
NATIONAL GROUNDSWELL OF SUPPORT
FOR CRIME AND LAWLESSNESS?
NO, THERE IS NOT.
MOST AMERICANS BELIEVE IN ORDER
AND THEY ALWAYS HAVE.
WHAT'S HAPPENING IS AN END RUN
AROUND DEMOCRACY.
A SMALL GROUP OF LEFT-WING
MEGA-DONORS IS DROWNING LOCAL
ELECTIONS WITH TIDAL WAVES OF
CASH.
AS IT TURNS OUT, THAT WORKS.
WE'VE ALREADY TOLD YOU IN SOME
DETAIL ABOUT HOW HUNGER
HUNGARIAN BILLIONAIRE
GEORGE SOROS GOT TO GARY KRASNER
ELECTED DISTRICT ATTORNEY IN
PHILADELPHIA.
VIOLENCE IN THAT CITY
IMMEDIATELY AND PREDICTABLY WENT
UP.
PEOPLE DIED AND IN PHILADELPHIA
THEY HAVE.
BY ANY MEASURE THE LARRY KRASNER
EXPERIMENT HAS BEEN ON UGLY
DISASTER.
THEY'D LIKE TO BRING IT TO YOUR
ACCOUNT AND THEY ARE TRYING TO
DO THAT.
CHESA BOUDIN WAS ELECTED D.A. IN
SAN FRANCISCO.
EVEN DIRTIER AND MORE CHAOTIC.
HE PLEDGED TO EFFECTIVELY
LEGALIZE, AND HE DISMISSED THE
PROSECUTION OF CRIMINAL GANG
MEMBERS AS A "ESPECIALLY
RACIST."
ALTHOUGH HE DIDN'T EXPLAIN HOW.
HE PROMISED TO DO AWAY WITH CASH
BAIL ENTIRELY.
EVEN IN AMERICA'S MOST
FLAMBOYANTLY LIBERAL CITY, THIS
WAS TOO MUCH FOR A LOT OF
PEOPLE.
WHEN YOU TEAR DOWN THE JUSTICE
SYSTEM ONLY THE CRIMINALS THRIVE
AND EVERYONE KNOWS THAT.
BEEN IN THE END, HE WAS ELECTED
ANYWAY BY A NARROW MARGIN.
HOW DID HE DO THAT?
WITH A COMMITTED BACKING OF
SILICON VALLEY'S RULING CRASH,
CLASS, HE WON THE SUPPORT OF
CAITLIN KRIEGER.
KRIEGER WHO WAS A LIVING PARODY
OF A SILLY OUT OF TOUCH RICH
LADY GAVE HIM $27,000.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE SHE
WOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT IF SHE
HAD THE POSSIBILITY OF LIVING
WITH THE CONSEQUENCES OF IT BUT
OF COURSE THERE WASN'T ANY
CHANCE OF THAT.
SHE WAS A BILLIONAIRE.
SHE COULD LIVE BEHIND THE GATES
AND PROTECTED BY HER OWN POLICE
FORCE IF SHE WANTED TO.
THE SAME IS TRUE OF ELIZABETH
SIMONS, DAUGHTER OF HEDGE FUND
LEADER JAMES SIMONS.
IF YOU SENSE A TREND HERE THAT'S
BECAUSE THERE IS A TREND HERE.
SCRATCH THE SURFACE AND YOU WILL
FIND THAT THE DESTRUCTION OF
CALIFORNIA HAS BEEN PAID FOR BY
THE VERY RICH.
THE GUILT RACKED HEIRS OF
INHERITED FORTUNES HAVE LONG
BEEN A MAJOR FORCE IN LEFT-WING
POLITICS OF COURSE, AND THE MORE
THEY DESPISE THEMSELVES, THE
MORE LEFT-WING THEY TENDED TO
BE.
WHAT'S NEW IS THE BURGEONING
COASTAL BILLIONAIRE CLASS.
OVER TIME THROUGH HARD WORK AND
INNOVATION, CONSERVATIVELY THEY
HAVE POLITICAL INSTINCTS.
PEOPLE LIKE THAT UNDERSTAND THEY
HAVE HIT THE LOTTERY.
THEY HAVE EARNED IT ALL FAIR AND
SQUARE, BUT DEEP DOWN THEY KNOW
IT'S A CROCK.
SO TO SETTLE THEIR CONCH
CONSCIENCES THEY FOUND RADICAL
CAUSES.
YOU PAY THE PRICE IN THE END.
THIS IS HOW PROPOSITION 47 WAS
PASSED IN CALIFORNIA IN 2014.
SINCE IT BECAME LAW, CRIME HAS
SURGED IN CALIFORNIA.
ON THE BAY AREA RAPID TRANSIT
SYSTEM FOR EXAMPLE, VIOLENT
CRIME HAS MORE THAN DOUBLED.
MURDERS, ASSAULTS AND HAVE
JUMPED BY 114%.
AND THAT'S MORE THAN ANY PLACE
IN SIZE IN THE COUNTRY.
WHY BECAUSE CRIMINALS UNDERSTAND
THE RULES.
THEY KNOW THEY CAN'T BE
PUNISHED.
AUTHORITIES AND SACRAMENT AS
THEY THE MEMBERS OF SHOPLIFTING
RINGS BRING CALCULATORS INTO
STORES TO MAKE SURE THAT THEFTS
COME IN UNDER $950.
THE LAW ALLOWS THEM TO STEAL
WITH IMPUNITY.
HOW DID IT HAPPEN?
YOU KNOW THE ANSWER.
THE MONEY LEFT ABOUT THE
ELECTION.
GEORGE SOROS BROUGHT IN
$2 MILLION.
THE STORAGE TYCOON GAVE ANOTHER
1.2 MILLION.
AS DID VENTURE CAPITALIST NICK
PRITZKER.
SEAN PARKER GAVE A HUNDRED
THOUSAND TO THE EFFORT.
TERRY THUNE, WIFE OF DUSTIN
MOSKOWITZ GAVE 150,000.
THAT ALLOWED HIM TO BECOME A
BILLIONAIRE WHILE STILL IN HIS
20s.
MOSKOWITZ AND HIS WIFE ARE NOW
REPORTEDLY WORTH MORE THAN
$12 BILLION.
NOW IF THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT,
POSSIBLY AN OBSCENE AMOUNT FOR
35-YEAR-OLD WHO SEPARATELY DONE
ANYTHING, MOSKOWITZ AGREES WITH
YOU OR PRETENDS TO AGREE.
".
AND I ARE STORIES OF THIS
CAPITAL, HE TOLD BUSINESS
INSIDER A FEW YEARS AGO.
IT BELONGS TO THE WORLD.
JUST BECAUSE ALL THAT MONEY
BELONGS TO THE WORLD, IT DOESN'T
MEAN THE WORLD GETS TO DECIDE
HOW IT SPENT.
ASK HIM AND HE RULING CLASS THEY
COULD CARE LESS ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENS TO ORDINARY PEOPLE AND
ORDINARY PARTS OF AMERICA.
THANKS TO THE PROJECTS THEY FUND
THE COUNTRY STREETS ARE DANGER,
DIRTIER AND MORE DANGEROUS.
THE MOSKOWITZ'S FEEL LIKE
INCREDIBLY GOOD PEOPLE AND IN
VIRTUALLY ENLIGHTENED PEOPLE AND
THAT'S WHAT MATTERS.
IN FACT THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS.
LISA PAGE PLODDED WITH HER
BOYFRIEND TO STOP A FROM
PRESIDENCY AND NOW SHE'S TALKING
OUT LOUD FOR THE FIRST TIME.
HEAR WHAT SHE SAYS, COMING UP
NEXT.
♪ ♪
>> Tucker: LISA PAGE, FORMER
FBI LAWYER SAID A BUNCH OF TEXT
MESSAGES DURING THE 2006
CAMPAIGN, AND THEN WE NEVER
HEARD FROM HER.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
TRACE GALLAGHER KNOWS THE
ANSWER, HE IS HERE TO TELL US.
>> FORMER FBI ATTORNEY LISA PAGE
SAYS SHE IS DONE BEING QUIET
AFTER THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES CALLED HER NAMES.
HIS ATTACKS ARE "SICKENING."
IT WAS SO HARD NOT TO DEFEND
MYSELF AND LET PEOPLE WHO HATE
ME CONTROL THE NARRATIVE.
I DECIDED TO TAKE MY POWER BACK.
CONSERVATIVE CRITICS WONDER WHY
SHE DECIDED TO CONTROL HER
NARRATIVE BY GIVING YOUR FIRST
INTERVIEW TO MOLLY JOHN FAST OF
"THE DAILY BEAST."
IN ANTI-TRUMP JOURNALIST WHO
OFTEN MOCKS THE PRESIDENT ON
TWITTER AND SAYS
HILLARY CLINTON'S PRESIDENTIAL
LOSS WAS THE WORST NIGHT OF HER
LIFE.
DURING HER INTERVIEW, LISA PAGE
DEFENDS HER TEXT MESSAGES WITHIN
FBI AGENT PETER STRZOK WHO SHE
WAS HAVING AN AFFAIR, IN 2016,
WRITING "TRUMP IS NEVER GOING TO
BECOME PRESIDENT, RIGHT?
RIGHT!"
AND STRZOK RESPONDS "NO, NO, WE
WILL STOP IT."
WANT TO BELIEVE THE PATH YOU
THROUGHOUT, THAT BEING DEPUTY
DIRECTOR ANDREW MCCABE THAT
THERE IS NO WAY HE GETS ELECTED,
BUT I'M AFRAID THAT WE CANNOT
TAKE THE RISK.
IT'S LIKE AN INSURANCE POLICY IN
THE UNLIKELY EVENT THAT YOU DIE
BEFORE YOUR 40.
LISA PAGE SAYS THAT TECHS WERE
TAKEN OUT OF CONTEST THE MIMETIC
CONTEXT, BUT SHE FAILS TO
EXPLAIN THE CONTEXT.
THIS IS BEFORE MICHAEL HORWITZ
IS SAID TO PUT OUT HIS REPORT ON
THE TRUMP-RUSSIA INVESTIGATION
THAT SOME BELIEVE WILL BE.
FINALLY WE SHOULD NOTE THAT WE
DON'T KNOW WHERE LISA PAGE IS
CURRENTLY WORKING, BUT WE ARE
WORKING ON IT, TUCKER.
>> Tucker: TRACE GALLAGHER,
3:00 P.M., INCURRING ALL THIS
WEEK.
GOOD TO SEE.
BACK TOMORROW, APM, SEAN HANNITY
RIGHT NOW.
>> Sean: RA, TUCKER,
THANK YOU.
WELCOME TO "HANNITY," WE START
WITH A TOP NEWS ALERT.
A TONIGHT BOMBSHELL STORY
SURROUNDING THE DEEP STATE AND
THE UPCOMING FISA REPORT,
EXPECTED ONE WEEK FROM TONIGHT.
THIS MIGHT EXPLAIN EVERYTHING
PAIRED REMEMBER, WE WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE GETTING THE FISA
REPORT IN MAY, JUNE, JULY,
AUGUST, ET CETERA, ET CETERA.
AG BARR SAID HE EXPECTED THE
REPORT IN MAY.
IF THE REPORT WE ARE LEARNING
ABOUT TONIGHT IS TRUE, WE MIGHT
NOW HAVE AN EXPLANATION FOR THE
ENTIRE HOLD UP.
LOOK AT THIS.
"THE WASHINGTON POST" IS
REPORTING THAT ATTORNEY GENERAL
BILL BARR HAS EXPRESSED
DISAGREEMENT WITH THE KEY
FINDING IN THE UPCOMING
INSPECTOR GENERAL REPORT
SURROUNDING THE ORIGINS OF THE
RUSSIA PROBE.
FIRST, THAT IS A GOOD THING,
BECAUSE REMEMBER THAT IS WHAT
THE DURUM INVESTIGATION IS ALL
ABOUT.
AT LEAST THE BEGINNINGS OF THAT,
BUT THAT IS ALSO BECOME
OFFICIALLY A CRIMINAL PROBE THAT
HAS EXPANDED INTO ALL THINGS
FISA AND OTHER THINGS, AND
ACCORDANT TO MY SOURCES TONIGHT
WHILE THE IG WILL CONFIRM A TON
OF DAMNING INFORMATION,
DEVASTATING INFORMATION ON THE
DOJ, THE FBI, THE FISA
APPLICATIONS, APPARENTLY THERE
HAS BEEN SOME DISAGREEMENT, A
LITTLE UNWILLINGNESS OF THE
OBAMA APPOINTED INSPECTOR
GENERAL TO TAKE THE KNEADING
STEPS TO SAY ONE AND ONE EQUALS
TWO.
IN OTHER WORDS, TO BLUNTLY SAY
WHAT IT IS.
AND BY THE WAY, BEHIND THE
SCENES I AM TOLD THERE HAS BEEN
A BRUTAL BACK AND FORTH, YOU CAN
ADD SIMPLE MATH, RIGHT?
APPARENTLY THAT LINE HAS BEEN
USED NUMEROUS TIMES.
ATTORNEY GENERAL REPORTEDLY
BELIEVES THAT THERE WAS NOT
SUFFICIENT BASIS.
AND THIS IS WHERE THE DURUM
REPORT COMES INTO OPEN
INVESTIGATION INTO THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN IN 2016.
HORWITZ ALLEGEDLY EXPECTED TO
DELIVER A MUCH DIFFERENT FINDING
ON THAT.
EVEN THOUGH THAT WAS NOT HIS
EARLY MANDATE.
HIS MANDATE WAS TO LOOK INTO
FISA ABUSE.
THIS WOULD EXPLAIN THE DELAY,
AFTER DELAY, AFTER DELAY,NDND
ALSO THE RECENT LEAKING THAT HAS
BEEN GOING ON WHICH HAS BEEN
RAMPANT.
ASSUMING THIS IS TRUE OF THE
OBAMA APPOINTED HORWITZ DOES NOT
CONCLUDE ON THE BASIC ISSUES
THAT WE ALL KNOW TO BE
ESTABLISHED FACT, PREMEDITATED
FRAUD ON THE FISA COURT,
REPEATEDLY.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THE AG IS
SIGNALING THAT THE DURHAM REPORT
IS WHERE ALL OF THE ACTION WILL
BE ON EVERYTHING.
AND WE DO NEED TO REMEMBER A
COUPLE OF IMPORTANT FACTS HERE.
REMEMBER THE INSPECTOR GENERAL
HAS NO POWER TO CONVENE A GRAND
JURY.
HAS NO POWER TO BRING
INDICTMENTS PIT HAS NO POWER TO
BRING IN CHARGES.
DURUM DOES HAVE ALL OF THAT
POWER.
AND REMEMBER THAT THIS IS NOW
OFFICIALLY A CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION THAT HAS EXPANDED
INTO MANY OF THE ISSUES THAT
WILL BEGIN NEXT WEEK'S REPORT.
AND AGAIN, I HEAR IT IS VERY,
JUST READING THE FACTS.
ALSO, ANOTHER IMPORTANT THING TO
REMEMBER, HORWITZ ALREADY
CONCLUDED BOTH McCABE AND
COMEY LIED.
THAT THEY LACKED CANDOR.
BY THE WAY, THAT WAS SOMETHING
THAT WAS A BIG DEAL WHEN IT WAS
A TRUMP ASSOCIATE.
AND BY THE WAY, AND THOSE TWO
CASES, NOTHING HAPPENED.
REMEMBER?
HE MADE REFERRALS, NOTHING
HAPPENED.
THE IG DOES NOT MAKE CRIMINAL
REFERRALS.
HE MAKES REFERRALS TO
INVESTIGATE.
FUNNY, BECAUSE CANDOR GOT
MICHAEL COHEN, PAUL MANAFORT,
MOST RECENTLY ROGER STONE IN
TIMES OF TROUBLE.
THE SYSTEM IS SO CORRUPT,
FRANKLY, REPULSIVE.
WE HAVE A DUAL JUSTICE SYSTEM IN
THIS COUNTRY.
AND DON'T FORGET, THIS IS WHAT
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SIGNALED IN
A RECENT SPEECH.
I WOULD ARGUE THAT NO ATTORNEY
GENERAL OF THE UNITED STATES
WOULD SAY THIS UNLESS YOU KNOW
SOMETHING WE DON'T KNOW.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> IMMEDIATELY AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP WON ELECTION,
OPPONENTS INAUGURATED WHAT THEY
CALLED "THE RESISTANCE."
AND THEY RALLIED AROUND AN
EXPLICIT STRATEGY OF USING EVERY
TOOL, AND MANEUVER TO SABOTAGE
THE FUNCTIONING OF THE EXECUTIVE
BRANCH.
AND HIS ADMINISTRATION.
NOW, RESISTANCE IS THE LANGUAGE
USED TO DESCRIBE INSURGENCY
AGAINST RULE IMPOSED BY AN
OCCUPYING MILITARY POWER.
THIS IS A VERY DANGEROUS AND
INDEED INCENDIARY NOTION TO
IMPORT INTO THE POLITICS OF THE
DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC.
>> Sean: I WOULD BUCKLE UP AS
A COUNTRY, THAT SOUNDS AS
SERIOUS AS IT CAN GET.
MUCH MORE ON THAT STRAIGHT
AHEAD.
LINDSEY GRAHAM, REMEMBER, IT
WEEK FROM THIS WEDNESDAY, HE
WILL HAVE HORWITZ BEFORE HIS
COMMITTEE AND THE SENATE AND
RESPOND EXCLUSIVELY TO THIS
DEVELOPING STORY TONIGHT.
ALSO BUCKLE UP, THE MONTH
OF DECEMBER IS ABOUT TO BE ONE
OF THE MOST PIVOTAL TIMES IN
MODERN AMERICA HISTORY.
LOOK AT THIS, AS WE SPEAK, HOUSE
DEMOCRATS, THEY HAVE BEEN ON
THIS QUEST FOR THREE YEARS
RACING AGAINST THE CLOCK,
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO WRAP UP
THEIR HALF