HAPPEN IF THE DEMOCRATS CHOOSE A
CANDIDATE THAT LACKS THE WIT,
THE GUTS, THE BASIC APPEAL TO BE
A MAJOR PARTY CANDIDATE IN ANY
YEAR.
IF YOU PRESUME TO BE TRUMP'S
STRONGEST CHALLENGER, YOU'D
BETTER WELL DEFEAT HIM.
NO ONE WANTS TO HEAR THAT YOU
LOST IN A NOBLE CAUSE.
HISTORY HAS ALREADY WRITTEN THAT
CAUSE.
IT IS FOR A COUNTRY THAT IS
BETTER THAN DONALD TRUMP TO SHOW
IT.
THAT'S "HARDBALL" FOR NOW.
ALL IN WITH CHRIS HAYES STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> TONIGHT ON "ALL IN" --
LIKELY NEW CHARGES FOR RUDOLPH
GIULIANI'S UKRAINE CREW.
>> I DON'T KNOW THOSE GENTLEMEN.
>> AS THE IMPEACHMENT OF DONALD
J. TRUMP PROCEEDS.
>> HERE'S WHAT I THINK THEY WILL
ADVANCE.
ONE IS BRIBERY.
>> TONIGHT WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
FOUND.
>> THERE IS NOTHING MORE
DANGEROUS THAN AN UNETHICAL
PRESIDENT WHO BELIEVES THEY ARE
ABOVE THE LAW.
>> WHAT THE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
IS PLANNING THIS WEEK.
>> NO ONE IS ABOVE THE LAW.
>> WHAT IT MEANS FOR THE
PRESIDENT AND HIS LAWYER.
>> I CAN'T WAIT TO COME BACK.
>>> THEN, ARE HOUSE DEMOCRATS
ABOUT TO GIVE THE PRESIDENT A
POLITICAL VICTORY ON TRADE?
THE INDICTED HOUSE REPUBLICAN
WHO THREW HIS WIFE UNDER THE BUS
TAKES A PLEA.
>> WHATEVER SHE DID, THAT WILL
BE LOOKED AT, TOO, I'M SURE.
I DIDN'T DO IT.
>> AND HOW TRUMP'S ADULT SON
LEVERAGED HIS DADDY'S POSITION
TO GAIN THE NEW YORK SOMETIMES
SELLER LIST.
>> I DIDN'T DO IT THROUGH MY
DAD'S TAXPAYER FUNDED LIST.
>> GOOD EVENING FROM NEW YORK.
THE IMPEACHMENT OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP DONALD J. TRUMP IS GETTING
CLOSER.
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
HAS BEGUN REVIEWING AT THIS HOUR
A REPORT ON EVERYTHING THEY'VE
LEARNED FROM THEIR
INVESTIGATIONS SO FAR.
REMEMBER, WE'VE SEEN 12
WITNESSES GIVE ABOUT 35 HOURS OF
PUBLIC TESTIMONY.
THERE WAS ALSO OVER 120 HOURS OF
TESTIMONY BEHIND CLOSED DOORS.
AND EVEN BEFORE ALL THOSE
HEARINGS, WE KNEW FROM THE CALL
NOTES THE WHITE HOUSE ITSELF
RELEASED THAT THE PRESIDENT
TRIED TO EXTORT FOREIGN COUNTRY
UKRAINE INTO HELPING HIM WIN
RE-ELECTION.
REMEMBER THE PHRASE, I WOULD
LIKE YOU TO DO US A FAVOR
THOUGH.
WE KNEW THAT FROM THE GET-GO.
AFTER SPENDING A FEW WEEKS
WATCHING AND READING THE
HUNDREDS OF HOURS OF TESTIMONY,
IT FEELS OVERWHELMINGLY CHEER,
ACCORDING TO THE TESTIMONY OF
CAREER CIVIL SERVANTS, THE
PRESIDENT DID DO JUST WHAT IT
LOOKED LIKE DID HE.
HE EXTOWARD UKRAINE.
UNSUCCESSFULLY, IT APPEARS.
THE COMMITTEE IS SET TO APPROVE
THE REPORT TOMORROW EVENING AND
THEN HIT HEAD TO THE HOUSE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE FOR REVIEW.
MEMBERS WILL USE THAT TO DECIDE
WHETHER TO DRAFT ARTICLES OF
IMPEACHMENT.
NOW, WE ARE GOING TO GET THE
FIRST FORMAL HEARING FROM THAT
COMMITTEE, THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE, ON THIS WEDNESDAY.
THEY WILL BE HOLDING A PUBLIC
HEARING EXAMINING THE
CONSTITUTIONAL GROUNDS OF THE
PRESIDENT'S IMPEACHMENT.
WE JUST LEARNED A FEW HOURS AGO
THIS EVENING, THE WITNESSES AT
THE HEARING, THERE WILL BE FOUR
LAW PROFESSORS, THREE CHOSEN BY
DEMOCRATS AND ONE BY REPUBLICANS
ON THE COMMITTEE.
IN ANTICIPATION OF THE
DEMOCRATS' HOUSE REPORT, TONIGHT
HOUSE REPUBLICANS RELEASED THEIR
OWN IMPEACHMENT PRE BUTTAL.
IT SAYS THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP DID
NOTHING EVEN SLIGHTLY IMPROPER.
THE "WASHINGTON POST" CALLING
THE REPORT A SERIES OF RED
HERRING THAT'S RELY ON A SERIES
OF STRAWMEN REBUTTING
ALLEGATIONS THAT ARE NOT REALLY
BEING MADE AGAINST TRUMP.
THIS IS VERY MUCH IN FAVOR OF
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IN
CONGRESS, THEY'VE SPENT WEEKS
AND MONTHS COMPLAINING ABOUT THE
PROCESS.
FOR A WHILE IT WAS HOW DARE YOU
TALK TO THESE WITNESSES BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS.
SO DEMOCRATS STARTED TO HOLD
PUBLIC HEARINGS AND IT BECAME,
THIS IS A RIDICULOUS CIRCUS.
HOW COME THE PRESIDENT CAN'T
SEND A HAIR TO DEFEND HIMSELF?
THEN WHEN THE DEMOCRATS OFFER TO
SEND A LAWYER TO THE JUDICIARY
HEARING, THE WHITE HOUSE REFUSED
TO PARTICIPATE.
NOW, ALL THIS IS HAPPENING WHILE
THERE ARE STILL ALL SORTS OF
OUTSTANDING QUESTIONS OF FACT
AND LAW THAT WHOM OVER THIS
WHOLE THING.
LIKE FOR INSTANCE THE COURT
CASES THAT MAY DECIDE WHETHER
CONGRESS GETS THE PRESIDENT'S
TAX RETURNS OR WHICH WITNESSES
ARE COMPELLED TO APPEAR BEFORE
THEM.
JUST THIS EVENING, A FEDERAL
JUDGE REFUSED TO DELAY, HER
WORD, FROM FORMER WHITE HOUSE
COWBOY DON McGAHN TO COME BLIGH
THE CONGRESSIONAL SUBPOENA.
THERE IS WILL THE CRIMINAL CASE
RELATED TO ALL THIS THAT
CONTINUES TO WINE ITS WAY
THROUGH SOUTHERN DISTRICT OF NEW
YORK.
THAT WOULD BE THE CASE OF
RUDOLPH GIULIANI'S INDICTED
ASSOCIATES.
REMEMBER, THOSE TWO MEN
REPRESENTED THEMSELVES TO
CONGRESS AS PART OF THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN LEGAL TEAM AND
ACCORDING TO THE INDICTMENT
FURNISHED BY SDNY, THEY
ALLEGEDLY WORKED TO SMEAR THE
AMBASSADOR TO UKRAINE FROM HER
POST.
AND ONE OF THEM SAID HE WOULD
LIKE TO PROVIDE DOCUMENTS TO THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
HE WOULD NEED A JUDGE'S APPROVAL
TO DO THAT.
HE WOULD BE IN THE PUBLIC'S
INTEREST AND TENDS TO APPROVE
THAT RELEASE.
ANOTHER THING TO KEEP YOUR EYE
ON.
HE SAID IT IS LIKELY THEY WILL
FILE, THEY DID NOT SAY WHETHER
OR NOT ANYONE ELSE WOULD BE
CHARGED.
JOINING ME, TWO PEOPLE CLOSELY
FOLLOWING ENTIRETY OF THE
IMPEACHMENT PROCESS.
THE NATIONAL SECURITY
CORRESPONDENT FOR POLITICO AND
MSNBC CONTRIBUTOR, AND
ELIZABETH, A FORMER
CONGRESSWOMAN WHO SAT ON THE
COMMITTEE DURING THE IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS OF RICHARD NIXON.
AUTHOR OF THE CASE FOR
IMPEACHING TRUMP.
ELIZABETH, LET ME START WITH
YOU.
THERE ARE TWO STORIES GOING
FORWARD OVER THE LAST MORE ONNER
TWO.
THE STORY OF THE WHISTLEBLOWER
EXPLAIN THAT BECAME THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY THAT WILL
LIKELY BECOME IMPEACHMENT OF THE
PRESIDENT OVER UKRAINE AND THEN
THE INDICTMENT OF THESE TWO MEN
WORKING WITH RUDY GIULIANI AND
THE TWO INTERSECT.
HOW MUCH DO YOU SEE THESE TWO
ROADS CROSSING BASED ON WHAT WE
LEARNED TODAY AT THE STATUS
HEARING IN.
>> EXTENSIVELY GIVEN THAT THESE
TWO MEN WERE INTERACTING BETWEEN
THEM.
AND THE UKRAINIAN OFFICIALS THAT
WERE TRYING TO OUST, FOR
EXAMPLE, THE FORMER AMBASSADOR
TO UKRAINE, MARIE YOVANOVITCH
TRYING TO PUSH THIS THEORY THAT
JOE BIDEN ACTED IMPROPERLY WITH
REGARD TO HIS SON ON THE ENERGY
BOARD.
THESE WERE PEOPLE DIRECTLY AT
THE CENTRAL OF THIS.
THEY'RE ACTING AS INTERMEDIARIES
OR TRANSLATORS OR FIXERS.
NOW ONE OF THEM REALLY WANT TO
TELL CONGRESS WHAT HE KNOWS.
AND THAT COULD BE EXCEEDINGLY
DANGEROUS FOR BOTH RUDOLPH
GIULIANI AND THE PRESIDENT.
THIS IS SOMEONE WHO HAS TOLD THE
PRESS THROUGH HIS HAIR THAT HE
WAS DIRECTLY INVOLVED IN
CONVERSATIONS WITH THE PRESIDENT
ABOUT GOING ON A SO-CALLED
SECRET MISSION IN ORDER TO DIG
UP DIRT ON JOE BIDEN AND UKRAINE
AND OSTENSIBLY OUST THE
UKRAINIAN AMBASSADOR,
YOVANOVITCH.
SO HE MOST LIKELY HAS A TREASURE
TROVE OF DOCUMENTS, EMAILS, THAT
HE IS WILLING TO SHOW CONGRESS
IS THAT BY EXTENSION, THE PUBLIC
BECAUSE HE IS BURNED BY THE FACT
THE PRESIDENT HAS TRIED TO
DISTANCE HIMSELF FROM HIM EVEN
THOUGH THEY ATTENDED NUMEROUS
EVENTS TOGETHER, PRIVATE
MEETINGS, ET CETERA.
>> THERE IS A NEXUS BETWEEN THE
CRIMINAL CASE AND THE
IMPEACHMENT INQUIRY THAT RECALLS
WATERGATE.
MY WIFE WAS REMINDING ME OF
THIS.
SHE WAS RE-READING IT.
THE IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS AND
EVEN OFFERED FAVORABLE TERMS TO
THOSE BEFORE HIM IF THEY DID IN
FACT COOPERATE WITH CONGRESS.
>> WELL, AS I SAID WHAT THE
JUDGE DID, HE SMELLED A RAT FROM
THE BEGINNING IN THE WATERGATE
BURGLARY AND HE IMPOSED, FIRST
OF ALL, EM, SENATE, HOUSE,
SOMETHING SMELLS HERE.
YOU HAVE TO STEP IN AND DO
SOMETHING.
THAT TRIGGERED THE SENATE
WATERGATE HEARINGS.
THE SECOND THING HE DID WAS
IMPOSE REALLY TOUGH EXTENSIONS
ON THE BURGLARS AND ONE OF THEM
BROKE.
THE OUTSIDE FEDERAL JUDGE WHO
SMELLS A RAT, CAN MAKE A BIG
DIFFERENCE, AND THESE DOCUMENTS
COULD HAVE A MAJOR IMPACT.
THERE ARE LOTS OF THEM.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT WE'LL
SEE THIS WEEK AND I'LL STAY WITH
YOU FOR A SECOND.
WE'RE MOVING NOW FROM HOUSE
INTEL TO JUDICIARY.
WHAT IS THE SIGNIFICANCE OF
THAT?
HOW MUCH LEFT IS THERE FOR
JUDICIARY TO DO SINCE THE
FACT-FINDING HAS BEEN DONE BY
THE INTEL COMMITTEE?
>> WELL, FIRST, THEY HAVE TO
HELP THEMSELVES, THE REST
CONGRESS AND THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
UNDERSTAND WHAT THE CONSTITUTION
MEANS BY THE IMPEACHMENT CLAUSE.
THE STANDARDS FOR IMPEACHMENT,
TREASON, BRIBERY, OTHER HIGH
CRIMES IS THAT MISDEMEANORS.
WHAT IS BRIBERY?
TREASON DOESN'T APPLY HERE.
WHAT IS OTHER HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS.
WE HAD TO DO THAT IN THE NIXON
IMPEACHMENT.
WE DID IT BEHIND CLOSED DOORS.
WE DIDN'T HAVE EXPERTS.
WE HAD TO DO OUR OWN HOMEWORK
BUT WE ALSO STUDY THAT HAD AND I
THINK IT IS VERY IMPORTANT TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE IN CONGRESS
TO UNDERSTAND THE MEANING OF THE
TERMS.
THE SECOND THING THAT WILL
HAPPEN IS THEY HAVE TO DECIDE,
WHAT ARE THEY GOING TO DO WITH
THESE FACTS?
HOW DO THEY FIT INTO THE
ARTICLES OF IMPEACHMENT?
IS THERE ENOUGH INFORMATION FOR
AN ARTICLE?
IF THERE IS, IS THERE GOING TO
BE AN ARTICLE ON BRIBERY?
OR ONLY ON ABUSE OF POWER?
THE OTHER THING IS, IS IT GOING
ON PUT ANYTHING ASIDE FROM
UKRAINEGATE?
THESE ARE REALLY THREE CRITICAL
ISSUES BEFORE CONGRESS.
>> ONE THING WE'VE SEEN BY
PREBUTTAL RELEASE, INCREASINGLY,
FACED WOOPS THE CHOICE TO DEFEND
THE MOST EXTREME INSIDIOUS AND
INDEFENSIBLE STATEMENTS OF THE
PRESIDENT, LIKE THE TRULY INSANE
CONSPIRACY THEORY ON THE PHONE
CALL, OR TO SOFTLY CHASTISE THE
PRESIDENT TO SAY HE SHOULD BE
IMPEACHED, YOU SEE THE
REPUBLICANS SAYING THE PRESIDENT
IS RIGHT ABOUT EVERYTHING.
WE LOVE HIM, WE LOVE HIM.
YOU'VE GOT REPORT ABOUT THE FACT
THAT THE SENATE INTEL COMMITTEE
CHAIRED BY REPUBLICAN LOOKED
INTO THIS CLAIM THAT UKRAINE
SOMEHOW WAS MEDDLING IN THE
ELECTION AND FOUND THERE WAS NO
THERE, THERE.
>> YEAH.
SO THE SENATE INTEL COMMITTEE
BEGAN LOOKING INTO THIS IN 2017.
THEY WERE OUTLINING EFFORTS BY
CERTAIN UKRAINIAN BUREAUCRATS
AND OFFICIALS AT THE EMBASSY TO
ALLEGEDLY HELP A DNC CONTRACTOR
LOOK INTO PAUL MANAFORT.
AND THIS DNC CONTRACTOR WAS
CALLED IN TO TESTIFY BEFORE THE
SENATE INTEL COMMITTEE.
SHE REALLY, IT WAS CONSIDERED BY
ALL ACCOUNTS TO BE A MET WASTE
OF TIME.
WHAT THE REPUBLICANS WERE HOOK
FOR WAS EVIDENCE OF A TOP DOWN
CONSPIRACY OF THE KIND RUSSIA
DID WHEN THEY INTERFERED IN 2016
COMPLETE WITH A WIDE RANGING
INTERFERENCE CAMPAIGN THAT MAY
HAVE BEEN COMPARABLE TO RUSSIA'S
ELECTION INTERFERENCE.
BUT THEY FOUND NOTHING OF THE
SORT.
WHAT THEY FOUND WAS SCATTER SHOT
EFFORTS BY A FEW UKRAINIAN
DIPLOMATS HERE AND THIS WHO
OBVIOUSLY DID PREFER HILLARY
CLINTON BECAUSE DONALD TRUMP WAS
SAYING AT THE TIME THAT CRIMEA
WOULD LOOK INTO ALLOWING CRIMA
TO BE RECOGNIZED AS RUSSIAN
TERRITORY AND EVEN LIFT RUSSIAN
SANCTIONS.
SO OBVIOUSLY THE UKRAINIANS HAD
A PREFERENCE FOR HILLARY CLINTON
AT THAT POINT.
THE SENATE COMMITTEE LOOKED INTO
THIS THOROUGHLY, DID NOT FIEND
ANY EVIDENCE THAT THERE WAS A
WIDE RANGING TOP DOWN CONSPIRACY
BY UKRAINE STOFFEL IDEA THAT THE
REPUBLICANS IN THE SENATE ARE
SAYING THAT THE UKRAINIANS
INTERFERED THE SAME WAY THAT
RUSSIA DID IN 2016 IS REALLY
DISINGENUOUS CONSIDERING ALL THE
WORK THE COMMITTEE DID TO DEBUNK
THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU BOTH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> JOINING ME FOR MORE, WHAT WE
EXPECT TO GET GOING FORWARD.
MICHAEL STEELE, AND MICKEY
EDWARDS, FORMER CONGRESSMAN FROM
OKLAHOMA.
MICKEY, SINCE YOU'RE HERE, I'LL
GO TO YOU FIRST.
THERE IS ALWAYS THE QUESTION.
I NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD BE THE
CASE THAT YOU SEE ANY KIND OF
OVERWHELMING BREAK THAT THE
PRESIDENT SHK IMPEACHED.
IT HAS ALWAYS BEEN QUITE
PARTISAN WITH THE EXCEPTION OF
NIXON.
BUT THIS IS A VARIETY OF PATHS
THEY COULD HAVE TAKEN AND IT
SEEMS LIKE THEY ARE CHOOSING IN
BOTH THE REPORT THEY ISSUED
TODAY, THE NOISES BEING MADE
FROM THE SENATE.
THE MAXIMMALIST PATH.
>> IT WAS PERFECT.
YOU SAW WHAT THE SENATOR FROM
WHO LOU IS DOING.
HE IS MAKING UP STUFF.
HE IS PRETENDING WHAT HE IS
GOING TO DO IS BE A GREAT
CHAMPION FOR THIS GUY IN THE
WHITE HOUSE HE FORGOT THAT THE
PRESIDENT JUST WENT DOWN TO HIS
STATE OF LOUISIANA AND URGED
PEOPLE THERE TO VOTE AGAINST
THE --
>> JOHN BELL EDWARDS.
WHO WON.
AND I THINK KENNEDY IS MAKING A
BIG MISTAKE AND I THINK THE
DEMOCRATS HAVE THE REPUBLICANS
IN A BOX BECAUSE THEY'RE IN A
POSITION NOW.
INSTEAD OF JUST SAYING, IT'S NOT
IMPEACHABLE.
NOT REMOVABLE.
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING IS THEY'RE
DENYING THE FACTS THAT EVERYBODY
KNOWS THAT THE COMMITTEES KEEP
COMING OUT WITH.
AND THEY HAVE NO SAY.
>> PART OF WHAT MICKEY IS
REFERRING TO IS JOHN KENNEDY'S
APPEARANCE ON "MEET THE PRESS."
I WANT TO MAY THAT FOR YOU.
IN THE CONTEXT, THE PRESIDENT IS
ATTEMPTING TO EXTORT TWO
INVESTIGATIONS OUT OF PRESIDENT
ZELENSKY.
ONE IS TO DIG UP DIRT ON JOE
BIDEN AND HUNTER BIDEN.
THE OTHER IS THE 9/11 TRUTHERNS
SERVERS.
THE UKRAINE THEY SAID DNC FRAME
RUSSIA FOR HACKING.
SO THIS IS KENNEDY ATTEMPTING TO
SORT OF, I GUESS, BOLSTER IT.
>> RUSSIA WAS VERY AGGRESSIVE
AND THEY'RE MUCH MORE
SOPHISTICATED.
BUT THE FACT THAT RUSSIA WAS SO
AGGRESSIVE DOES NOT AND CHEWED
THE FACT PRESIDENT POROSHENKO
ACTIVELY WORKED FOR --
>> MY GOODNESS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
SENATOR KENNEDY, YOU NOW HAVE
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE SAYING
HE ACTIVELY WORKED FOR THE
DEMOCRATIC NOMINEE FOR
PRESIDENT.
COME ON.
I HAVE TO PUT UP, YOU REALIZE.
THE ONLY OTHER PERSON SELLING
THIS ARGUMENT OUTSIDE THE UNITED
STATES IS THIS MAN.
VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> THIS IS WHERE WE'RE SORT OF
AT, MICHAEL.
>> IT'S EXACTLY WHERE WE ARE.
IT'S AMAZING TO WATCH THE
EVOLUTION SORT OF MOVE OUT OF
THE HOUSE AND NOW INTO THE
SENATE SPACE.
IT'S BEEN MY CONTENTION ALL
ALONG.
AND SENATOR KENNEDY IS A
PRECURSOR OF WHAT WILL COME WHEN
IT ALL GETS TO THE SENATE.
THAT THIS WHOLE EFFORT HAS BEEN
ABOUT TWO THINGS.
GUM IT UP AS MUCH AS POSSIBLE
AND MAKE SURE NOTHING MAKES
SENSE TO ANYONE.
>> IS THAT REALLY TRUE?
WHEN IT COMES TO THE SENATE,
MITCH McCONNELL WILL BE IN THE
BEST POSITION POSSIBLE TO SAY,
YOU KNOW, THERE'S NO THERE,
THERE.
I DON'T THINK WE'LL TAKE THIS
MATTER UP.
OR WE'LL TAKE IT UP BUT IT IS
ALREADY BAKED IN.
YOU'VE HAD FOLKS LIKE THE GOOD
SENATOR FROM SOUTH CAROLINA, MR.
GRAHAM SAYING, I'M NOT EVEN
GOING TO READ THE MATERIAL THAT
COMES OVER FROM THE HOUSE.
SO THIS IS A PRECURSOR TO MAKE
SURE THAT DONALD TRUMP HAS
MAXIMUM PROTECTION.
THE QUESTION I HAVE IS FOR WHAT?
AT THE END OF THE DAY, WHAT DO
YOU GET OUT OF IT?
>> AND THE OTHER THING ABOUT IT
IS, YOU CAN PROTECT HIM IN THE
WAY THAT WILL HURD DID.
THERE ARE WAYS TO SAY HE
SHOULDN'T BE IMPEACHED IN WAYS
THAT ARE NOT REPEATING THIS
CRAZY THEORY THAT IS BEING BOTH
DISSEMINATED BY RUSSIAN
INFORMATION, ASIDE FROM BEING
HIGHLY WRONG AND MISLEADING.
>> WHAT THEY'RE TRYING TO DO,
THE SAME THING THAT TRUMP DOES
HIMSELF.
SOME PEOPLE SAY THIS.
SO THE PUBLIC SAYS, WELL, THERE
ARE TWO SIDES HERE.
>> OR ENOUGH FOR THE PUBLIC AND
PARTICULARLY THE PRESIDENT'S
BASE TO POINT TO A BUNK OF
THINGS THAT FEELS LIKE IT LETS
THEM OFF THE HOOK.
THIS IS A WITCH HUNT.
>> SO YOU HAVE TRUMP HIMSELF WHO
TAKES EVERYTHING TO THE MAXIMUM
EXTREME.
ALL RIGHT?
AND JUST MAKES IT, FROM A WITCH
HUNT TO THIS AND THAT.
AND EVERYONE WHO FOLLOWED BEHIND
HIM HAVE TO GO THAT FAR AS WELL.
>> YES.
THEY ALL BECOME EVERYONE.
IT IS WILD TO WATCH.
I SAW THIS HAPPEN THIS WEEKEND.
THERE WAS A FIGHT HAPPENING IN
WHICH, JOHNNY ISAACSON IS
RETIRING IN THE GEORGIA SENATE.
SO THERE IS THIS BIZARRE BATTL
THAT'S BREWING IN WHICH THE
PRESIDENT WANTS TO NAME DOUG
COLLINS, A SORT OF STRONG
BLOCKING BACK FOR THE PRESIDENT,
RIGHT?
ONE OF THE BASEMENT BOYS WHO
GOES IN THERE AND LEVELS AGAINST
THE MEDIA.
AND HE WANTS TO APPOINT THIS
BUSINESS WOMAN FROM THE STATE.
AND WHAT YOU SEE IS THIS
PERSONALITY.
NOT A NOVEL INSIGHT THAT YOU A
TOTAL ONE THAT REVOLVES AROUND
THE PRESIDENT.
MATT DPAITS IS SECOND GUESSING
THE PRESIDENT'S JUDGE.
HE WANTS PEOPLE ARE ESSENTIALLY
LIKE A LENINIST CADRE AROUND
HIM.
>> THAT'S THE SCARIEST PART.
TRUMP WHERE HE STAYS OR GOES IS
HEAVING US WHERE WE HAVE TO
REBUILD CIVIL SOCIETY.
WE HAVE TO REBUILD THE WHOLE
IDEA OF A DEMOCRATIC SOCIETY
THAT WE'VE HAD BECAUSE HE'S
ERODING ALL THE VALUES, ALL THE
NORMS.
IT'S A CULT, AS YOU SAID.
THAT EVERYBODY OUT THIS SAYS, WE
HAVE TO GO ALONG WITH WHAT HE
WANTS.
HE'LL TELL US WHO HE WANTS TO
BE.
>> EXACTLY.
HE WILL TELL THE GOVERNOR OF
GEORGIA WHO HE SHOULD APPOINT.
AND IT IS ESSENTIALLY IPSO FACTO
ON ITS FACE FOR ANYONE TO
CONTEST OR DISAGREE WITH THE
PRESIDENT ON THAT.
THAT THERE IS NO FIRST BASE
SPACE FOR ANYONE TO HAVE AN
INDEPENDENT VIEW ON ANY MATTER.
>> NO.
THERE IS ONLY ONE VIEW AND
THAT'S TRUMP'S VIEW.
TO MICKEY'S POINT, THAT'S WHAT
MAKES THIS ALL SO DANGEROUS.
AS MICKEY NOTED, WE WILL HAVE TO
DO SOME SERIOUS REBUILDING.
NOT JUST THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
WHICH IS SOMEWHAT IRRELEVANT IN
THE OVERALL SCHEME.
WE'VE TAKEN OURSELVES SO FAR
OUTSIDE OF, WE'RE NOT EVEN NEAR
A STREAM.
WE'RE JUST STANDING IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOWHERE WITH DONALD
TRUMP SCREAMING AT US.
BUT THAT'S THE PROBLEM FOR THE
REST OF US AS WE TRY TO PUT BACK
IN PLACE THOSE INSTITUTIONS THAT
HAVE SAFEGUARDED NOT JUST OUR
DOMESTIC SECURITY BUT OUR
FOREIGN SECURITY AS WELL.
AND IT MAKES IT MUCH HARDER TO
DO WHEN YOU SECONDS GUESS AND
DOUBT EVERYTHING THAT YOU HEAR,
SESEE, AND READ.
>> THAT'S THE IDEA BEHIND IT
ALL.
THANK YOU BOTH.
THAT WAS GOOD.
>> NEXT, A WHOLE NEW COMMITTEE.
CONGRESSMAN JAMIE RASKIN JOINS
ME HERE TO TALK ABOUT WHAT WE'LL
SEE THIS WEEK.
WILDLY DIFFERENT FROM THE INTEL
HEARINGS.
little
love my-y way ♪
♪ Spread a little
something to remember ♪
Philadelphia cream cheese.
Made with fresh milk
and real cream
makes your recipes
their holiday favourites.
The holidays are
made with Philly.
I'm your curious cat,
and you know what they
thsay about curiosity.es.
It'll ruin your house.
So get Allstate and be better
protected from Mayhem,
like meow.
(contemplative synth music)
- [Narrator] Forget about
vacuuming for up to a month.
Shark IQ Robot deep-cleans
and empties itself
into a base you can
empty once a month.
And unlike standard
robots that bounce around,
it cleans row by row.
If it's not a Shark,
it's just a robot.
>>> THIS WEEK STARTS THE NEXT
BIG PHASE OF THE IMPEACHMENT
INQUIRY.
WE GO FROM QUESTIONS OF FACT TO
QUESTIONS OF LAW.
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
DID THE FACT-FINDING PORTION OF
THIS.
IT WILL BE A PORTION FOR THE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE TO WRESTLE
WITH WHAT COUNTS AS TREASON,
HIGH CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS AND
WHETHER THE PRESIDENT WITH THE
FACTS THAT HAVE BEEN ESTABLISHED
HAS MET THAT STANDARD.
>> FORMER LAW PROFESSOR, WHO HAS
BEEN PROVIDING GUIDANCE ON HOW
TO NAVIGATE THIS AND HE JOINS ME
NOW.
>> WHAT DO YOU SEE?
>> THERE WERE COMPLAINTS FROM
REPUBLICANS.
AND THERE WAS A GHOST OF A
POINT.
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE DOING
THE FACT-FINDING PART OF THIS
WAS A LITTLE DIFFERENT THAN HOW
IT HAS BEEN HANDLED IN THE PAST.
GIVEN THAT IT IS BEING PASSED
FROM INTEL TO THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE, WHAT DO YOU VIEW AS
YOUR COMMITTEE'S RULE?
>> WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT WHAT
THE FOUNDER'S MEN BY HAVING
IMPEACHMENT IN THE CONSTITUTION.
WE KNOW THE ELECTORAL COLLEGE
MEETS EVERY FOUR YEARS.
WHY DID THEY DECIDE TO HAVE
IMPEACHMENT IN THERE?
THEY WANTED THE PEOPLE TO HAVE A
LAST INSTRUMENT OF
CONSTITUTIONAL SELF-DEFENSE
AGAINST A PRESIDENT WHO ACTS
LIKE A KING AND TRAMPLES THE
TRULY OF LAW.
IT IS ALL ABOUT GETTING RID OF
THE KINGS.
IT WAS ALL KINGS AND QUEENS AND
ELECTION AND TREACHERY AND WAR
BY THE KINGDOMS FOR POWER.
THEY WANTED TO CREATE ON A
DIFFERENT PRINCIPLE.
IT WAS THE KING IS THAT THE
QUEEN AND THE CLERKY AND ON THE
BOTTOM WAS THE PEOPLE.
AND OUR FOUNDERS FILMED IT
UPSIDE DOWN AND SAID WE THE
PEOPLE.
WE STARTED THAT IT WAY.
THE FRAMERS PUT IN EVERY
CONCEIVABLE SAFEGUARD TO MAKE
SURE THE PRESIDENT WOULD NOT
BECOME LIKE A KING.
>> YOU'RE USING THIS FRAMEWORK.
WHAT ABOUT WHEN SOMEONE SAYS, I
DON'T CARE WHAT THE FOUNDERS
THOUGHT.
WHY DOES IT MATTER TO ME?
WHY SHOULD I CARE IN I'M A NURSE
OR A REAL ESTATE PROFESSIONAL
AND I DON'T LIKE DONALD TRUMP.
WHAT IS THE BITE OF WHAT HE HAS
DONE IN THE LIFE OF THE
REPUBLICAN?
>> THE WHOLE POINT IS BITS THE
COMMON PEOPLE.
IT IS ABOUT THE COMMO  PEOPLE.
NOT A MONEY MAKING OPERATION FOR
ONE GUY AND HIS ROYAL FAMILY.
IT IS NOT TO EXPAND THE BUSINESS
EMPIRE AND TO WORK WITH TYRANTS
AND DESPOTS AROUND THE WORLD.
IT IS SUPPOSED TO BE FOR THE
COMMON GOOD.
IT IS SUPPOSED TO BE TO ADVANCE
THE COMMON GOOD.
TO PROVIDE FOR THE COMMON
DEFENSE.
THE BLESSINGS OF LIBERTY.
THAT'S THE PREAMBLE OF OUR
CONSTITUTION AND IT FLOWS INTO
ARTICLE ONE WHICH SAYS THE
LEGISLATIVE POWER IS VESTED IN
CONGRESS.
IT IS UP TO CONGRESS TO BE THE
PEOPLE.
COMMERCE, WAR, COPY RIGHT.
AND THEN YOU GET ON ARTICLE TWO
AND IT IS FOUR SHORT SECTIONS.
ONE IS ABOUT IMPEACHING THE
PRESIDENT WHO FORGETS WHAT HIS
JOB IS.
WHAT IS HIS REAL JOB?
TO TAKE CARE THAT THE LAW IS
FAITHFULLY EXECUTED.
>> YOU JUST OUTLINED A BROAD
CASE.
IN THE ABSTRACT THEORETICAL
TERMS.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
PRESIDENCY IS A PUBLIC TRUST FOR
THE GENERAL WELFARE.
THE JOINT CONSTITUTIONAL
CONCEPTION.
VERSUS USING IT AS A PRIVATE GET
RICH QUICK OPERATION.
OR A PRIVATE MEANS OF MACHINE
POWER THAT WE'VE SEEN.
LIKE CORRUPT WARD BOSSES.
>> YES.
>> IS THAT THE CASE THAT YOU
ANTICIPATE MAKING?
THAT'S BROADER THAN WHAT I
UNDERSTAND IS COMING DOWN THE
PIPE FROM INTEL ABOUT UKRAINE.
>> THE FRAMERS OF THE
CONSTITUTION.
WHAT WE HAVE IN MIND.
WE HAVE TO RECOVER THIS.
WE NEED A NATIONAL CIVICS LESSON
INTO WHAT OUR CONSTITUTION IS
ABOUT.
THE CONGRESS WAS CHARGED WITH
THE POWER OF PROMOTING THE
GENERAL WELFARE.
IT IS CONGRESS THAT PASSES THE
LAWS.
THE PRESIDENT'S JOB TO TAKE CARE
THAT IT IS GENERALLY EXECUTED.
WHY DO WE HAVE THE POWER TO
IMPEACH THE PRESIDENT AND HE
DOESN'T HAVE THE POWER TO
IMPEACH US?
THE FRAMERS OF THE CONSTITUTION
WANTED TO PUT THE PEOPLE AND
THEIR REPRESENTATIVES IN CHARGE.
WHAT WE'RE ABOUT TO EMBARK ON IS
NOT ABOUT CRIME AND PUNISHMENT.
DONALD TRUMP WOULD NOT TO GO
JAIL FOR ONE DAY UNDER
IMPEACHMENT.
IT IS MAKING SURE THAT THE
GOVERNMENT IS WORKING FOR THE
PEOPLE AND NOT FOR THE PRIVATE
INTERESTS OF THE PRESIDENT.
HERE OR ANYWHERE ELSE.
>> HERE'S MY DIAGNOSIS OF THE
WAY THE CAUCUS HAS RESPONDED TO
NEW FACTS.
THE FOLLOWING.
I WANT TO HEAR YOUR RESPONSE.
THEY THOUGHT THE MUELLER REPORT
WAS VERY BAD.
THEY THOUGHT THEY HAD SHOWED
THAT THE PRESIDENT DID OBSTRUCT
JUSTICE AND THAT'S AN
IMPEACHABLE OFFENSE BUST THEY
WERE WARY THAT IT WAS A
DIFFICULT CASE TO MAKE TO THE
PUBLIC AND THAT THERE IS A
POLITICAL WILL THAT HAS TO
HAPPEN.
AND THE MOMENT FOR THE MEMBERS
OF THE CAUCUS WAS SEEING HIM USE
HIS POWERS TO ATTEMPT TO RIG THE
NEXT ELECTION.
HOW MUCH DOES THAT FEATURE IN
ABOUT WHY IT CROSSES?
>> I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT
THE MUELLER REPORT.
IT WAS ABOUT WHAT THAT IN 2016
IN THAT ELECTION.
AND REMEMBER, THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL BARR ESSENTIALLY
KIDNAPPED THE REPORT FOR THREE
AND A HALF WEEKS, MISSTATED THE
CONTENTS, PROMPTING TO WRITE NOT
ONE BUT TWO LETTERS OF PROTEST
ABOUT CONFUSION OF THE PUBLIC.
BUT THIS WAS VERY DIFFERENT WITH
THE UKRAINE SHAKEDOWN.
IT WAS HAPPENING IN REAL-TIME.
THE PRESIDENT WASN'T DELEGATING
TO IT ERIC TRUMP AND DONALD
TRUMP JR.
HE WAS DOING IT HIMSELF.
HE WAS THE ONE ON THAT JULY 25th
PHONE CALL.
HE WAS THE ONE WHO SENT RUDY
GIULIANI AND HIS TEAM OF
OPERATIVES TO SHAKE DOWN THE
UKRAINIAN GOVERNMENT.
SO ALL OF THIS HAPPENED IN
REAL-TIME.
ATTORNEY GENERAL BARR WAS NOT
ABLE TO COVER IT UP.
SO THIS IS THE MOST VIVID
DEMONSTRATION OF HOW THEY'RE
DOING BUSINESS IN THE TRUMP
WHITE HOUSE.
>> THAT'S THE QUESTION THAT
HAUNTS ME PERSONALLY.
IS THIS THE ONLY TIME THEY DID
IT?
>> IF IT ISN'T, I WOULD LIKE TO
HAVE THE FACTS ABOUT WHAT THE
BACK CHANNEL OF TURKEY IS LIKE
AND SAUDI ARABIA IS LIKE AND A
VARIETY OF OTHER FOREIGN POLICY
MOVES.
THE PRESIDENT HAS MADE THROUGH
THE BACK CHANNELS.
THEY'VE BEEN INCREDIBLY FRIENDLY
TO STATES THAT HAVE LEFT PEOPLE
SCRATCHING THEIR HEADS.
JOHN BOLTON TOLD A PRIVATE GROUP
OF PEOPLE, HE THINKS FINANCIAL
INTERESTS ARE DRIVING IT.
THAT'S JOHN BOLTON.
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID IN A PRIVATE
DINNER.
>> AND THE EMOLUMENTS CLAUSE IS
CENTRAL TO UNDERSTANDING THE
FRAMERS' CONCEPTION OF OUR
CONSTITUTION.
IT IS NOT THE PRESIDENT'S JOCK
RUNNING OFF SELL HIS INFLUENCE
TO FOREIGN POWERS TO GET HIMSELF
RICH.
NOR IS IT THE PRESIDENT'S JOB TO
CHANNEL THE.
AT A PAIRS' MONEY.
>> THAT'S A LEGAL RESPONSE.
I DONE FEEL LIKE I KNOW FULLY AS
A U.S. CITIZEN AND A JOURNALIST
WHO COVERS THIS.
>> I SHARED YOUR PASSION FOR
FINDING OUT THE ANSWERS TO EVERY
ONE OF THOSE PARTICULAR LEADS.
IT IS ABOUT COULD NOT OUR
OVERSIGHT RESPONSIBILITY.
ON THE OTHER HAND, DONALD TRUMP,
NOT HERE IN THE CONTEXT OF
IMPEACHMENT BUT AS A POLITICAL
OBSERVER WHO HAS WATCHED FOR
SEVERAL YEARS IN CONGRESS.
AS HE ONE-MAN CRIME WAVE.
HE HAS MORE THAN 3,000 LAWSUITS
THAT HE'S EMBROILED IN.
WHEN HE WAS IN PRIVATE BUSINESS,
HE DID NOT FAYE CONTRACTORS AND
HE DIDN'T PAY THE PLUMBERS AND
HE DIDN'T PAY THE CARPENTERS.
HE DIDN'T PAY ANYBODY AND
THERE'S LOTS OF LITIGATION
THERE.
WITH UNIONS AND ON AND ON.
WE CAN'T DO ALL OF THAT HERE.
WE WON'T BE ABLE TO DO THAT
HERE.
BUT WE CAN DO IS DETERMINE
WHETHER THERE WERE HIGH CRIMES
AND MISDEMEANORS.
THE CONSTITUTION TALKS ABOUT
TREASON, BRIBERY, OTHER HIGH
CRIMES AND MISDEMEANORS.
THEY'RE BETRAILS OF THE
ESSENTIAL DUTIES OF THE OFFICE.
TREASON BETRAYS NATIONAL
SECURITY.
BRIBERY BETRAYS THE PUBLIC
INTEREST.
THE OTHER HIGH CRIMES AND
MISDEMEANORS ARE SUBSTITUTING
YOUR PRIVATE INTERESTS AND
AMBITIONS FOR THE NATIONAL
INTERESTS.
FOR THE PUBLIC INTEREST.
AND I THINK THE UKRAINE ELSE
CAPTURES ALL OF THEM.
IT ALSO LEADS INTO OTHER ABUSES
OF POWER.
THE SORTS OF OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE THAT WE'VE SEEN FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TRIED TO
BLOCKADE WITNESSES.
HE'S TRIED TO WITHHOLD EVIDENCE.
HE'S TRIED TO FRUSTRATE OUR
INVESTIGATION AT EVERY TURN.
AND EVERYBODY SHOULD BE
CONCERNED ABOUT THAT.
WHATEVER YOU THINK ABOUT THE
SHAKEDOWN ITSELF, WHETHER YOU
THINK IT WAS BRIBERY, EXTORTION
OR SOMETHING ELSE.
WHATEVER YOU THINK, EVERYBODY
SHOULD BE OPPOSED TO THE
PRESIDENT BEING ABLE TO
OBSTRUCT.
WHAT IT MEANS IS WE HAVE A
PRESIDENT WHO CAN OPERATE WITH
IMPUGNITY AND IMMUNITY.
HE IS ABLE TO COVER UP HIS
CRIMES.
THAT'S A VERY DANGEROUS
PRECEDENT TO SET.
>> OKAY.
WE'LL BE SEEING YOU WEDNESDAY AT
THAT HEARING.
COME BY ANY TIME.
>>> NEXT, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS FEELING
PRESSURE TO PASS THEIR SIGNATURE
AGENDA ITEM THIS YEAR.
WHY IT LOOKS LIKE SOME HOUSE
DEMOCRATS ARE PREPARED TO HELP
HIM OUT.
AFTER THIS.
AFTER THIS
(Speaking Japanese) Where am I?
(Woman Speaking French)
Are you crazy/nuts?
Cyclist: Pip! Pip!
(Woman Speaking French)
I'm here, look at me. It's
completely your fault.
(Man Speaking French)
OK? It's me. It's my fault?
No, I can't believe how
easy it was
to save hundreds of dollars on
my car insurance with GEICO.
(Pterodactyl screech)
Believe it.
GEICO could save you 15% or more
on car insurance.
Fine, no one leaves the
table until your finished.
Fine, we'll sleep here.
♪
It's the easiest because
it's the cheesiest.
Kraft. For the win win.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
>>> THERE ARE EIGHT LEGISLATIVE
DAYS LEFT ON THE CALENDAR AND IN
THAT LITTLE TIME FOR DONALD
TRUMP AND HIS REPUBLICAN ALLIES
IS GETTING THE HOUSE
REPRESENTATIVES TO PASS NAFTA
2.0 OR THE U.S. MCA.
UNITED STATES, MEXICO, CANADA
AGREEMENT.
SOMEWHAT REMARKABLY GIVEN THE
SITUATION WE'RE IN, A
SIGNIFICANT NUMBER OF HOUSE
DEMOCRATS REPRESENTING SWING
DISTRICTS SEEM EAGER TO DO THE
SAIL.
LARGELY BECAUSE WOULD IT GIVE
THEM A TANGIBLE DELIVERABLE.
THEY SAY, LOOK.
WE GOT SOMETHING DONE.
AT THE SAME TIME, LABOR UNIONS,
INCREDIBLY IMPORTANT
CONSTITUENCY, ARE STILL OPPOSED
TO MANY OF THE FEATURES OF THE
AGREEMENT OF THE ESPECIALLY ON
THE ENFORCEMENT SIDE.
AND THERE'S A REAL OPEN
POLITICAL QUESTION ABOUT WHETHER
RATIFYING ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S
BIGGEST AGENDA ITEMS AND HANDING
HIM A VICTORY IS THE BEST WAY TO
GIVE CONTROL OF THE HOUSE WHILE
THEY'RE ALSO IMPEACHING HIM.
JOINING ME, HE WROTE A PIECE
ENTITLED A BAD TRADE.
I'VE BEEN READING YOU ON THIS
AND YOU'VE BEEN DOING REPORTING
ON IT.
FIRST LET ME GET YOUR SENSE AS
SOMEONE COVERING THIS VERY, VERY
CLOSELY WHERE THINGS STAND RIGHT
NOW WITH THE POSSIBILITY OF IT
BEING RATIFIED.
>> WELL, THE LAST THING THAT
NANCY PELOSI SAID WAS, SHE WAS
HOPEFUL THAT THERE COULD BE
SOMETHING THAT SHE COULD PUT ON
THE FLOOR BY THE END OF THE
YEAR.
IF YOU REALLY DIG INTO ALL THESE
STORIES, AND LOOK AT THE NAMES
OF WHO IS PUSHING FOR THIS DEAL,
IT IS THE SAME DOZEN, MAYBE 15
HOUSE DEMOCRATS FROM MARGIAL
DISTRICTS, LED BY SHERRY, THE
HEAD OF THE D TRIPLE C, THE
CAMPAIGN ARM, AND RICHIE NEIL,
THE HEAD OF THE WAYS AND XHEENS
COMMITTEE, SORT OF A CORPORATE
AVATAR IN SOME WAYS.
THOSE ARE WHO ARE PUSHING FOR
THIS DEAL FOR THE REASONS THAT
YOU DESCRIBE.
OUR SOURCES SAY THAT UNLESS
RICH, THE HEAD OF THE AFL-CIO
ACTUALLY SIGNS OFF ON THIS
THING, IT IS VERY UNLIKELY TO
PASS.
WE'VE HEARD THAT FROM MEMBERS.
WE'LL SEE IF THAT HOLDS.
AND PELOSI IS IN THE MIDDLE OF
ALL THIS WORKING BETWEEN THE
DOZEN ODD HOUSE DEMOCRATS WHO
SEEM TO BE WANTING TO GET
SOMETHING DONE IN ORDER TO SAY
THEY CAN GET SOMETHING DONE, AND
THE VAST MAJORITY OF THE CAUCUS
AND THE LABOR MOVEMENT WHO ARE
OPPOSED TO IT.
>> IT SEEMS TO ME, BEFORE THIS
DRAFTING WAS MORE FINALIZED AND
THESE QUESTIONS WERE IRONED OUT,
IT SEEMED THAT IT WOULD BE A
GENUINELY DIFFICULT CROSS
PRESSURE SITUATION IF YOU
BELIEVED WHOLEHEARTEDLY IT WAS A
GOOD AGREEMENT BUT YOU WOULD BE
HANDING A POLITICAL VICTORY TO
DONALD TRUMP.
YOU WOULD HAVE TO SAY, I BELIEVE
IN THE AGREEMENT, I'LL SIGN AND
IT IF DONALD TRUMP GETS CREDIT,
THAT'S WHAT I'LL DO.
I'M JUST HERE TO LEGISLATE.
BUT IN THIS CASE, THE BIGGEST
CONSTITUENCY OF LABOR IS STILL
NOT ON BOARD YET.
>> THE BIGGEST PROBLEM AS YOU
MENTIONED, ENFORCEMENT.
WE HAVE A SITUATION IN MEXICO
WHERE TRADE UNIONISTS ARE STILL
BEING KILLED, KIDNAPPED,
DISAPPEARED.
AND WE'RE GOING TO POTENTIALLY
PASS A TRADE DEAL THAT ALLOWS
THEM ON OPERATE AND ASSUMES THAT
THEY'RE GOING TO ENFORCE THE
LABOR SECTIONS OF THE AGREEMENT,
WHICH ARE SUPPOSED TO BE BETTER
FOR WORKERS WERE NOT MEXICO IN
TERMS OF THEIR WAGES AND THEIR
CONDITIONS, WHICH IN TURN THE
THEORY GOES, WILL IMPROVE, LIMIT
OUTSOURCING AND IMPROVE THE
INDUSTRIAL BASE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
IT DOESN'T MAKE A LOT OF SENSE.
THAT THAT WOULD BE THE CASE.
AND THERE ARE OTHER THINGS IN
THE AGREEMENT THAT ARE POSITIVE.
IT IS DEFINITELY A MIXED BAG.
AN AGREEMENT THAT THE
ENFORCEMENT IS SKETCHY ON IS NOT
REALLY WORTH THE PAPER IT'S
PRINTED ON.
IF THE WHOLE POINT IS TO IMPROVE
LABOR CONDITIONS, AND HAVE THAT
RISING TIDE LIFT ALL BOATS FOR
ALL WORKERS THROUGHOUT NORTH
AMERICA.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THE EXECUTIVE EDITOR OF THE
AMERICAN PROSPECT.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU ON.
>> STILL AHEAD, DONALD TRUMP JR.
GETS A BOOST IN BOOK SALES FROM
PEOPLE TRYING TO GET ON THE GOOD
SIDE OF OLD DAD.
THE BULK ORDERS COMING UP.
PLUS TONIGHT'S THING ONE, THING
TWO.
IT'S A DOOZY.
Liberty Biberty-
Cut. We'll dub it.
Liberty Mutual customizes
your car insurance
so you only pay for
what you need.
Only pay for what you need.
♪ Liberty. Liberty.
Liberty. Liberty. ♪
♪ Spread a little love today ♪
♪ Spread a little
love my-y way ♪
something to remember ♪
Philadelphia cream cheese.
Made with fresh milk
and real cream
makes your recipes
their holiday favourites.
The holidays are
made with Philly.
Man: sneezes
Skip to the good part with
Alka-Seltzer Plus.
their holiday favourites.
Now with 25% more
concentrated power.
Nothing works faster for
powerful cold relief.
Oh, what a relief it is!
So fast!
I looove travel.
Italy!
Yaaaaass.
With the United
Explorer Card,
I get rewarded
wherever I go.
Going out for a bite.
Rewarded!
Going new places.
Anytime.
Rewarded!
Getting more
for getting away.
Rewarded!
Learn more at The Explorer Card
dot com.
and get...
Rewarded!
Thousands of women with
metastatic breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of the body,
are living in the moment
and taking IBRANCE.
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor
is for postmenopausal women
or for men with HR+/HER2-
metastatic breast cancer,
as the first hormonal
based therapy.
IBRANCE plus letrozole
significantly delayed
disease progression
versus letrozole,
and shrank tumors in
over half of patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE
can develop low
white blood cell counts
which may cause
serious infections
that can lead to death.
IBRANCE may cause severe
inflammation of the lungs
that can lead to death.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have new
or worsening symptoms,
including trouble breathing,
shortness of breath,
cough, or chest pain.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if
you have fever, chills,
or other signs of infection,
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects
include low red blood cell
and low platelet counts,
infections, tiredness, nausea,
sore mouth, abnormalities
in liver blood tests,
diarrhea,
hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Be in your moment.
Ask your doctor
about IBRANCE.
Donald Trump failed as a
businessman.
He borrowed billions
and left a trail of bankruptcy
and broken promises.
He hasn't changed.
I started a tiny investment
business,
and over 27 years,
grew it successfully to 36
billion dollars.
I'm Tom Steyer and I approve
this message.
I'm running for president
because unlike other candidates,
I can go head to head with
Donald Trump on the economy,
and expose him fo what he is:
a fraud and a failure.
>>> THING ONE TONIGHT.
IF YOU REMEMBER BACK TO THE
EARLY DAYS OF 2016, THE VERY
FIRST MEMBERS OF CONGRESS TO
PUBLICLY ENDORSE THE CAMPAIGN OF
DONALD TRUMP FOR THE PRESIDENT
WERE THESE TWO MEN.
CHRIS COLLINS, A REPUBLICAN FROM
NEW YORK, AND DUNKIAN HUNTER, A
REPUBLICAN FROM CALIFORNIA.
BOTH OF THESE MEN HAVE SINCE
BEEN INDICTED.
NOT FOR ENDORSING DONALD TRUMP.
FOR CHRIS COLLINS, IT WAS
INSIDER TRADING.
HE PLEADED GUILTY AND IS
AWAITING SENTENCING.
DUNCAN HUNTER WAS CHARGED WITH
60 COUNTS RELATED TO MISUSE OF
CAMPAIGN FUNDS.
HE DID NOT DO IT.
HE TOLD US HIS WIFE DID IT.
>> YOU ALSO SAID YESTERDAY THAT
YOUR WIFE HANDLED A LOT OF THE
FAMILY EXPENSES AND THE CAMPAIGN
FINANCES.
SO ARE YOU SAYING THAT IT IS
MORE HER FAULT THAN YOUR FAULT?
>> I'M SAYING, WHEN I WENT TO
IRAQ IN 2003 THE FIRST TIME.
I GAVE HER POWER OF ATTORNEY AND
SHE HANDLED MY FINANCES
THROUGHOUT MY ENTIRE MILITARY
CAREER AND THAT CONTINUED WHEN
I'VE GONE INTO CONGRESS.
I'M GONE FOR FIVE DAYS AND HOME
FOR TWO.
AND SHE'S MY CAMPAIGN MANAGER.
WHATEVER SHE DID, THAT WILL BE
LOOKED AT, BUT I DIDN'T DO IT.
>> WHATEVER SHE DID, THAT WILL
BE LOOKED AT.
HUSBAND OF THE YEAR, DUNCAN
HUNTER IS NOW CHANGING HIS TUNE.
THAT'S THING TWO.
TUNE.
THAT'S THING TWO
>>> DUNCAN HUNTER, THE
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN
REPRESENTING CALIFORNIA'S 50th
DISTRICT WAS INDICTED ALONG WITH
HIS WIFE FOR MISUSING CAMPAIGN
FUNDS ON A TRULY IMPRESSIVE
VARIETY OF ITEMS.
LIKE THEY APPARENTLY SPENT
$1,300 ON VIDEO GAMES, $800 ON
AN ORAL SURGEON, $14,000 FOR A
FAMILY VACATION IN ITALY, MORE
THAN $600 TO FLY THE FAMILY'S
PET RABBIT NAMED EVERYTHINGBERT
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
$462 FOR 30 SHOTS OF TEQUILA AND
NEARLY $900 TO STAY AT A HOTEL
WITH A WOMAN WHO WAS NOT HIS
WIFE.
KIND OF ON THE NOSE THERE.
FOR A WHILE HE WAS BLAMING HIS
FAMILY SAYING HIS SON USED THE
WRONG CREDIT CARD FOR THE VIDEO
GAMES AND HIS WIFE WAS IN CHARGE
OF THE FINANCES.
HE EVEN TOOK A PAGE OUT OF
PRESIDENT'S BOOK AND CALLED THE
WHOLE THING A WITCH HUNT.
NOW HE IS TAKING IT ALL BACK.
TOMORROW MORNING HE SAYS HE'S
TAKING UP THE DEAL PLEADING
GUILTY.
HE IS TAKING FULL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR HIS ACTIONS.
SORT OF.
>> THE PLEA THAT I SECOND WAS
MISUSE OF MY OWN CAMPAIGN FUNDS
OF WHICH I PLED GUILTY TO ONLY
ONE COUNT.
I THINK IT IS IMPORTANT THAT
PEOPLE KNOW THAT I DID MAKE
MISTAKES.
I DID NOT PROPERLY MONITOR OR
ACCOUNT FOR MY CAMPAIGN MONEY.
I JUSTIFIED THAT PLEA WITH THE
UNDERSTANDING THAT I AM
RESPONSIBLE FOR MY CAMPAIGN AND
WHAT HAPPENS TO MY CAMPAIGN
MONEY.
(Dog barking)
♪ (Music building) ♪
Experience the
power of sanctuary
at the Lincoln
Wish List Sales Event.
Sign and drive off
in a new Lincoln
with zero down,
zero due at signing,
and a complimentary
first month's payment.
My body is truly powerful.
I have the power to lower
my blood sugar and A1C.
Because I can still
make my own insulin.
And Trulicity activates
my body to release it
like it's supposed to.
Trulicity is for people
with type 2 diabetes.
It's not insulin.
I take it once a week.
It starts acting in my
body from the first dose.
Trulicity isn't for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Don't take Trulicity
if you're allergic to it,
you or your family have
medullary thyroid cancer,
or have multiple endocrine
neoplasia syndrome type 2.
Stop Trulicity and call
your doctor right away
if you have an
allergic reaction,
a lump or swelling in your neck,
or severe stomach pain.
Serious side effects
may include pancreatitis.
Taking Trulicity with a
sulfonylurea or insulin
increases low blood sugar risk.
Side effects include nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting, belly pain,
and decreased appetite,
which lead to dehydration and
may worsen kidney problems.
I have it within me
to lower my A1C.
Ask your doctor about Trulicity.
>>> IT'S A NEW MONTH OUT THERE.
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
WE CAN FINALLY ANNOUNCE THE
DATES FOR OUR FRIDAY NIGHT LIVE
SHOWS.
WE'VE GOT SOME REALLY GREAT
GUESTS IN THE WORKS AND I'M
EXCITED TO SHARE WITH YOU.
AND RIGHT NOW, THERE ARE TWO
DATES ON THE CALENDAR.
THIS FRIDAY, DECEMBER 6th AND
NEXT FRIDAY THE 13th.
TICKETS ARE AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW
AS IN RIGHT THIS SECOND.
IF YOU HEAD TO OUR WEBSITE,
MSNBC.COM/ALLIN AND COME JOIN
US.
AND THEN IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR
MORE OF THAT CONTENT IN NEW
YORK, THIS IS LAST STOP OF OUR
PODCAST TOUR.
HAVING THEM TOGETHER WILL MAKE
FOR A ARE CREATORS,
CONVERSATIONALISTS, THESE EVENTS
HAVE BEEN ASTOUNDING, THE ENERGY
THE SORT OF VIBE.
I'LL BE JOINED BY TONY KUSHNER,
NOT ONLY ONE OF MY INTELLECTUAL
HEROES, TONY AND EMMY WINNING
PAY RIGHT, KNOWN FOR ANGELS IN
AMERICA AND "A BRIGHT ROOM
CALLED DAY," BLUES I'M GOING TO
BE TALKING ABOUT JEREMY O HARRIS
"SLAVE PLAY" IS BLOWING UP RIGHT
NOW.
A WIDE RANGING CONVERSATION
ABOUT POWER, AND SPECTACLE AND
STORY TELLING DURING THESE
SURREAL TIMES.
CANNOT WAIT TO SEE YOU THERE.
TE
That's why Fidelity
leads the industry in value
while our competition
continues to talk.
♪ Talk, talk ♪
♪ Spread a little love today ♪
♪ Spread a little
love my-y way ♪
something to remember ♪
Philadelphia cream cheese.
Made with fresh milk
and real cream
makes your recipes
their holiday favourites.
The holidays are
made with Philly.
♪
I thought I was managing.
my moderate
to severe Crohn's disease.
Then I realized something
was missing... me.
My symptoms were keeping me
from being there.
So, I talked to my doctor
and learned HUMIRA is for people
who still have symptoms
of Crohn's disease
after trying other medications.
And the majority
of people on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom relief
and many achieved remission
in as little as 4 weeks.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened;
as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions, and
new or worsening heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Be there for you, and them.
Ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
(birds chirping)
(KICKSTART MY HEART
BY MOTLEY CRUE)
(truck honks)
(wheels screeching)
(clapping)
(sound of can hitting
bag and bowl)
(clapping)
Always there in crunch time.
>>> DONALD TRUMP JR., THE
PRESIDENT'S SON HAS LITERALLY
SPENT HIS ENTIRE ADULT LIFE
TRADING ON HIS DAD'S NAME.
THAT HAS CONTINUED INTO THE
PRESIDENCY WHERE HE WROTE A BOOK
MARKETED TO MAGA HEADS
EVERYWHERE, AND THE BOOK WAS
PUBLISHED LAST MONTH AND DEBUTED
ON THE "NEW YORK TIMES"
NONFICTION BEST SELLER LIST.
IT APPEARED WITH THIS DAGGER
SYMBOL NEXT TO IT AND THAT
INDICATES THE BOOK IS ON THE
BEST SELLER LIST, NOT
NECESSARILY BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE
BUYING COPIES BUT BECAUSE SOME
ENTITIES ARE BUYING THE BOOK IN
BULK.
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" HAS A STORY
OF JUST HOW BULK SALES HELPED
PROPEL THE NEW BOOK TO NUMBER
ONE.
OVER A HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS
SPENT BY THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
AND ID LOGICALLY FRIENDLY
OUTFITS.
POLITICAL AND INVESTIGATIVE
REPORTER, NICK CONOSORA GOT THE
SCOOP AND HE JOINS ME NOW.
WHAT'S THE STORY ON THE BULK
PURCHASES IN THIS BOOK?
WE FOUND NINE ORGANIZATIONS OF
GOP PARTY, WHO ARE SELLING THE
BOOK TO DONORS OR PROMOTING
STOPS ON TRUMP'S BOOK TOUR.
EITHER WAY, IT ADDS UP TO A
MASSIVE PROMOTIONAL EFFORT FOR A
FIRST TIME AUTHOR WHO DOESN'T
HOLD OFFICE AND IS STILL BEST
KNOWN AS HIS FATH'S SON.
>> THE NATIONAL REPUBLICAN
COMMITTEE SPENT $75,000 ON THE
COPIES OF THE BOOK.
THE RNC THROUGH OCTOBER, 94,000,
AND TURNING POINT USA HAD BOUGHT
ABOUT 2,000 COPIES AND THE
NATIONAL REPUBLICAN SENATORIAL
COMMITTEE, JUST SO FOLKS KNOW,
FOR THE FIRST FEW WEEKS OF A
BOOK, THAT'S AN ENORMOUS AMOUNT
OF SALES.
IF YOU DID THAT TO ANY BOOK, YOU
WOULD BE PUSHING IT UP THE LIST.
>> HE'S A TRUMP.
AND IT'S A LARGE BOOK FOR THE
IMPRINT.
I THINK PROBABLY ON THE BEST
SELLER LIST, A BOOK TOUR, THE
QUESTION IS WHERE WOULD HE BE.
THAT'S NOT SO CLEAR.
HIS PEOPLE SAY IT WOULD BE AT
NUMBER ONE NO MATTER WHAT.
THE POINT IS I, YOU KNOW, FOUND
36 MILLION E-MAILS SENT OUT TO
PEOPLE WHO WERE PART OF THESE
DIFFERENT GROUPS PROMOTING THE
BOOK.
>> THAT IS A LOT OF PUBLICITY.
>> THAT'S NOT THAT MUCH BUT IT'S
A GREAT THING FOR A FIRST TIME
AUTHOR.
AND YOU PUT PRETTY MUCH ANY BOOK
IN 36 MILLION E-MAILS, IT'S
GOING TO HAVE A PRETTY GOOD
CHANCE.
>> MY FAVORITE DETAIL, WHICH IS
IN THE LEAD OF THE ARTICLE IS
THAT THE BOOKS ARE STOCKPILED AT
TALKING POINT USA IN THE OFFICE
IN BOXES, I THINK WE HAVE THE
PHOTO AND IT'S UNDERNEATH A
POSTER THAT SAYS IF YOU READ IT
THERE, CAPITALISM, NOT CROW CRO.
>> THERE WAS SOME CONFUSION AS
WHAT THE PURPOSE OF THE BOOK WAS
FOR.
I WAS TOLD BY TURNING POINT THEY
PLAN TO HAND OUT COPIES OF THE
BOOK TO VIP TICKET HOLDERS AT
UPCOMING CONFERENCE WHERE DONALD
TRUMP JR. IS A HEADLINER AND
WILL BE SIGNING BOOKS.
>> I THINK THIS IS HILARIOUS
BECAUSE IT'S THE WORLD'S MOST
FAMOUS LEGACY CASE GETTING HELP
FROM DADDY BUT ALSO INTERESTING
BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN A CULTURAL
TRANSFORMATION AMONG THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY, REPUBLICAN
CAMPAIGN OPERATIONS AND
IDEALOGICALLY AFFILIATED GROUPS.
THEY ARE SPENDING MORE AND MORE
MONEY AT TRUMP PROPERTIES, AT A
TIME, RIPPING OFF YOUR DONORS
HAS BECOME A HABITUAL PART.
>> FROM TRUMP HOTEL TO
WASHINGTON, TO TRUMP DORAL IN
FLORIDA, BUSINESS BEFORE THE
ADMINISTRATION, HOLD YOUR EVENT
AT A TRUMP PROPERTY.
IF YOU'RE A FOREIGN COUNTRY,
HOLD YOUR NATIONAL INDEPENDENCE
CELEBRATION AT A TRUMP PARTY,
HOLD YOUR ANNUAL HOLIDAY PARTY
AT A TRUMP PARTY.
EVERYONE UNDERSTANDS THIS IS A
HELPFUL WAY TO GET AHEAD IN
TRUMP'S WASHINGTON.
>> WE ALSO WERE TOLD, IT'S WORTH
REMINDING PEOPLE OF THIS, THERE
WAS THE BIG PRESS CONFERENCE
WITH A BUNCH OF STACKS OF PAPER
AND HIS LAWYER, TURNED OUT LATER
THE PAPER WAS BLANK, WAS A PROP,
THE PRESIDENT WASN'T DIVESTING
FROM BUSINESSES BUT ERECTS THIS
CONCEPTUAL BARRIER, AND HIS
LARGE ADULT SONS WOULD BE THE
ONES RUNNING THE BUSINESS WHILE
HE TOOK TIME AWAY IF THEM.
IT'S CLEAR TO ANYONE WHO
WATCHES, THESE TWO WERE
OBVIOUSLY INTERMINGLED IN EVERY
POSSIBLE WAY.
>> IT'S HARD TO KEEP TRACK,
RIGHT, DONALD JR. IF HE'S
ATTACK
IMPEACHMENT WITNESSES, I'M A
PRIVATE CITIZEN.
SO HE SEEMS TO INHABIT BOTH
ROLES AS CONVENIENT FOR THEM.
>> DO YOU THINK THERE IS ANY
PUSHBACK AMONG DONORS ON THIS
ARRANGEMENT?
IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE THAT'S PART
OF WHAT'S SO INTERESTING.
MOST OF THE PLACES THAT YOU ARE
SEEING SOFT CORRUPTION, OR
PAY-TO-PLAY CORRUPTION IS WITH
DONOR'S MONEY.
IT IS WITH THE WORLD OF PEOPLE
THAT ARE HAVING RAISED FROM THEM
AND CIRCLES ARE FINE WITH THE
PRESIDENT OR HIS FAMILY GETTING
A CUT.
>> I WILL SAY THEY'RE FINE WITH
IT.
ALMOST EVERYONE WHO'S GETTING
ONE OF THESE BOOKS THROUGH ONE
OF THE PARTY COMMITTEES CLICKED
ON AN E-MAIL SAYING YES, I WILL
GIVE YOU MONEY FOR A COPY OF THE
BOOK.
I DON'T THINK DONORS ARE BEING
HARMED IN THE MAKING OF THE BOOK
SALE AND JUST A FACT, I THINK
THERE IS DEMAND FOR THIS BOOK
AND DONORS DO WANT IT, AND THEY
ENJOY WHAT HE BRINGS TO THE
TABLE AS A TRUMP SURROGATE.
HE TICKS OFF THE RIGHT PEOPLE
AND HE LOVES THAT.
>> THAT IS WHAT CONSERVATISM IS.
>> THAT IS ALL IN FOR THIS
EVENING.
THE RACHEL MADDOW SHOW STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING.
>> I JUST HAD MYSELF BUY THE
BOOK 94,000 TIMES AND CALLED
MYSELF A NONPROFIT.
>> ANYONE UNDERSTANDS THAT IT'S
HARD TO SELL A BOOK, AND THE
PROMOTIONAL PUSH BEHIND PEOPLE
SPENDING A HUNDRED THOUSAND
DOLLARS TO BUY YOUR BOOK HELPS A
LOT.
>> I WOULD SAY YOU AND I HAVE
HAD BOOKS COME OUT THAT HAVE
DONE WELL, QUITE RECENTLY I HAD
ONE, AND WITH THIS DONALD TRUMP
JR. STORY OUT THERE, PEOPLE ARE
GIVING ME THE SIDE EYE.
>> I CAN'T WALK IN MY OFFICE, WE
HAVE SO MANY RACHEL MADDOW BOXES
COVERING EVERY SURFACE, LIKE WE
HAVE TO MEET IN ANOTHER ROOM.
>> I FEEL LIKE, WELL, SO THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY IS BUYING FOR
DON JR., WHO DO YOU THINK IS
BUYING FOR ME, REALLY, YOU THINK
THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY IS BING
FOR CHRIS AND RACHEL.
>> THE PEOPLE ARE THE PEOPLE.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
>> GET IT IN BOOK STORES,
WHEREVER BOOKS ARE SOLD.
IT'S EXCELLENT.
>> I'LL GIVE YOU YOUR KICK BACK
UNDER THE DESK.
THANKS, MAN.
AND THANK YOUS TO YOU AT HOME
FOR JOINING US THIS HOUR.
I HOPE YOU HAD A GOOD HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
I HAD A GREAT HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
I'M DELIGHTED TO BE BACK.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE NOW LOOKING
BACK AT IT, BUT I KID YOU NOT,
IF YOU LOOK BACK IN HISTORY, YOU
WILL CONFIRM THAT TED CRUZ WON
THE FIRST ONE.
YES, THAT TED CRUZ.
HE WON THE FIRST CONTEST IN THE
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY
IN 2016.
HE BARELY WON THE IOWA CAUCUSES.
BUT THEN IN VERY QUICK
SUCCESSION, THE NEXT THREE
CONTESTS WENT TO THE SAME GUY.
AFTER IOWA WAS NEW HAMPSHIRE,
NEW HAMPSHIRE WAS WON BY DONALD
TRUMP, BY A LOT.
THEN THE NEXT ONE UP WAS SOUTH
CAROLINA.
THAT WAS ALSO WON BY DONALD
TRUMP, BY A LOT.
THEN THE NEXT ONE UP WAS NEVADA,
THAT WAS ALSO WON BY DONALD
TRUMP BY A LOT.
BY A MILE.
AND SO, YEAH, YOU LOOK BACK AT
THE HISTORY OF THE PRIMARY, TED
CRUZ DID STRIKE FIRST IN IOWA,
BUT TRUMP BASICALLY STARTED
RUNNING THE TABLE IMMEDIATELY
THEREFORE.
AND OTHER CANDIDATES STARTED
DROPPING OUT OF THE RACE VERY
QUICKLY.
YOU REMEMBER HOW GIGANTIC THE
FIELD WAS.
IT WENT FAST WHEN TRUMP STARTED
WINNING THE PRIMARIES AND
CAUCUSES.
AT THE OUTSET, WHEN HE JOINED
THE RACE, JEB BUSH WAS THE
NOMINEE OF THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
BY ACCLIMATION, THAT WAS THE
BELTWAY LINE.
JEB WOULD LOCK UP THE MONEY AND
ENDORSEMENTS AND RUN AWAY WITH
IT.
JEB BUSH DIDN'T WIN IN NEVADA,
SOUTH CAROLINA, LOST, AND HE
DROPPED OUT AFTER SOUTH CAROLINA
ON FEBRUARY 20th, 2016.
BY LATE FEBRUARY 2016, IN THE
NOMINATING CONTEST THAT YEAR,
CANDIDATE DONALD TRUMP REALLY
WAS JUST RUNNING AWAY WITH THE
PRIMARY.
BUT IT'S INTERESTING.
THE ENDORSEMENTS DIDN'T REALLY
FOLLOW.
I MEAN, EVEN AFTER HE WON NEW
HAMPSHIRE, CAME CLOSE IN IOWA,
THEN HE WON NEW HAMPSHIRE, WON
SOUTH CAROLINA, WON NEVADA AND
IT WAS BY THESE INCREASINGLY
LARGE MARGINS, STILL BY THAT
POINT IN THE RACE, BY FEBRUARY
2016, BY THE TIME HE WON NEVADA,
TRUMP HAD ZERO ENDORSEMENTS FROM
ANY REPUBLICAN SERVING IN
CONGRESS.
NO REPUBLICAN ENDORSED DONALD
TRUMP FOR PRESIDENT UNTIL QUITE
LATE INTO THE PROCESS WHEN HE
WAS ALREADY WAY AHEAD TOWARD
WINNING THE NOMINATION.
THAT MADE IT A BIG DEAL FOR HIM
AND HIS CAMPAIGN WHEN THE FIRST
ENDORSEMENTS FINALLY BELATEDLY
ARRIVED.
IN THE U.S. SENATE, FAMOUSLY,
HIS FIRST ENDORSEMENT CAME FROM
THEN ALABAMA REPUBLICAN SENATOR
JEFF SESSIONS.
THAT LED TO A VERY HIGH PROFILE
ROLE IN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN FOR
SENATOR SESSIONS.
IT LED ULTIMATELY TO HIS
APPOINTMENT, HOWEVER, UNLIKELY,
AS DONALD TRUMP'S FIRST ATTORNEY
GENERAL, WE ALL KNOW HOW THAT
WORKED OUT.
JEFF SESSIONS WILL FOREVER BE
LIKE A SAD CHILDREN'S BOOK FABLE
ABOUT HOW DONALD TRUMP SPELLS
LOYALTY.
THAT'S HOW WE REPAID JEFF
SESSIONS.
BUT EVEN THOUGH THE JEFF
SESSIONS ENDORSEMENT FOR TRUMP
KIND OF LOOMS LARGE IN HISTORY
BECAUSE IT WAS THE FIRST SENATE
ENDORSEMENT AND BECAUSE OF HOW
PEAR SHAPED THAT WENT IN THE
TRUMP SESSIONS RELATIONSHIP,
WASN'T THE FIRST OVERALL FROM
CONGRESS.
CANDIDATE TRUMP'S FIRST
ENDORSEMENTS IN 2016 FROM
REPUBLICANS SERVING IN CONGRESS
CAME A FEW DAYS BEFORE THE
SESSIONS ENDORSEMENT FROM THE
SENATE.
EARLIER THAT SAME WEEK, THE DAY
AFTER TRUMP WON THE NEVADA
CAUCUSES, TRUMP ACTUALLY GOT HIS
FIRST TWO CONGRESSIONAL
ENDORSEMENTS FROM THESE TWO
REPUBLICAN MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE,
ON YOUR LEFT, CHRIS COLLINS,
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN FROM NEW
YORK, ON THE RIGHT, DUNCAN
HUNTER, REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN
FROM CALIFORNIA.
THOSE WERE THE FIRST TWO
REPUBLICAN MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
TO BE WILLING TO GO OUT ON A
LIMB AND GIVE THEIR SUPPORT TO
DONALD TRUMP AS A