THE NEARLY BILLION THAT
CONSUMERS SPENT ON LINE SINCE
THANKSGIVING. AND IT IS ALREADY
LOOKING LIKE A MUCH NEEDED MARY
CHRISTMAS FOR THE RETAIL SECTOR
SO LET'S BRING BACK BAKER
MACHADO AND TIM STENOVIC OVER
THE NEW YORK
STOCK EXCHANGE. 10 OF THE TEAM
IN ADOBE HAS BEEN SENDING OUT
UPDATES SINCE LAST WEEK
TRACKING WHERE PEOPLE
ARE SPENDING HOW THEY'RE
SPENDING AND WHAT THEY'RE
SPENDING IT.
>> AND SO WHAT CAN YOU TELL US
WHY JOE WHAT A JUST A FEW
MONTHS MAKES HIM IN A FEW
MONTHS AGO WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
A RECESSION AND NOW WE'RE
TALKING
ABOUT RIGHT HEARD BREAKING
BLACK FRIDAY RECORD BREAKING
CYBER MONDAY AND A RECORD
BREAKING HOLIDAY SHOPPING
SEASON FOOT
DIVE INTO SOME OF THESE NUMBERS
ARE PRELIMINARY NUMBERS SO BE
SURE TO CHECK BACK BECAUSE
THEY'RE LIKELY GOING TO GET
REVISED AS THE COMPANY GETS
MORE DATA ONLINE SALES OVER
BLACK FRIDAY BROKE A RECORD
NEARLY HALF OF PEOPLE SHOPPED
FROM THEIR PHONES. ADOBE
ESTIMATES THAT THERE'S GOING TO
BE ABOUT A BILLION DOLLARS LEFT
ON THE SHIP ON
THE TABLE BECAUSE OF THE 6
FEWER DAYS BETWEEN THANKSGIVING
AND CHRISTMAS THIS YEAR.
SO DESPITE THAT THE NUMBERS ARE
STILL INCREDIBLY STRONG THEY
REMAIN TO GET TO THAT $1
TRILLION MARK E-COMMERCE
GROWING AT 14% AND THAT IS
FASTER. THE OVERALL RETAIL
SALES SO OVERALL RETAIL SALES
ARE PROJECTED TO GROW AT 4%
E-COMMERCE EXPECTED TO GROW AT
14%
PEOPLE INCREASINGLY SHOPPING
FROM THEIR MOBILE DEVICES AND
AND JUST FROM THEIR DESKTOPS
LET'S TALK A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
WHERE THE BEST DEALS ARE AND
ARE TO BE HAD SO DON'T BE
IS PREDICTING THAT THESE BY
CYBER MONDAY DEALS ARE GOING TO
BE ON TV'S THE SAVINGS OF AN
AVERAGE OF
19% ELECTRONICS OVERALL MIGHT
BE EVEN BETTER THOUGH IF YOU
WAIT UNTIL
AFTER CHRISTMAS. REMEMBER THAT
IT'S NOT JUST BLACK FRIDAY AND
CYBER MONDAY, SOME OF THE BEST
DEALS HAPPEN AFTER THE HOLIDAY
SHOPPING SEASON. IF YOU CAN
ACTUALLY HOLD OUT FOR THAT LONG
AND THEN WE'RE ALSO LIKELY TO
SEE SOME EVEN LAST MINUTE DEALS
ON THE CYBER MONDAY ON
CYBER MONDAY. SO CHECK YOUR
INBOX FOR THOSE BECAUSE WITH
THE REAL TIME DATA THAT
COMPANIES GET FOR WHO'S ON THE
WEBSITE. WHAT PEOPLE ARE BUYING
HIM A CUP
PRICES EVEN FURTHER LATER IN
THE DAY IF THEY SEE THAT THEY
WANT TO ACTUALLY BOOST SALES
MORE. IF YOU MISSED OUT NEVER
FEAR 64% OF PEOPLE ACCORDING TO
ADOBE DON'T FINISH THEIR
SHOPPING. CYBER MONDAY.
SO RETAILERS KNOW THIS SO THE
CHANCES THAT THERE WILL BE SOME
DEALS BACK ON THE TABLE BEFORE
CHRISTMAS GUYS I GOT TO
TELL YOU. I SPENT DAYS LIKE
WEEKS RAILING ON CYBER MONDAY
AND BLACK FRIDAY. I SPEND MORE
MONEY
ON FRIDAY. THE THROUGH LATE
LAST NIGHT THAT I EVER HAVE AND
IT'S
ALWAYS SO.
>> IT IT'S EITHER WAY IF YOU
DIDN'T ADMIT THAT I WAS GOING
TO CALL YOU OUT.
>> AND PRIVATELY AND I WAS
REALLY
WAY OUT SO I I ACTUALLY ENDED
UP FACE TIMING BAKER FROM THE
DRESSING ROOM THAT
A CREW.
>> I HELPED HIM PICK OUT HIS
SUIT WHAT HE WAS GETTING FOR
THIS ISSUE LIKE 50% OFF YOU
KNOW.
>> WE KNEW YOU DID GET
50%.
>> 50% OFF
FOR ABOUT TO SYRIA TO REST OF
US ARE JUST 16%. I GOT TO DO A
SHOUT OUT TO ACTIVE BRAD
YESTERDAY MORNING ATTACK.
BRAD HAS THE COOL ISSUES OUT
ANYONE. SO I SAID BRAD WHAT ARE
THE SCORE ON SHOES, YOU HAVE
YOU SENT HIM TO ME
60% OFF.
>> OUT I WAS SAYING THAT I
AT LEAST 40%
CADA WORKED IS 40 TO 6 LEAD
TIME ASSAULTED OF SUMMER-LIKE
YEARS THE TEAM LEFT. 50 I JUST
I HAVE
TO SAY.
>> BECAUSE I I WAS LIKE I'M NOT
GOING TO BUY ANYTHING IT'S
CONSUMERISM IS TERRIBLE ALL
SUCH A WASTE AND I LIKE YOU
KNOW IT.
>> AND GUYS I BOUGHT A CAR THIS
WEEKEND THAT'S COMING THAT'S
WHAT IT WAS DUMPING THIS WEEK.
>> YOU KNOW IT BY ANYTHING
THIS WEEK.
>> OUT OF FAVOR UP FOR A JOLT.
>> I'M BAKER IT DOES SEEM LIKE
EVERY YEAR THE LINES BETWEEN
BLACK FRIDAY AND
CYBER MONDAY. THERE WERE EVEN
MAKE A LOT OF SENSE CONSIDERING
HOW WE
SHOP RIGHT.
>> WHAT DO YOU GUYS REMEMBER
GUYS I WAS OLD ENOUGH TO
REMEMBER ABOUT BLACK FRIDAY
WHEN WOODS TURNED ON THE
TELEVISION AND THERE WOULD BE
THIS MASS THE AMOUNT OF PEOPLE
RUNNING INTO A BRICK AND MORTAR
LOCATION TRAMPLING ALL OVER
EACH OTHER'S THEY CAN SAVE
$10 ON A BLENDER THAT'S NOT SO
MUCH THE CASE ANYMORE BECAUSE
EVERYTHING SORT OF BLENDING
TOGETHER LOOK AT THIS IS WHAT
BLACK FRIDAY WAS THIS ON FRIDAY
AND THAT'S WHAT WE SAW SOME
GOOD SALES NUMBERS, BUT GUYS WE
DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY GO TO THE
HOSPITAL THIS WEEK AND WE
DIDN'T SEE ANYBODY LIKE LITTLE
O'CLOCK SOMEBODY OVER LIKE THE
LAST TICKLE ME ELMO THAT WAS
OUT THERE BECAUSE EVERY YEAR
GUYS MORE MORE THOSE
DOORBUSTERS BECOME LESS AND
LESS APPEALING OUT THERE THE
WHOLE CHOKE HOLIDAY
SHOPPING SEASON. IT'S REALLY
MERGING INTO JUST ONE OF THAT
IT STARTS RIGHT BEFORE
THANKSGIVING BECAUSE NOW THE
SUDDEN YOU'RE GETTING THOSE
E-MAILS AS TIM MENTIONED EVEN
BEFORE THANKSGIVING THE MONDAY
BEFORE THANKSGIVING ABOUT ALL
OF THOSE DEALS ARE GAY PLUS A
LOT OF THOSE PHYSICAL STORES
LIKE TARGET AND WALMART ARE
OBSESSED WITH THIS BOUGHT THIS
THING THAT'S OUT THERE.
ONLINE WHICH A PICKUP IN STORE
TO CONTINUE 70 MORE INCENTIVES
TO NOT HAVE TO GO IN AND ON A
FRIDAY AT 3 O'CLOCK IN
THE MORNING. BUT GUYS DON'T
FORGET ABOUT HOW CYBER MONDAY
FOR US STARTING WITH ALL OF
THAT IN 2005 WHEN THE NATIONAL
RETAIL FEDERATION COINED THE
TERM BECAUSE THEY WERE SEEING
PEOPLE FRESH OFF THE LONG
WEEKEND OF WINDOW, SHOPPING
WORKERS WOULD GO BACK
TO WORK. THEY WOULD HAVE THIS
AMAZING FAST INTERNET AT WORK
NOT LIKE THE DIAL UP THAT THEY
HAD IN THEIR HOUSE
AND THEN THEY WOULD INSTEAD OF
WORKING THEY WERE JUST BIASED
BUNCH OF STUFF ON MONDAY.
BUT NOW GUYS
TO MENTION. SHOPPERS ARE
SMARTER WE'VE GOT SOME MUCH
THAT NOW THE SEGMENT GOING ON
YOU KNOW GOOGLE AND TAKING IN
EXTORT PROMO CODE TO FIND EVERY
SINGLE AMOUNT OF DISCOUNTS THAT
YOU POSSIBLY CAN IT'S NO
LONGER. THE LUXURY OF GOING
AND STANDING IN LINE AT BEST
BUY 03:30AM IN THE MORNING JUST
TO GET LIKE A RANDOM DVD PLAYER
LIKE IT WAS
AND NOW GUYS IT'S A MARATHON,
IT'S NOT A SPRAY WAIT 10
MINUTES MORE AND YOU'LL GET A
NEW DEAL VISITING THE DEALS
TONIGHT, THOSE THIS AREA
TONIGHT AS TIM MENTIONED
THAT'S BETWEEN 10:00PM AND
02:00AM WHEN THERE'S EVEN MORE
DEALS FOR ALL OF THESE
RETAILERS ARE TRYING TO CLEAR
OUT
EVERYTHING ELSE AND BY THE WAY
64% OF PEOPLE DON'T EVEN
FINISHED THEIR HOLIDAY SHOPPING
SO WHO IS NOT TO SAY IT'S GOING
TO EVEN
MORE DEALS UNLIKE ANOTHER 2
WEEKS OR SO SO THIS IS JUST THE
MASS CRAZY MARATHON INSTEAD
OF THIS ONE DAY SPRINT TO GET
EVERYTHING DONE LIKE IT USED TO
THAT.
>> FOR 01:00AM GLAD THAT THAT
LINING UP AT 03:00AM ON I
LACKED FRIDAY'S NOT TOTALLY
HAPPENING ANYMORE.
>> NO I'M GLAD I'M GLAD THAT'S
GONE BECAUSE MY DAD MAYBE GO
WITH HIM ONE TIME IT WAS LIKE A
100 PEOPLE SLEEPING. THEY'RE
SAYING YOU YOU'VE DONE
THIS YET THIS WAS LIKE BACK IN
THE EARLY 2 THOUSANDS WERE
LITERALLY YOU WILL BE LIKE OH
MY GOD WE'VE GOT TO GET THIS
BLUE RAJA LIKE TENDON AND WE
GOT BIGGER, I THINK MY DAD GOT
LIKE A BLUE RAY PLAYER I THINK
THEY GOT CDS REMEMBER THOSE
THINGS LIKE WHAT YOU WOULD DO
THAT BECAUSE I'M GETTING LIKE
THESE AMAZING DEALS ON IT NOW
YOU JUST LIKE TYPE INTO GOOGLE
AND IT'S AN EVENT.
>> MY FAVORITE IS WHEN BAKER
STARTS ANY SENTENCE THAT I'M
OLD ENOUGH TO REMEMBER THAT
THIS IS A 100 YEARS I MEAN I AM
THE OLDEST MILLENNIALS IT.
I THOUGHT YOUR SEAT HIM IT WHAT
IT IS BUT SOMETHING WAS NOT
HERE. I GLADLY TAKE OVER THAT
ROLE.
ALL RIGHT I HAD A VOICE THAT
ARGUE WITH YOU I THINK THAT
THEY FEEL
THAT WAY NOT SEE BY THE WAY
SINCE THE SEGMENT STARTED I'VE
ALREADY BOUGHT 3 THINGS ALREADY
SO IT'S GOING TO
>> OVER TO ME BECAUSE I I'M
DONE I'M NOT
BUYING IT I GOT A WOMAN IS THAT
OK BAKER 10 BYE BETTER THANK
YOU SO MUCH.
♪
>> WITH MORE ON THIS. LET'S
BRING IN BRADLEY MOSS
NATIONAL SECURITY. PRESIDENT'S
TEAM WON'T PARTICIPATE THIS
WEEK BUT DID NOT RULE OUT
PARTICIPATING IN FUTURE
MEETINGS DOES IN WHAT SCENARIO
DOES THE TRUMP LEGAL TEAM TAKE
PART IN THE IMPEACHMENT
HEARINGS.
>> SURE SO MORE LIKELY THAN NOT
THEY'RE NOT ALL THAT SLOW TO
GET INVOLVED THE SUBSTANTIVE
LEVEL TILL WE GET TO THE SENATE
TRIAL WHEN YOU LOOK AT HOW SOME
PEOPLE HEARING
IT'S THE EQUIVALENT TO YOU KNOW
THINK ABOUT IT IN A NORMAL
COLUMBUS TO SELECT A GRAND JURY
PROCEEDINGS YOU LIVE BUT RATHER
HE PUT IT AND THEY YOU KNOW
CRIMINAL DEFENDANTS. OIL
IS CALLED IT A POLITICAL ISN'T
LARGELY INVOLVED THIS IS ALL
STILL OVER BECAUSE IT'S SO
PUBLIC INTEREST AND THE CONTEXT
OF A
POLITICAL CIRCUS. BUT THE ROLE
OF THE PRESIDENT AND HIS
ATTORNEYS HERE IS ULTIMATELY
WHAT THEY WANT TO MAKE OF IT.
IT'S FUNNY TO SCHOOLS BASED ON
THE RIGHT THAT HAVE BEEN
REPORTED TO THEM BY THE
MAJORITY IN THE HOUSE
OF REPRESENTATIVES, IT'S HOME
HEARINGS IT CAN MOVE TO CERTAIN
WITNESSES. BROUGHT IN TO
PROVIDE WHAT THEY WANT TO STOP
IT OR EVIDENCE OF THE BUGS
HONOREES THE PRESIDENT IF THEY
SO CHOOSE, BUT THE MOMENT THEY
ARE MORE LEVEL THAT
NOTHING ELSE.
>> IF YOU THOUGHT POSSIBLY IN
JUST TRY TO GET THE WILL OF THE
SENATE NOT BE WORRIED ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> BRADLEY NO DOUBT THIS MIGHT
VOTED ON BY PARTY LINES AS PER
THE USUAL LIKE WE SEE
IN WASHINGTON BUT FOR
CONSTITUTIONAL SCHOLARS CHOSEN
BY DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
WILL
SEPARATELY TESTIFY JUST ON THE
STANDARDS OF THE IMPEACHMENT
ON WEDNESDAY. WHAT ARE THEY
LOOKING TO GET OUT OF THAT ONE
MORE THAN LIKELY THEY'RE GOING
TO VOTE BASED ON WHAT THE PARTY
IS TELLING THEM ANYWAY.
>> SO THIS IS BASICALLY THIS IS
THE PROCESS IS IT'S NOT US.
IT'S NOT SEXY WITH THE AIR OF
UNREALITY TOWELS AND WHAT
EVERYDAY NEEDS THERE WAS SOME
BUZZ BUT THIS IS I REPEAT
OF POSSIBILITY WHAT WE NEED A
LEGAL SCHOLARS BRING IN THE
PAST THE SHOW'S DOLLARS TO ITS
LANE. I THAT WAS PUBLISHED JUST
THAT WITH THE COST
TO SOLDIERS, BUT ALSO THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC TO THE EXTENT
THAT THEY'RE WATCHING HOW THIS
WORKS ON WHAT THE CONCEPT OF
THE HIGH PROBLEM IS THE MEDIA
IS IN THE PATH OF THE PEOPLE
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE MOST IS
ALL PART OF PUNISHMENT ONE CAN
MAKE FOR THE PRESIDENT IN ALL
STATES WILL TALK ABOUT A LITTLE
FROM OFFICE AND SO WITH THAT IN
THE HEARINGS. THINK BEING
BROUGHT IN THESE DOLLARS TO
OUTLINE JUST WHAT THIS IS MEANT
TO
LIVE OUT WHAT WAS SUPPOSED TO
BE DEFINED AS THE HIGH FROM A
MISDEMEANOR WHAT DOES AND DOES
NOT BALL FIGHT IN THE ABSTRACT
AND THAT LEADS INTO THAT
THOUGHT OUR WHICH IS WILL THE
NEXT STAGE IN THIS PROCESS.
>> WELL PROBABLY YOU WORK WITH
THE LAWYER WHO REPRESENTED
IMPEACHMENT WHISTLEBLOWER IS
THERE ANY POSSIBILITY THAT WE
ARE GOING TO HEAR FROM THE
WHISTLEBLOWER ABOUT THE
WHISTLEBLOWER WILL TESTIFY.
>> SO THAT'S THE $64,000
QUESTION HERE OF THESE YEARS
WILL THIS PERSON HAVE TO
TESTIFY IN
THE FALL. OBVIOUSLY AS FAR AS
LOOKING AS THE SUN IS NOT
NECESSARY. THE PRESIDENT HAS
DONE AND RAISE THE LAW THERE.
>> WE'LL FOLLOW UP ON ALL OF
THE OFFICES OF ONE OF FULL OF
LIFE ON MORE
AS WELL.
>> SO YOU WANT TO CALL OFF OF
ITS LARGEST COMPANIES IN
THE SUN.
>> ALL THAT BEING STALLED IN
THE SENATE PORTION OF
THIS PROFIT.
>> WHERE WE'RE LIKELY TO HOLD
UP ANY CERTAINLY POSSIBLE
THAT PRESENCE LEGAL TEAM WILL
MAKE THE MOST BEFORE YOU KNOW
KEEP JUSTICE ROBERTS WILL
PRESIDE OVER A TRIAL. HE RULED
THAT TO TOSS THEM, BUT I ALSO
THOUGHT IT WAS SO UPSET WITH
THIS IN TERMS OF WHAT THEY ATE
HER WHEN THEY HEARD
IT FROM AND HOW THEY
COORDINATED ALL SALUTING THEIR
COMPLAINT BROUGHT ON BILLY THE
SABRES SO THAT IS SOMETHING
WE'LL SEE HOW DULL.
>> HOW WOULD HOW WOULD THAT
BOLSTER PRESIDENT TRUMP'S CASE
HOW THAT BOLSTERED REPUBLICANS
TEARS BECAUSE IT WASN'T
FOR SO.
>> SO IT'S NOT SO MUCH ABOUT
THE LEGAL ARGUMENT AS IT IS
ABOUT POLITICAL THE EASING
OF BASICALLY ESPECIALLY FOR THE
GRASSROOTS SO CRITICAL OF THE
PRESIDENT. HE'S NOW TRYING TO
SHORE UP SUPPORT
AMONG SENATE REPUBLICANS IT'S
TRYING TO THROW MUD WALL AND
SEE WHAT STICKS AND SEE IF THEY
CAN TAKE 30 OF THE PERSON WE
BELONG IN THE
FIRST PLACE ABOUT THE LEGAL
STANDARD IN ALL OF THE CASE
THIS IS THE FACT THAT WE'RE NOT
DEAL WITH THEM THE POLITICAL
OF EACH LOTS TO CHEW ASIAN ALL
THE MODELS THE POLITICS NOT A
FACILITY, THE LAW.
>> ACCESS IS JONATHAN SWAN HAD
HIS INTEREST IN COURT LAST
NIGHT ABOUT ONE IF THE TRUMP
LEGAL TEAM MIGHT PARTICIPATE IN
THIS AND THIS MIGHT NOT BE
UNTIL MAYBE THE SENATE GETS
THIS CASE IS THE IDEA BEHIND
THIS THAT THE HOUSE IS MOST
LIKELY GOING TO VOTE FOR
IMPEACHMENT ANYWAY, SO IT
DOESN'T REALLY MATTER OF THE
PRESIDENT TESTIFIES
OR NOT BUT THE BIG SITUATION
WILL BE IN THE SENATE WITH THE
PRESIDENT MOST LIKELY WILL BE
ABLE TO PLEAD HIS CASE MUCH
DIFFERENTLY TO A MUCH LARGER
AUDIENCE.
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY AND ALSO THE
FACT THAT IT IS STILL THE
PRESIDENT'S PARTY HOST CONTROL
THEY WILL SET
THE RULES. YOU KNOW HOW THEY
ALSO USE YOUR TIME TRYING TO
GET SOME OF HIS KEY WILL
MOVE WITNESSES. HE'S HAVING THE
SUPPORT OF THE
MAJORITY PARTY INVOLVED RAN
SUPPOSED TO LEAVE THE HOUSE
REPRESENTATIVES WHERE HE'S
DEALING WITH AN OPPOSITION
PARTY CONTROLLING ALL
THE COMMITTEES. THE CHAIRMAN
HAVE A LOT OF DISCRETION OF
SOLACE IN THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE OF THOSE
HEARINGS BUT HE DID ALL HE NOW
TURN THEM OUT OF THE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE IN A LOT OF
DISCUSSION OF IS THAT THE WORLD
WHO WILL BE A LOT OF ALL OF
THIS IS HOW MOST OF THE FLIGHTS
POSSIBLE QUESTIONS WILL
BE DEPORTED, PLEASANT AND SO
YOU ALSO NOTES THAT THE
PRESIDENT'S LEGAL TEAM FOR THE
MAJOR POLITICAL ARGUMENT AS FAR
AS I'M CONCERNED I WAS A LOCAL
OF BOTH
FLAWED PROCESS. THERE'S NOT A
LOT OF UPSIDE EACH INVOLVED AT
ALL ALL IN THE HOUSE BEFORE SHE
CALL SERVICE ALL THE SAME I
WANT TO BE A NEW LOOK FOR THE
CENTRAL WE THINK
WILL SURVIVE.
>> PROBABLY WILL HAVE ABOUT 40
SECONDS LEFT BUT THAT'S
INCREDIBLY UNLIKELY THAT THE
PRESIDENT WERE REMOVED FROM
OFFICE BY JUST GIVEN THE MAKEUP
OF THE SENATE WAS A WIN LOOKED
LIKE THE DEMOCRATS ARE.
>> THE WIN FOR THE
DEMOCRATS HAAS THE PEOPLE MOST
OF THE OTHER PEOPLE WILL THAT
COST IS NOBODY. NO MATTER WHAT
THE POLLING SHOWED US NO MATTER
WHAT WE WOULD LIKE TO THAT IS
SUCCEEDING WITH REMOVAL IN A
SUBTLE THE WE SAW
YOUR VISIT ALL OF SOCIAL
JUSTICE WE BUILD OUR
CONSTITUTIONAL DUTIES. ALL HE
SAID IT WAS TO ACQUIT PRESIDENT
IS NOT REMOVED THAT GOES TO THE
VOTERS, BUT IT GOES TO THEM
WITH
THE FULL AIRING OF THE RECORD
NOT JUST THE POLITICAL SPIN IN
THE MEDIA OVER.
ON AND UNDER OATH OF THE PUBLIC
HEARINGS OFFICE CRITICAL FOR
THE US.
>> I BRADLEY MOSS NATIONAL
TOURNEY GREAT TO HEAR BRADLEY.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US, THANK
YOU.
♪
>> RIDES ALL THE
>> WELCOME BACK TO CHEDDAR
BUSINESS EVERYONE AS WE WRAP UP
THE LAST MONTH THE YEAR AND
DECADE, WOW
CUP STAR. EMPLOYERS AND
EMPLOYEES ARE HURTING LOOKING
AHEAD TO 2020 JOINING US NOW
ANDREW CHAMBERLAIN THERE IS THE
CHIEF ECONOMIST AT
GLASSDOOR AND YOU RECENTLY
PUBLISHED PREDICTIONS FOR THE
2020 JOB MARKETS, YOUR
PREDICTION FOR FASTEST GROWING
GENERATION IN THE WORKFORCE
NEXT YEAR PROBABLY NOT WHO
PEOPLE WOULD EXPECT SO WHO
>> MOST HIRING HAS FOCUSED ON
GEN Z ARE MILLENNIALS THESE
WORKERS FOR TECH
SKILLS, BUT THE TRUTH IS THE
FASTEST GROWING COHORT IS
SENIORS OVER 65 WORKERS THESE
ARE
BABY BOOMERS STAYING IN THE
WORKFORCE LONGER THEY'RE
HEALTHIER THAN EVER THEY NEED
THAT RETIREMENT INCOME AND I
DON'T THINK MANY EMPLOYERS
TODAY ARE READY TO ATTRACT THEM
OR HAVE
AND CULTURE OF THE WORKPLACE IS
TO KEEP
HAPPIEST WORKERS.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT
CULTURE ANDREW BECAUSE WE HAVE
SEEN BACKLASH OF COMPANIES LIKE
GOOGLE AND FACEBOOK DUE TO
SERIOUS CULTURE PROBLEMS, NOT
JUST HAVING TO DO WITH A GENDER
PAY BUT ALSO WITH TRYING TO
FORM UNIONS AND THOSE PEOPLE
SPECIALLY IN LAST
TO EXPECT EMPLOYERS TO TRY TO
CORRECT THOSE CULTURAL ISSUES
IN THAT HAVE
TO COME TO TRACK TO 10 TALENT
OR IS A SILICON VALLEY, A
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS DOLLARS A
YEAR FREE FOOD ENOUGH TO KEEP
THEM COMING.
>> NO IT'S NOT ENOUGH TO KEEP
THEM COMING FREE FOOD A PING
PONG TABLES AND OUR WORKERS
WANT ALL OF MY RESEARCH SHOWS
THAT PEOPLE
CARE ABOUT WHERE OPPORTUNITIES
THAT THEY'RE LIKE GREAT
LEADERSHIP IN THE AIR ABOUT
HAVING A MISSION
AND VISION THAT MAKES OUR JOB
PART OF THEIR LIFE SO I
DEFINITELY THINK BEYOND TAKIN
TRADITIONAL INDUSTRIES, PEOPLE
ARE FOCUSED MORE THAN EVER ON
CULTURE BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE THE
MOST ASSETS IN KNOWLEDGE BASED
INDUSTRIES TODAY AND NOT
BUILDINGS AND SAW FOR ANYMORE
AND SO I THINK CEOS HAVE A
GROWING REALIZATION YOU CAN
DELIVER GREAT
CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE. YOU CAN'T
REALLY DELIVER GREAT FINANCIAL
RETURNS AND WHAT YOU HAVE
SATISFIED AND ENGAGED WORKERS
WHO LOVE WHAT THEY DO FOR
THEIR JOB.
>> DURING THE MOST RECENT
RECESSION. WE SAW KIND OF 2
THINGS ON THE JOBS FRONT.
IT WAS MARCH CUTS BUT IT
WAS ALSO HIRING FREEZES WELL
PRETTY MUCH IN
EVERY SECTOR. HOW ARE COMPANIES
LOOKING AT THE INCOMING
POTENTIAL RECESSION AND I MEAN
IT'S PART
OF A CYCLE FOR ECONOMICS SO
IT'S GOING TO HAPPEN. IT'S JUST
A MATTER OF WHEN AND HOW DO
THEY START TO BAKE THAT INTO
THEIR OWN FORECASTING AND WHERE
THEY'RE GOING TO EITHER
INCREASE OR STABILIZE HEADCOUNT
AND CERTAIN DIVISIONS.
>> YEAH, THIS LAST DECADE HAS
BEEN A WHIRLWIND FOR TALENT
PROFESSIONALS. THIS DECADE
STARTED WITH ONE OF THE WORST
LABOR MARKET SINCE THE GREAT
DEPRESSION, AND
IT'S ENDED WITH ONE OF THE
STRONGEST LABOR MARKET SINCE
THE 1960'S SO GOING FORWARD
THERE'S DEFINITELY GREATER RISK
OF RECESSION.
NO ONE REALLY KNOWS WHEN THE
NEXT RECESSION IS COMING EXCEPT
WE KNOW FOR SURE IT IS COMING
OUR BEST ADVICE FOR EMPLOYERS
TODAY IS STAY FLEXIBLE.
I DON'T MAKE LONG-TERM
COMMITMENTS UNLESS YOU HAVE TO
TRY TO RELY ON PART-TIME REMOTE
WORKERS GIG WORKERS, WHENEVER
YOU CAN TO TRY TO FILL OUT
PAYROLLS AND ALSO IDENTIFY ARE
HIGH QUALITY HIRING
CHANNELS TODAY BECAUSE WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN DURING A
RECESSION ARE GOING TO BE
FLOODED WITH RESUMES PEOPLE
DESPERATE LOOKING FOR WORK YOU
NEED TO FIND RECRUITING TOOLS
TODAY THAT HELP YOU SORT
THROUGH THOSE CANDIDATES FIND
THE GREAT FITS NOW'S THE TIME
TO GET THAT RIGHT.
>> AND YOU WANT TO ASK ABOUT AI
BECAUSE WHEN WE TALK I HEAR
ABOUT
IT AFFECTED WORKERS. WE
OFTENTIMES HER ABOUT ITS EFFECT
ON BLUE COLLARED ANDREW AD FOR
EXAMPLE PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE,
TALK SO MUCH THE AUTOMATION OF
SO MANY NEW COLOR
JOBS, BUT ONE THING THAT YOU
FOUND IS THAT AI IS ACTUALLY
GOING TO YOU. GET A SEAT IN
UPPER MAN. SO WHAT EXACTLY DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT.
>> SO IT
TURNS OUT IN PRACTICE AI IS NOT
DESTROYING JOBS. IT'S MOSTLY
TEAMING UP WITH WORKERS TO MAKE
THEM
MORE PRODUCTIVE. THE FIRST
GENERATION OF AI
TOOLS WERE LITTLE PRODUCTIVITY
APPS THINGS THAT WOULD SCHEDULE
A MEETING OR YOU OR DO BASIC
CUSTOMER SERVICE ON YOUR
WEBSITE. TODAY THE NEXT
GENERATION OF AI TOOLS IS DOING
MANAGEMENT RELATED TASKS.
THEY'RE MONITORING WORKERS TO
GIVING THEM
REAL TIME FEEDBACK, THEY'RE
COACHING THEM SO TO SPEAK
WHETHER IT'S A SOFTWARE THAT IT
TEACHES YOU TO DRIVE HERE UBS
TRUCK BETTER OR WHETHER IT'S ON
THE SALES FLOOR IN A RETAIL
OPERATION TELLING YOU TO
ASSEMBLE YOUR TEAM'S THE RIGHT
WAY AND WHAT YOU SHOULD DO MORE
OF UNLESS UP TO THE MOST
PRODUCTIVE SO MANAGEMENT AS THE
ONE THAT'S GOING TO BE AFFECTED
BY AI TOOLS IN 2020 AND BEYOND
I DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO
DESTROY A LOT OF JOBS FOR
MANAGERS, BUT I THINK IT'S
GOING CHANGE THE INTERACTION
BETWEEN MANAGERS
AND HIM EMPLOYEES EMPLOYEES ARE
GOING TO SEE AI TOOLS GIVING
THEM ADVICE AND COACHING THEM
MORE AND MORE
AND ALLOWING MANAGERS TO BE
FREED UP TO BE MORE CREATIVE
AND STRATEGIC.
>> WHAT ABOUT INTERNATIONAL
AM IN I THINK WE'VE BEEN
FOCUSING VERY MUCH ON THE US
ECONOMY
AND SURE A LOT OF MAJOR OTHER
ECONOMIES ARE IMPACTED BY THE
OUTPUT HERE FROM THE US SIDE
BUT THEN ADDITIONALLY IF YOU
THINK ABOUT THE UK BRITAIN WAS
STARTING TO GET A REPUTATION AS
A BURGEONING TECH OF RIGHT
BEFORE THIS LITTLE THING CALLED
BREXIT CAME ALONG
HOW DO YOU EXPECT THE UK'S
IMMINENT DEPARTURE FROM THE
EUROPEAN UNION TO CHANGE THAT.
>> WELL NO QUESTION A BREAK
UNCERTAINTY IS ALREADY HURTING
HIRING AND
BUSINESS PROSPECTS IN THE UK.
IT'S A MASSIVE SOURCE OF
UNCERTAINTY AND UNCERTAINTY IS
ALWAYS BAD FOR BUSINESS.
AND WHAT IT IS GOING TO DO IS
IT'S GOING CHANGE THE HIRING
STRATEGIES OF COMPANIES IN THE
UK BECAUSE IF IMMIGRATION
RULES CHANGE AFTER BREXIT YOU
CAN'T NECESSARILY COUNT ON
BEING ABLE TO ATTRACT TECH
TALENT AROUND THE WORLD TO COME
TO LONDON FOR THOSE JOBS.
SO THAT MEANS YOU HAVE TO RELY
MORE ON
REMOTE WORKERS. AND SECONDLY
YOU HAVE TO MOVE POSITIONS TO
PLACES LIKE DUBLIN OR PARIS
THERE ARE ONLY AN HOUR FLIGHT
AWAY
FROM LONDON. THAT WILL REMAIN
IN THE EU THAT WON'T BE SUBJECT
TO IMMIGRATION CHANGES. SO I
DON'T THINK IT'S GOING TO BE A
DISASTER FOR UK EMPLOYERS.
I THINK MOST OF THEM WHETHER IT
JUST FINE, BUT IT'S TOUGH TO
GOING TO CHANGE THE MIX OF
WHERE THEY HIRE REALLY SOUGHT
AFTER TECH TALENT THAT CAN'T
GET TO
LONDON ANYMORE.
>> ENJOY YOUR THOUGHTS ON THE
BIG ECONOMIC NEWS THAT CAME OUT
JUST AFTER 10:00AM EASTERN TIME
HERE THE INSTITUTE FOR SUPPLY
CHAIN MANAGEMENT HAS SOUND
COMING OUT WITH MANUFACTURING
DATA THAT AGAIN FOR THE 4TH
MONTH IN A ROW CAME
IN BELOW 50%
INDICATING THAT MANUFACTURING
IN THE US CONTINUES TO BE IN
RECESSION AS A RESULT YOU SAW
MARKETS HIM FOR
THE EXCHANGE TO DOWNWARD TRIPLE
DIGIT DECLINES RIGHT FOR THE
DOW OFF
OF THAT. WHY WE SEE MANY
FACTORY CONTINUES.
>> IT'S CLEARLY THE TRADE WAR,
IT'S A 100% OF THE TARIFFS.
NO QUESTION I MEAN WHEN YOU
INCREASE THE COST OF GOODS
COMING INTO THE
UNITED STATES. IT'S A TAX THAT
GETS PASSED ON TO CONSUMERS AND
SENSUOUS SAME EFFECT IS RAISING
PRICES AND SO IT HURTS DEMAND
AND IT HURTS MARGINS
OF MANUFACTURERS. SO IN OUR
DATE ON GLASS OR ONE OF THE
BIGGEST
JOB SITE SO WHICH SEE ONLINE
JOB POSTINGS LIKE WE SEE HIRING
ALL OVER THE UNITED STATES AND
WE STILL HAVE CLOSE THIS YOU
5 AND A HALF MILLION OPEN JOBS
IN THE US BUT IN THE
MANUFACTURING SAID AFTER FOR
HIRING ON GLASS OR WE
DEFINITELY HAVE SEEN HOBACK
PRETTY CLEARLY DOCUMENTED
RIGHT APP THE TRADE BILL BUT
AFTER THE SERIES OF STEPS THAT
HAVE ESCALATED THAT THEY WERE
HAVE HAPPENED. SO NO QUESTION
MANUFACTURING IS IN. A
CONTRACTION
RIGHT NOW. THE BIG QUESTION IS
WHETHER THAT WILL REALISTICALLY
SPREAD TO OTHER US SECTORS THAT
BIG SECTORS THE IT AND TODAY
OUR
NOMINEE FRACTURING IT'S HEALTH
CARE, IT'S A PROFESSIONAL
SERVICES AND
FOOD SERVICE JOBS. THOSE THOSE
ARE THE BIG JOBS THAT ARE
HIRING THE AND SO WILL
MANUFACTURING SPILL OVER INTO
HEALTHCARE. I'M NOT SO SURE I
THINK THAT'S WHAT'S REALLY
KEEPING THE ECONOMY MOVING
FORWARD.
>> JUST VERY QUICKLY AND
REPORTED IN 20 SECONDS OR LESS
THE JOBS ECONOMY THAT SIGNALS
TO THE CONSUMER THAT THINGS ARE
STRONG FOR THEM AND THAT THEY
SHOULD
CONTINUE PURCHASING IF THEY
WANT TO OF BUT ULTIMATELY THAT
PLAYS RIGHT INTO A DAY LIKE
TODAY WITH CYBER MONDAY AS WELL
A TIMELY QUESTION I SUPPOSE HOW
DO YOU KIND OF
LOOK AT AND MARY THE DATA
BETWEEN THE JOBS ECONOMY AND
CONSUMER TO TRY AND CREATE YOUR
OWN FORECASTS AROUND THIS
HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> WELL I THINK THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON IS GOING TO BE
RELATIVELY STRONG I THINK WE
STILL HAVE A NEAR A 50 YEAR
UNEMPLOYMENT RATE ON VERY LOW
LAYOFFS, HAPPENING AND EVEN
THOUGH THERE'S SOME UNCERTAINTY
WITH THE CHAOS AND
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT AND
POLITICS AND SOME QUESTION
ABOUT THE TRADE WAR AND
UNCERTAINTY ECONOMY STILL
PRETTY STRONG OVERALL AND
SO IS IT WAS THE LONGEST
EXPANSION EVER IN US HISTORY,
IT'S STILL HAPPENING. I THINK
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO GO OUT
SPEND AS USUAL THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON.
>> ALL RIGHT ANDREW CHAMBERLAIN
WHO IS THE CHIEF ECONOMIST AT
GLASSDOOR THANKS SO MUCH FOR
TAKING TIME TO ATTEND.
>> EVERYONE WELCOME BACK TO
CHEDDAR MOVERS THE FEDERAL
ENERGY
REGULATORY COMMISSION IS AN
INDEPENDENT AGENCY THAT
REGULATES THE INTERSTATE
TRANSMISSION OF ELECTRICITY,
NATURAL GAS
AND OIL AS ENERGY EVOLVES AND
FINDS ITSELF IMPACTED BY
EMERGING TECHNOLOGIES. THE
AGENCY FINDS ITSELF AS A KEY
PART OF ITS FUTURE AND WITH US
NOW TO DISCUSS THIS FOR ENERGY
REGULATORY COMMISSION CHAIRMAN
NEIL
CHEDDAR GENO THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR TAKING TIME FOR THANK YOU
FOR HAVING ME ABSOLUTELY WOULD
SET RIGHT IN THE EXPLAIN TO OUR
VIEWERS. THE FEDERAL ENERGY
REGULATORY COMMISSION'S COURSE
POSSIBILITIES PARTIES HEADING
INTO 20 TALK TO ME OUR TOP
RESPONSIBILITIES, KEEPING THE
LIGHTS ON. WE
ARE THE BETTER IT IS VERY
AGENCY THE RESPONSIBILITY OF
OVERSEEING THE RELIABILITY OF
THE GRID AND I THINK THAT IS
OUR FOREMOST RESPONSIBILITY AND
OBLIGATION. WE
APPLICATIONS FOR ENERGY
INFRASTRUCTURE PROJECTS.
AND OVERSEE THE COMPETITIVE
WHOLESALE ELECTRIC.
>> THERE'S A CRISIS HAPPENING
IN CALIFORNIA WITH A SCHEDULED
POWER OUTAGES THAT EFFECT
MILLIONS AND YES, THE INJURY
THERE EXPECT THIS
TO MAYBE GO ON FOR THE NEXT
DECADE IS THERE ANYTHING THAT
THE REST OF THE COUNTRY CAN DO
THAT FEDERAL BODIES CAN DO.
REINSTATE THE STABILITY OF THE
POWER GRID
IN CALIFORNIA.
>> SO THAT'S A STATE ISSUE AND
THE CPC THERE HAS THAT
CORE RESPONSIBILITY. IT'S
OBVIOUSLY SOMETHING THAT WE ARE
TRACKING LOOK WITH THE
COMMISSION WORK WITH
STAKEHOLDERS ALL AROUND
THE COUNTRY TO ENSURE
THAT WORKED INCENTIVIZING THE
RIGHT INVESTMENTS THAT TO THE
GRID OF THE FUTURE COULD BE
THERE FLEXIBLE RELIABLE GRID.
IT'S
SOMETHING THAT WE WORK HARD
WITH OUR PARTNERS GOT FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT STATE GOVERNMENT
STAKEHOLDERS AROUND THE
COUNTRY. THERE'S LESSONS THAT
CAN BE LEARNED FROM THIS
EXPERIENCE AND JUST TO ADD ON
THIS.
>> AND THE STATE BODIES
ACTUALLY WORKED TOGETHER WHO
WAS THE ULTIMATE SAY, SO THAT'S
AN INTERESTING
LOOK.
>> FIRM BELIEVER IN STATES
RIGHTS AND STATES ABILITIES TO
MAKE DECISIONS ABOUT THEIR
LOCAL ENERGY FUTURES
THAT WE OVERSEE COMPETITIVE
WHOLESALE MARKETS THAT CROSS
STATE LINES.
>> WE'RE SEEING SOME INSTANCES
IN REGIONS OF THE COUNTRY WHERE
STATES ARE TAKING ACTIONS
THAT ARE DISTORTING THE MARKETS
THAT WE OVERSEE AND IN
THOSE INSTANCES AS THAT THE
FEDERAL COMMISSION WOULD NEED
TO INTERVENE TO ENSURE THAT WE
HAVE THE RIGHT PRICE SIGNALS
BEING SENT THE
STARTING HOW MAKE DECISIONS
THAT THEY WANT TO PROP UP OR
SUBSIDIZE A PARTICULAR RESOURCE
IN THEIR STATE. IF THAT SUBSIDY
WINDS UP.
INHIBITING STATE THESE
RESOURCES FROM COMPETING IN THE
MARKET BECAUSE OF THAT THAT
INACCURATE
PRICE SIGNAL THAT MAY REQUIRE
SOME FEDERAL ACTION
IS THAT.
>> MEAN SOME COMPANIES WILL
MOVE TO DIFFERENT STATES OR DO
THEY DO THEY LARGELY STAY IN
THE OWNS THE
OWN STATE THAT THEY OPERATE AND
THEY'VE STARTED TO OPERATE AND
FOR SOME CASES DECADES
OF TIME.
>> ALSO JUST BE CLEAR I'M AT
ABOUT LIKE SPECIFIC, YOU KNOW
COMPANIES THAT I'M A SPECIFIC
RESOURCES. WITHIN THE STATE'S A
LOT OF COMPANIES OPERATE
ACROSS STATE I SOME OF YOU KNOW
WITHIN STATE LINES BUT WHEN
STATES ARE TAKING LEGISLATIVE
ACTION WITHIN THEIR BORDERS
THAT ARE DISTORTING A REGIONAL
MARKET THAT TRAVELS OUTSIDE
THEIR BORDERS THAT
IS SO WE'RE RUNNING INTO THIS
CONUNDRUM. OK I THINK THAT'S A
GOOD THE FIRST ALSO
REVIEW'S PROPOSALS TO
BUILD LIQUEFIED NATURAL GAS WE
SIMPLIFY THIS IS LNG THIS SO
WHAT IS THE IMPORTANCE OF US
LNG EXPORTS IN THE GLOBAL TRADE
COMMISSION AND GLOBAL ENERGY
TRADE YES, LOOK THIS IS A IT'S
A REALLY
EXCITING TIME. IN 2017 US
BECAME A NET EXPORTER OF ENERGY
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 16 YEARS.
THIS HAS POSITIVE ECONOMIC
BENEFITS FOR JOB CREATION
JOB GROWTH AND THE US ECONOMY
AS GEO
POLITICAL IMPLICATIONS, OUR
ALLIES WANT TO DO BUSINESS WITH
THE US AND HAVE AN ALTERNATIVE
TO RUSSIAN GAS IT ALSO HAS A
POSITIVE
ENVIRONMENTAL IMPACT. US CLEAN
LNG DISTORTING MORE CARBON
INTENSE OR SAYS A FUEL AND
OTHER PARTS OF THE WORLD WILL
LEAD TO LOWER
CARBON EMISSIONS IMPACT CARBON
MITIGATION I WANT TO
GO TO.
>> THE SECURITY OF OUR SYSTEMS
AND WE'VE SEEN REPORTS THAT
THERE ARE
MANY FOREIGN ACTORS TRYING TO
INFILTRATE A POWER GRID, HOW
BIG OF A THREAT IS THIS TO OUR
NATIONAL SECURITY.
>> IT'S A NEW REALITY THAT WE
ALL MUST
CONTEND WITH. CYBERSECURITY THE
THE RELIABILITY AND SECURITY OF
OUR ENERGY INFRASTRUCTURE IS
PARAMOUNT. I THINK WE ARE
BENEFITING IN THE ENERGY
TRANSITION FROM TREMENDOUS
TECHNOLOGICAL INNOVATION THAT
INNOVATION COMES WITH A
DOWNSIDE RISK OF THAT IS
INCREASED CYBER VULNERABILITY
AND I THINK
IS IMPORTANT AGENCIES ACROSS
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT STATE
GOVERNMENT THROUGHOUT
THE COUNTRY WORK TO STAY AHEAD
OF OF ALL THE THREATS ARE
ADVERTISED SERIES NOW. AND
THEY'RE CONSTANTLY EVOLVING AND
WE HAVE TO EVOLVE STAY
ONE STEP.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
ON THAT THIS MORNING. THANK YOU
FOR HAVING ME ON SATURDAY IS
THE CHAIRMAN OF THE FEDERAL
ENERGY REGULATORY COMMISSION
RINGING THE OPENING BELL TODAY.
♪
>> HOLIDAY SHOPPING SEASON HAS
BEGUN IN SHOPPERS ARE JUST
LOOKING FOR A GOOD PRICE.
BUT WHETHER BRANDS ARE
SOCIALLY RESPONSIBLE. THE NORTH
FACE IS ONE BRAND THAT'S
RETHINKING THE WAY IT MAKES ITS
PRODUCTS IN GIVING BACK JOINING
US NOW IS EVIL IN OUR CHIEF
MARKETING OFFICER AT
THE NORTH AS STEVE THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR JOINING HOUSE THE
NORTH FACE PRIORITIZING ETHICAL
PRACTICES THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME WELL
TO BE HONEST FOR THE NORTH FACE
IS BEING PART OF THE DNA YOU
KNOW SINCE ITS FOUNDATION IN
THERE
66 BECAUSE THAT COMPANY WAS
ALWAYS FUNNY DON'T LOVE FOR THE
OUTDOORS TO GET MORE PEOPLE TO
ENJOY THE OUTDOORS AND TO ALSO
PROTECT OUR
PLAYGROUND SO
TO HAVE VERY SUSTAINABILITY AND
SUSTAINABLE AND ECO-FRIENDLY
PRODUCT AND IT'S HARD
AND SO THIS HOLIDAY IS IN EVERY
HOLIDAY FRANKLY FOR THE NORTH
FACE IS AN OPPORTUNITY TO
ACTUALLY CONTINUE TO INVITE
MORE PEOPLE TO
GET OUTSIDE TO YOU KNOW, I'D
LOOK UP TO A DROP
THEIR PHONES AND GET OUTSIDE,
BUT ALSO IT'S AN OPPORTUNITY
FOR US TO GIVE BACK TO THE
COMMUNITY AND MAKE A
SUSTAINABILITY STICK STATEMENT
AS WELL AND SO WE'RE EXCITED TO
USE YOU KNOW THIS
PERIOD CONTINUE TO GIVE BACK
THE COMMUNITIES THAT POWER
THE OUTDOORS AND THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE DOING
TO SEIZE.
>> I KNOW STEVE YOU GUYS
LAUNCHED YOUR EGO HERITAGE
COLLECTION THIS FALL, YOU HAVE
A FUTURE LIGHT AND YOUR CLASSIC
DENALI FLEES AS WELL SO TELL US
WHAT THOSE ARE ACTUALLY MADE
OUT OF.
>> YES GREAT QUESTION SO AND
YOU KNOW THE NORTH FACE ALWAYS
BELIEVED THAT IN ORDER TO
PROTECT THE ENVIRONMENT YOU
NEED TO
MAKE PRODUCTS THAT LAST THAT'S
WHERE WE HAVE A YEAR YOU KNOW
LIKE A LIFETIME WARRANTY ON OUR
PRODUCT. THE DENALI WHICH WAS
CREATED SO YOU KNOW THAT THIS
YOU KNOW ICONIC FLEECE YOU KNOW
THE NORTHEAST LAUNCHED SINCE
96. SINCE THE VERY BEGINNING
WAS ALWAYS MADE OF A 100%
RECYCLED CITIES NEEDS TO KNOW
IT CONTINUES TO BE THE KEY YOU
KNOW THE CASE A FEW MONTHS AGO
WE LAUNCHED THIS NEW OUTERWEAR
INNOVATION CALLED
FUTURE LIGHT WHICH IS THE MOST
SUSTAINABLE YOU AGREE THE BOWL.
A WATERPROOF MEMBRANE WE'VE
EVER CREATED AND IT'S MADE OF
YOU KNOW 90% ARE RECYCLED
PRODUCTS, SO IT'S THE MOST
INNOVATIVE REMEMBERING THE
NORTH FACE CREATED, BUT IT'S
ALSO THE MOST SUSTAINABLE SO WE
BELIEVE THAT WE CAN LEAVE
WITH INNOVATION AND
SUSTAINABILITY AND THE SAME
CENTER. WE HAVE A NUMBER OF
OTHER PROJECT THAT SPEAKS TO
THIS COMMITMENT TO
SUSTAINABILITY WE HAVE A
RENEWED COLLECTION. YOU KNOW
THAT COMES FROM ESSENTIALLY
ALL THE YOU KNOW THEY'RE YOU
KNOW I WOULD SAY TO THE DEFECT
AND YOU KNOW
FROM FROM A A
PRODUCTS THAT ARE BEING BUILT
AND WE'RE BUILDING A COLLECTION
FOR ITS OR ESSENTIALLY THREW
THE PUCK REGION FIGHT IN
THE PROCESS. YOU HAVE A LOT OF
SCRAPS OR LEARN THE FACTS A LOT
OF RETURNS AND WERE YOU KNOW
USING OLDIES A MATERIAL IS TO
ACTUALLY ARE AND CREATE NEW
PRODUCTS WE'D LIFETIME TO OFFER
THEM TO CONSUMERS SO WE HAVE A
NUMBER OF THESE YOU KNOW KIND
OF INITIATIVES THAT SPEAKS TO
OUR COMMITMENT TO
SUSTAINABILITY.
>> STEVE YOU ALSO CREATE
ECO-FRIENDLY PRODUCTS THROUGH
REGENERATIVE FARMING SO WHAT IS
THAT.
>> SO A BIG PART OF IT DON'T
YOU THINK ABOUT THE APPAREL
MANUFACTURING INDUSTRY IT'S A
BIG
COAT RIGHT FOR YOU KNOW FOR
CLIMATE CHANGE AND POLLUTION
AND SORT THROUGH EVERY STEP OF
OUR PRODUCT
CREATION PROCESS. WE'RE TRYING
TO BE AS YOU KNOW, YOU LIMIT
OUR COVERAGE FROM PRINT AS MUCH
AS POSSIBLE AND IN SOME
INSTANCES WE'RE TRYING TO ALSO
BE EVEN
POSITIVE IN WHAT WE'RE DOING
THE COUNTY WILL COLLECTION IS A
IS A IS
A COLLECTION OF WORLD THAT IS
BEING DONE IN THE UNITED YOU
KNOW THROUGH THAT YOU
KNOW LIKE CAREFUL THINKING OF
EVERY STEP OF THE PARK CREATION
PROCESS, WE FARMERS TO
ACTUALLY BE NET POSITIVE A YOU
KNOW FOR THE ENVIRONMENT ARE SO
THIS IS YOU KNOW ONE OF THE
EXAMPLE OF THE COLLECTION THAT
YOU'VE
TALKED ABOUT.
>> I THINK YOU ALSO
YOUR CUSTOMERS CHILLS WHERE THE
DONATIONS THAT THEY WANT WHERE
THEY COULD GO WHAT WAS THE
IMPETUS BEHIND ALLOWING THE
CUSTOMER TO MAKE THAT SORT OF A
DECISION.
>> YOU KNOW IT'S IT'S A IT'S A
IT'S REALLY EXCITING TO SEE HOW
ENGAGE IN OUR
COMMUNITY IS CONSUMER REALLY
WANT YOU KNOW
BRANDS TO LIVE UP TO WHAT YOU
KNOW TO VALUES THAT THE
CONNECTU IT'S OBVIOUSLY WHEN
YOU WORK FOR YOU KNOWING THE
OUTDOOR ENVIRONMENT. YOU KNOW
THE NORTHEAST WE LOVE WHILE
PLACES WE LOVE YOU KNOW GETTING
MORE PEOPLE OUTSIDE AND OUR
COMMUNITIES DURING GAUGED
AS TO THE ONLY AREAS THAT THEY
WANT TO KNOW SPACE TO
PARTICIPATE AND MORE IN
AND SO IN IN WORKING WITH
OUR COMMUNITIES. THEY WERE VERY
VOCAL IN SAYING THAT THEY WOULD
LIKE TO HAVE A POINT OF VIEW ON
WHERE YOU KNOW THE FUNDS THE
EXPLORE FUNDS WOULD GO
TO IMPACT THEIR LOCAL MARKETS
AND KNOTS THAT WAS BASICALLY
THE DESIGN LISTENING TO OUR
NEW COMMUNITY TO ACTUALLY GIVE
THEM THE OPPORTUNITY TO DECIDE
WHERE THE FUNDS THAT WE WILL
COLLECT THIS HOLIDAY
WILL GO TO
TO IMPACT THEIR COMMUNITIES AND
THE BEST WAYS IN THESE 3
DIFFERENT YOU FOUNDATIONS THAT
CAN CHOOSE FROM
THE NATIONAL PARKS FOUNDATION'S
THE GIRL SCOUTS OF AMERICA HAS
AND THE TRUST FOR PUBLIC LANDS.
ALL YOU DOING INCREDIBLE WORK
TO GET PEOPLE OUTSIDE AND TO
PROTECT OUR PLAYGROUND
AS WELL.
>> SEE WE MENTION THAT PEOPLE
ARE SHOPPING THIS HOLIDAY
SEASON LOOKING FOR GOOD DEALS
BUT I THINK MILLENNIALS AND GEN
Z IN PARTICULAR REALLY HOPING
TO SHOW THAT THEY CARE ABOUT
CERTAIN CAUSES WHEN THEY USE
THEIR MONEY AND WHEREVER
THEY'RE SPENDING SO
WHAT DO YOU HOPE THE NORTH FACE
CONVEYS WHEN WHEN PEOPLE SEE
SOMEONE OUT ON THE STREET
WEARING A NORTH FACE PARKA.
>> YOU KNOW FOR US OUR
HOPE IS THE NORTH FACE IS IS
HAS ALWAYS BEEN ABOUT
EXPLORATION. IT'S
ABOUT ENABLING. CONSUMERS AND
NEIGHBORING ATHLETES TO GET
OUTSIDE INTO THE ENJOY THE
OUTDOORS SOMETIMES IN THE
HARSHEST CONDITIONS FOR
OPENNESS TO AND MOUNTAINEERS
BUT FRANKLY WE WANT YOU KNOW WE
WANT YOU KNOW THE NEXT
GENERATION OF WHAT WE CALL
EXPLORES OF CONSUMERS TO GET
OUT. AND ENJOY THE OUTDOORS BUT
WE ALSO WANT CONSUMERS TO KNOW
THAT WE DO THAT IN A WAY THAT
WILL RESPECT NOT ONLY OUR
PLANET. BUT ALSO THAT WILL
UPHOLD ON THE HIGHEST A YOU
LEVELS OF SUSTAINABILITY BUT
ALSO YOUR ABILITY AND QUALITY
OUR ATHLETES USE OUR PRODUCT IN
THE HARSHEST CONDITIONS,
SOMETIMES IT'S A MATTER OF LIFE
AND DEATH
IN TERMS OF TRYING TO RIDE YEAR
FOR THEM, SO WE WANT CONSUMERS
TO KNOW THAT IT'S ABOUT
QUALITY. IT'S ABOUT YOU KNOW
PASSION FOR THE OUTDOORS IT'S
ABOUT INVESTING IN OUR FUTURE
TO PROTECT THE ENVIRONMENT.
>> THAT CEILING OUR CHIEF
MARKETING OFFICER AT THE NORTH
BAY. THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
JOINING US.
>> THE HOUSE FLOWER SHOPPERS
BECOME ONE OF THE MOST
INSTAGRAMMABLE BAKERIES OUT
THERE PROBABLY SEEN THIS ON
YOUR FEET LOOK AT THAT CAKE
LOOKS DELICIOUS THAT'S THE
FAMOUS RAINBOW EXPLOSION CAKE
WELL THE BAKERY HAS NOW TURNED
INTO A WELL KNOWN BRAND IS
NOW MAKING IT'S WAY THE SHELVES
A BIG RETAIL STORES LIKE
WILLIAMS SONOMA
AND EVEN POTTERY PART SO HERE
WITH MORE IS A MERE A CASE OF
SHE IS AUTHOR AND FOUNDER OF
FLOWER SHOP AND THEY ARE GREAT
TO HAVE YOU HERE
THANK YOU.
>> FOR HAVING SEX WITH YOUR
SHIRT SO MUCH COLORING THAT'S
THE INSIDE OF YOUR CAKE SAME TO
YOU RAY. I KNOW YOUR NAME BUT
SUS
IS THIS GLITTERY
>> HAPPENING FOR YOU GUYS, BUT
IT'S MODELED COLLABORATING WITH
WILLIAMS SONOMA AND YOU GUYS
DECIDE THAT YOU WANTED TO
LAUNCH A HOLIDAY EXPLOSION CAKE
KIT NOT JUST THE CAKE. THE
CAMP. ACTUALLY WE LAUNCHED WITH
WILLIAMS SONOMA THE SUMMER AND
IT WAS JUST SUCH A HUGE SUCCESS
WAS THE CAN WAS SO ABOUT
EVERYWHERE THEY HAVE A 200
SOMETHING STORES AND
IT WAS JUST THE THING THAT
EVERYONE TO DO AND SO I WAS
THINKING YOU KNOW GINGERBREAD
HOUSES ARE ONE OF MY FAVORITE
THINGS TO DO OVER
THE HOLIDAYS. BUT THEN YOU
CAN'T REALLY EAT IT RATED SUV'S
OUT FOR A LONG TIME AND SO I
WANTED TO COME UP WITH AN
ACTIVITY IN THE CAKE KIT FOR
CHRISTMAS IS SO
PERFECT BECAUSE IT'S SO FUN YOU
CAN DO WITH THE WHOLE FAMILY.
IT'S LIKE STEP-BY-STEP
EVERYTHING'S IN THERE YOU JUST
NEED THE DAIRY AND
THEN IT'S OSHA'S TO LOOK AT
THAT BECOMES LIKE A PAY 10 OH
YEAH, I THINK IT'S LIKE FULL
ACTIVITY IN MY MIND IS LIKE
CRABS TIME THAT YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO SEE SO MANY VIDEOS
LIKE ACROSS SOCIAL MEDIA OF THE
CAKES
JUST BEINGS.
>> BILL FILLING OUT THE
WRINKLES
EVERYWHERE ELSE THE VERY THING
I LOVE SEEING HOW PEOPLE TAKE
THE KIDS ARE TRANSFORM IT INTO
WHATEVER CREATIVITY THAT THEY
HAVE BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE
EVERYONE HAS THEIR OWN TWIST ON
IT.
>> OK SO IN ADDITION TO THAT
YOU GUYS ARE ALSO LAUNCHING AN
EXCLUSIVE HOME DECOR LINE WITH
POTTERY BARN, A YEAH WELL SO
TELL US WHAT WAS THE IMPETUS
BEHIND GETTING INTO
THAT AREA.
>> SO HOW DO YOU WANT KIDS
ACTUALLY IS WHERE WE STARTED
BUT THE COLLECTION WAS SO FUN
THAT WE EXTENDED IT SO TODAY WE
ANNOUNCE WORD DROPPING
THE COLLECTION DECEMBER 12TH
WHICH ARE VERY EXCITED ABOUT
AND IT'S POTTERY BARN POTTERY
BARN KIDS AND PARTY
RUN TEEN. SO MY FEAR IS THAT
EVERYONE IN ALL AGES SHOULD
LIVE A RAINBOW LIVES.
>> I HAPPEN TO LIKE US AND WE
STARTED DOING IT BECAUSE I'M
THAT'S HOW I SAY LIVEESTYLE ANDW
AND TO ME THAT'S ON YOUR
BIRTHDAY YOU WAKE UP YOU A
FAVOR CLOTHES, YOU YOUR
FAVORITE FOOD TO HAND THEIR
FAVORITE PEOPLE AND LIKE ALL
DAY
EVER BUT YOU CREATED ALL OF
THAT RIGHT. SO IF YOU CAN DO IT
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY YOU CAN DO
THAT YOU'RE AROUND SO ON
TO CREATE A SPACE WHERE YOU
CREATE YOUR OWN HAPPINESS AND
LIVE IN THIS LIKE RAINBOW
AND OF. DREAMS OF THE UNICORN
THOSE AND SMILEY'S IN GLITTER
DOES ALL THE FUN THAT SOUNDS
AMAZING YOU'VE BEEN SO BUSY
THAT ALSO BRINGS US YOUR SECOND
BOOK WHICH IS THE MAGICAL LAND
OF BIRTHDAYS THAT.
>> BE KIND OF JUST LIKE BUILT
UNDER ALL OF YOUR DIFFERENT
PRADA.
>> THE MAGICAL AND BIRTHDAYS A
CHILDREN'S BOOK THAT YOU KNOW 6
TO 11 YEAR OLDS
BUT REALLY THAT'S THE LEVEL
THAT I READ BUT IT'S AMAZING
BECAUSE
IT REALLY TAKES YOU THROUGH THE
UNDERSTANDING THAT NO MATTER
WHERE FROM THE WORLD OR WHAT
YOU BELIEVE IN. WE ALL SHARE
A BIRTHDAY AND THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT MAKES US ALL HUMAN AND
THAT IT'S REALLY COOL TO
EXPLAIN IT THROUGH A CHILDREN'S
STORY, THE MAGIC A LAND WHERE
YOU FIND YOUR BE BUDS AND YOUR
BE BUDS ARE REALLY JUST THIS
PEOPLE BORN ON THE SAME DAY AS
YOU. SO I HAVE LIKE ELVIS
PRESLEY AND DAVID BOWIE WAY
THOUGH.
I HAVE AMAZING ONES SO THIS
BOOK THEY JUST WANT TO WRITE IT
SO THE KIDS COULD SORT OF
CONNECT WITH KIDS AROUND THE
WORLD BY UNDERSTANDING THAT
THEY'RE
ALL BORN.
>> ON THE SAME DAY AS SOMEONE
ELSE SO LET'S GET BACK TO THE
CAKE FOR A
ON THE ICE SOMEONE'S WAS ONE OF
THE MOST LIKELY THEIR INSTAGRAM
AND THIS WAS LIKE A VIRAL
SENSATION. WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
IT ABOUT THIS THAT MADE IT SUCH
A SENSATION OVERNIGHT.
>> I THINK THAT IT'S
THE LYRICS BLOATING HAPPINESS
RIGHT LIKE YOU THINK ABOUT IT
AND YOU SEE USE CAKE
AND IT'S COVERED IN THOUSANDS
OF SPRINKLES ON THE OUTSIDE YOU
ALREADY ARE JUDGING IT BY ITS
COVER AND GOOD. YOU CUT IT OPEN
AND
IT'S LIKE ALL THESE PRINGLES
COMING OUT AND THEN ON TOP OF
IT IS 6 LAYERS OF RAINBOW CAKE
AND IT'S
>> ON THE IT'S ALL
FOR US.
>> THEY EVEN ARE CRAZY ONES
FROM MY FIRST BOOK AND HAS BEEN
GOES WITH CHARLIE BURGERS AND
POPCORN AND SPAGHETTI IT'S
SHOWING HOW TO DO EVERYTHING
WITHOUT FUND IT BUT I THINK
THAT THAT
SORT OF KENYADA VIBE TO IT I
MEAN I GREW UP IN MEXICO CITY
ON HIS WERE HUGE FROM AND THAT
MOMENT WHEN YOU BREAK IT OPEN.
THERE WAS NO INSTAGRAM WHEN I
WAS GROWING UP.
>> IF THERE WAS BE
NOT AS WORRIED AS THING THAT
EVERYONE'S TRYING TO
>> AND I THINK ONCE YOU GET
OLDER YOU JUST GO TO A
RESTAURANT WHERE YOU JUST CUT
THE CAKE AND YOU LOSE
THE PINATA ELEMENT TO IT AND
THIS IS SORT OF A WAY TO BRING
IT TO A RESTAURANT, YOUR OWN
PAY OUT AT
THE TABLE AND I WANT TO TALK
JUST LIKE VERY BRIEFLY ABOUT
YOUR UPBRINGING BECAUSE KELLY
YOU MENTIONED YOUR FROM MEXICO,
YOU STARTED OUT IN THE FASHION
WORLD AND THEN STARTED MAKING
CAKE POP.
THAT'S HOW YEAH I WAS READING
CAN HOUSE WAS AS MAKING CAKES
ACTUALLY
FOR DEFERRED PEOPLE AT WORK
WHEN IT WAS THEIR BIRTHDAY AND
PEOPLE WOULD ASK ME IF
THEY COULD BORDERLINE HAS KIND
OF THINK MOST OF THAT'S NOT
WHAT I DO FOR A LIVING AND I
NEVER THOUGHT OF BAKING OR JUST
PLAYING WITH SPRINKLES FOR A
LIVING UNTIL MORE MORE PEOPLE
STARTED TO ASK ME AND I WOULD
WAKE UP BEFORE GOING TO WORK TO
DO AND SO I TURNED MY SIDE
HUSTLE INTO MY REAL
OF US.
>> WHAT YOU ALREADY HAVE ONE
SHOP OPEN YOUR I READ THAT
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE A SECOND
ONE YOU HAVEN'T ANNOUNCED YET
AS
FOR IT. WHAT DID YOU LEARN FROM
THE FIRST LOCATION THAT YOU
WANT THAT YOU'LL DO MAYBE
DIFFERENTLY WITH THE
SECOND ONE.
>> I WOULD BE BASICALLY THE
SAME IT WILL BE VERY SIMILAR
BUT I FIND THAT AS SOMEONE WHO
DIDN'T
GROW UP SORT OF GOING TO CALL
AN AREA SCHOOL OR WORKING AT
DIFFERENT BAKERIES. I LEARNED
SO MUCH BY THE PEOPLE THAT
SURROUND ME AT WORK AND SO
HIRING PEOPLE WHO ARE
PASSIONATE IN ARE WILLING TO
LEARN FROM ME, BUT ALSO I
LEARNED FROM THEM SO MUCH SO
I THINK BUT THAT'S ALWAYS
KEEPING AN OPEN MIND THAT
CREATIVITY CAN COME FROM
ANYWHERE AND IT'S REALLY
EXCITING TO BOUNCE IDEAS OFF OF
DIFFERENT PEOPLE SO I'M EXCITED
TO GET
A WHOLE NEW TEAM AND HAVE SORT
OF 2 TEENS TALKING TO A
DOZEN VILLAGES.
>> AND CONGRATULATIONS ON
EVERYTHING YOU'VE ACHIEVED ALL
THESE DIFFERENT PROJECTS YOU'VE
TAKEN ON I HAVE TO ASK THOUGH
BECAUSE YOUR K
LIKE AT THE FOREFRONT OF THE
SOCIAL MEDIA SENSATIONS AS IT
RELATES TO FOOD. HOW DO YOU
KIND OF STAY RELEVANT OR IS
THAT SOMETHING YOU EVEN THINK
ABOUT
IT TODAY TO BE HONEST WITH YOU
IT'S SOMETHING THAT COMES UP A
LOT AND I DON'T THINK OF ANY
SPECIFIC
THING ALIKE WILL THIS BE
RELEVANT OR IS THIS GOING TO
GET THE LIKES OR NOT WHAT I
FIND IS
THAT WHATEVER MAKES ME REALLY
HAPPY WHEN I SEE IT IS
ORGANICALLY WHAT'S GOING MAKE
SOMEONE ELSE HAPPY WAS ALREADY
FOLLOWING US OR WANTS TO SEE A
NEW HAPPY ACCOUNT AND SO
WHETHER IT'S LIKE A SILLY
BOOMERANG
OF SPRING OR YOU KNOW THE NEXT
CAKES THAT WE HAVE COMING OUT
OF BEEN WORKING ON THIS GOLD
BAR FOR A
IT TAKES A WHILE TO HUDDLE
TOGETHER BUT I THINK THE WHAT'S
GOING MAKE ME HAPPY WELL WHAT I
WANT TO BRING TO SOMEONE'S
OF THAT WHAT WOULD I FEEL SO
EXCITED TO SHARE AND SHOW TO A
CHILD FOR THE FIRST TIME AND
I THINK THAT'S REALLY WHAT
MAKES IT MORE EXCITING TO ME
THAN RELEVANCY BECAUSE I THINK
THAT ANYTHING CAN BE RELEVANT
AT ANY TIME IT MAKES YOU HAPPY.
>> SO WHAT ARE WHAT A VALID
POINT I'M SOME SHE'S AUTHOR AND
FOUNDER OF FLOWER SHOP GREAT TO
HAVE YOU HERE HER BOOK OF
COURSE THE MAGICAL LAND OF
BIRTHDAYS. NOW THANKS AGAIN.
THANK YOU.
>> WELCOME BACK TO CHEDDAR
SHAKERS EVERYONE WILL FOLLOWING
WE WORK'S FAILED ATTEMPT TO GO
PUBLIC AND ITS DRAMATIC DROP IN
VALUATION PRESSURE IS MOUNTING
FROM LIKE SOFT BACK FOR MORE ON
THIS WE'RE JOINED BY DAVID
SPRANG THE CEO AND FOUNDER OF
THE VENTURE CAPITAL FIRM RUNWAY
GROWTH CAPITAL DAVID SO GOOD TO
HAVE YOU BACK
ON CHEDDAR ONE TOP 2020 GIVEN
WHAT WE SAW IN 20 MONTHS.
WE
WORK'S FAILURE. A DRAMATIC DROP
IN VALUATION FOR RIVER FOR LIVE
THE COMPANY IS SERIOUSLY OFF
THEIR
IPO PRICES. DO YOU THINK WE'RE
GOING TO SEE A DECLINE OF
VENTURE CAPITAL FUNDING IN
2020.
>> VENTURE CAPITAL FUNDING, NO
I THINK WILL CONTINUE TO SEE A
RISE IN VENTURE CAPITAL FUNDING
THEIR EYE ON THE
DRIVE OUT. THERE'S A LOT OF
MONEY IN THE SYSTEM AND
INNOVATION CONTINUES AND IPOS
HAVE
NEVER BEN THE BIGGEST EXIT FOR
VC SOME YOU HAD SOME
VERY VERY HIGH PROFILE IPOS
SOME OF WHICH HAVE DONE WELL
SOME AS YOU MENTIONED HAVEN'T
DONE AS WELL, BUT IT'S
CERTAINLY NOT GOING STOP
INVESTMENT.
>> THE RIGHT MEASURE THAT OF A
SUCCESSFUL EXIT.
>> THE SEAS AND MAYBE WE SHOULD
JUST TALK A LITTLE BIT ABOUT
THE VENTURE MINDSET BECAUSE IT
IS A HIT
BUSINESS. SO YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT
IN STATISTICS, A NORMAL
DISTRIBUTION. THE BELL CURVE
THAT WE ONLY STUDIED AND
STATISTICS WELL, VENTURE
CAPITAL WORLD FOLLOWS A POWER
LAW DISTRIBUTION WHERE ALL OF
THE RETURN ARE IN A VERY VERY
SMALL NUMBER
OF DEALS AND THE VENTURE WORLD
THAT HOLDS TRUE VIRTUALLY A
100% OF RETURNS IN THE VENTURE
INDUSTRY COME FROM ONLY 2 AND A
HALF PERCENT OF THE INVESTMENT,
SO YOU CAN IMAGINE
BC'S REALIZE IT'S A HOME RUN,
NOT EVEN A HOME RUN A GRAND
SLAM DUNK. SO EVERYBODY IS
TRYING TO
TAKE IT THE RUN AND YOU KNOW I
COUNTED THERE'S BEEN A BOAT A
25 BILLION PLUS EXITS OVER THE
LAST DECADE
20 OF THOSE WERE FROM IPOS AND
5 ARE FROM EVAN, A SO THERE'S A
VERY VERY SMALL NUMBER OF DEALS
THAT ARE DRIVING ALL THE RETURN
AND THOSE ARE CONCENTRATED WITH
A VERY SMALL NUMBER
OF ENTRIES.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE
RESPONSIBILITY OF THE VENTURE
FIRMS THEMSELVES. PROPERLY
VALUE COMPANIES REMAIN IN THE
CASE OF SOFTBANK IT SEEMS LIKE
THERE HAVE BEEN A SERIES OF
THEIR INVESTMENTS THAT WHEN
THEY INVESTED AT THE VERY WHEN
IT CAME DOWN TO.
THE EXIT THE VALUATIONS
WERE CRUSHED LOWER THAN WHAT
THEY HAD ABOUT WHAT THEY HAD
INVESTED IN AT THAT VALUATION.
>> SO THERE'S NO REAL INCENTIVE
FOR A VENTURE FIRM
TO HIM LATE THE VALUE OTHER
THAN IF THEY'RE MARKETING TO
RAISE A NEW FUND AND AT THE END
OF THE DAY IT'S REALLY JUDGED
BY RESULTS SO LIMITED PARTNERS,
THE INVESTORS IN VENTURE FIRMS
ARE LOOKING TO GET 3 TIMES
THEIR MONEY ON AN INVESTMENT IN
HIGH QUALITY MEANT
TO FUND THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN
VERY OFTEN ONLY 5% OF THE
TIME BUT IT'S BASED ON PURE
CASH AND CASH O SO WHAT THE
INTERIM VALUES ARE THERE'S NOT
A LOT OF ATTENTION PAID
TO THAT OTHER THAN ONE EURO
TRYING TO MARKET IF AND
THEREFORE FOR SOFTBANK TRYING
TO MARKET YOU KNOW THE SECOND
FUND THAT IT'S A CHALLENGE TO
HAVE THESE BIG RIGHT TO
OFTENTIMES WE TALK ABOUT THE
COP WE TALK ABOUT THE SEAS
TAKING A PIECE OF.
>> GIVING MONEY TO THE COMPANY
FOR FUN OF THE COMPANY, BUT
WHAT YOU DO IT FROM A GROWTH IS
A LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT WITH
WITH VENTURE DEBT WE TALK ABOUT
EXTENDING THE RUNWAY AS FOR
THESS.COMPANIES. YES, WHAT
>> YES SO WHAT WE'RE DOING IS
WE'RE OFFERING TO LEND MONEY
HAS IT ALL TURN TO YOUR
COMPLIMENT
TO EQUITY FOR COMPANIES THAT
AREN'T THE ONES THAT GET TALKED
ABOUT ON THE SHOW NOT THE
UNICORNS BECAUSE THEY CAN GET
MONEY EASILY. BUT THERE'S A
HUGE IMBALANCE IN THE VENTURE
CAPITAL WORLD AND MAYBE JUST TO
TALK ABOUT THAT FOR A SECOND
AND THEN WE'LL TALK ABOUT HOW
RUNWAY HELPS ADDRESS THAT.
BUT EVERY YEAR THERE'S ABOUT
2500 COMPANIES THAT TAKE
VENTURE CAP FOR THE FIRST TIME
SO 2500 COMING INTO THE SYSTEM
AND ONLY A 1000 THAT ARE GOING
OUT AND WE TALK A LOT ABOUT THE
IPOS THAT THAT IS IT TINY
TINY THING OVER THE LAST 5
YEARS IT'S ONLY BEEN ON
AVERAGE 7 MENTOR BACKFIELD SO
IT'S A TINY THING SO WE'RE
LEAVING
1500 COMPANIES THAT ARE KIND
OF ORPHANED WHERE THEY DON'T
GET THE ATTENTION OF EVEN A LOT
OF THEIR EARLY BACKERS BECAUSE
THEY'RE PUTTING THEIR DRY
POWDER INTO THE HOME RUNS AND
THAT LEAVES THESE OTHER
COMPANIES KIND OF TO START THE
RIVER FORTH AND
FOR THEMSELVES AND THAT'S WHERE
WE CAN COME IN AND PLAY A ROLE
IN FUNDING THEM BY LENDING THEM
MONEY INSTEAD OF AKRON.
SO QUICK EXAMPLE IF YOU'VE GOT
A COMPANY IS VALUED AT A $100
MILLION TODAY. AND YOU NEED TO
RAISE
20 MILLION. IF YOU DO THAT AN
EQUITY YOU'RE GOING TO GIVE UP
OVER 16% OF YOUR COMPANY IF YOU
COME TO US AND TAKE THE 20%.
WE'LL GET A LITTLE BIT OF
EQUITY BUT IT WILL BE LESS THAN
ONE PERCENT AND IF YOU'RE
100 MILLION COMPANY BECOMES A
BILLION
DOLLAR COMPANY WITH ALL THE EYE
ALL THE ENTREPRENEURS THINK
THAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN.
AND YOU GAVE AWAY A 165 MILLION
EXTRA DOLLARS THAT YOU DIDN'T
HAVE TO AND SO FOR REALLY
LATE-STAGE COMPANIES THAT ARE
AT A POINT WHERE THEY CAN START
TO USE LEVERAGE. IT'S BECOMING
MORE AND MORE ABOUT THAT.
>> THE RATE CUTS THIS YEAR LOW
INTEREST RATE ENVIRONMENT IS
GOOD FOR
YOUR BUCK THIS IS AND HOW SO
WELL IT IT MAKES THE COST OF
DEBT EVEN LESS YOU KNOW
ON-TREND IT'S ALWAYS BEEN THE
CASE THAT.
>> THE DEBT IS CHEAPER EQUITY
BUT IN A LOW INTEREST RATE
ENVIRONMENT THAT'S EVEN MORE.
RIGHT AND SO FOR NEXT YEAR.
>> THAT HAS NOT SIGNALED THAT
THEY WILL CONTINUE BUT AT THE
FORECAST ANYTHING FOR YOU ON
>> WELL SO WE SEE RATES
CONTINUING TO DECLINED A YOU
KNOW I DON'T OFTEN GET TO A 0
RATE ENVIRONMENT IN THE US, BUT
WE CERTAINLY DON'T SEE RATES
GOING IN THE
NEAR FUTURE.
>> WHAT HE SEES MAIN AREAS OF
INNOVATION IN 2020.
>> WELL, SO I THINK AI IS GOING
TO CONTINUE TO BE A
AREA OF OF INVESTMENT I THINK
FOOD TECH WILL
BE A ANOTHER BIG AREA THAT WILL
CONTINUE TO SAY CURRY TALKING
BEYOND THE IMPOSSIBLE FOR BUT
ACROSS THE WHOLE THING. AND
THEN YOU KNOW IN COLLECT.
PRACTICAL BLOCK CHAIN WHICH
COULD HAVE APPLICATION IN
SUPPLY CHAIN MANAGEMENT WHICH
COULD BE USED IN THE FOOD
SUPPLY OR OTHER PLACES AND I
HUMAN AUGMENTATION IS GONE THE
ANOTHER AREA THAT'S GOING TO
START
TO GET MORE ATTENTION SO
IMAGINE A WORKER
IN THE AMAZON WAREHOUSE THAT
COULD HAVE THEIR BODY
PHYSICALLY
AUGMENTED TO MAKE IT EASIER ON
THEM TO DO WHATEVER TOUR HELPS
SO NOT SURGICALLY.
I'VE NOT YET BUT THAT'S
THAT'S COME THAT IS COMING UP A
LITTLE RIGHT SO WHAT DO YOU
WHAT DO YOU HAVE
IN MIND. WELL SO WE'RE REALLY
NOT THE GUYS THAT ARE OUT THERE
MAKING THOSE CUTTING EDGE
INVESTMENTS BECAUSE WE DO
LATE STAGE LOANS. SO YOU KNOW
THAT I USED TO BE AN EARLY
STAGE, THE SCENE THAT WAS MY
JOB NOW I'VE GOT AN EASIER ONE
WAGES, WAIT FOR GREAT
ENTREPRENEURS AND GREAT FECES
BILL BUSINESSES TO THE POINT
THAT THEY CAN USE DEBT AND THEN
WE COME IN, BUT WE TRY TO YOU
KNOW KIND OF SEE AHEAD IN
I THINK THE AREAS THAT I
MENTIONED WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO RECEIVE A LOT OF
FUNDING IN 2020.
>> LASTLY I'M REALLY QUICKLY
HERE.
CHANGE THE WAY THEY OPERATE
BASED ON WHAT FACEBOOK GOOGLE
AND.
A FACE TO THE REGULATORY
SCHEME.
>> YES,
DEFINITELY PRIVACY IS A BIG
ELEMENT OF CONSIDERATION FOR
EVERY INVESTMENT THAT I THINK
ANY ANYBODY THAT.
>> ALL RIGHT DAVID THANKS SO
MUCH FOR BEING ON THE TODAY,
THANK YOU DAVID STRANG IS CEO
AND FOUNDER OF THE SEA RUNWAY
GROWTH.
>> WANT TO CONTINUE FOR
WEEKEND. WE ARE AWAITING
COMMENTS FROM PRESIDENT DONALD
TRUMP THIS MORNING I BELIEVE
THAT IT HAPPENED DURING THE
TESTING OF THE I
♪
A
COMPARABLE STORE. KILL ELLIOTT
CONSIDERING NOT PLAYING THIS
UPCOMING SEASON.
♪
>> SOMETIMES THE BEST GIFTS
COMPANY AGREES.
♪
GIBSON VALLEY'S BECAUSE ALWAYS
LIKE THAT AND HEAVY IN THE
LEAD. WELL, I THINK THE WORLD
HAS CHANGED. THESE ARE GOING TO
HAVE THAT LEADING EDGE.
♪
THAT MONEY IN THE BANK DOS
EXCESS IS ALIGNED WITH THE
SUCCESS OF THE WORLD AROUND US
IT'S NOT ALL GLITZ FROM LAMB
HERE IN THE CITY OF ANGELS.
♪
>> ON CAPITOL HILL IS AN ALL
OUT BRAWL BETWEEN THESE
CANDIDATES NEED TO OPERATE FROM
A PLACE OF
♪
COURAGE.
>> THE BETTER GOOD MORNING TELL
ME EVERYTHING COME ON NOW
READILY GET.
>> THE TURN OF EVENTS FOR THIS
COMPANY IS ABSOLUTELY
INCREDIBLE AND KEEPS IT SEEMS
TO BE THE WORD ON
♪
>> EVERYONE'S LIPS.
>> BECAUSE OF ITS WHEN HER
CONDITION AFTER A HUT.
♪
I WENT BACK UP TO DATE.
>> HER FRIEND OF THE SHOW.
>> HAPPY CYBER TODAY TO DIE.
>> I GOT TO MONITOR IS A 100
BUCKS EACH FOR K QUALITY I GOT
TO GREEN SCREENS RIGATO
I HAD A BUNCH OF PIECES PARTS
AND BUILDING MY SECOND PIECE AS
WE TALKED ABOUT LAST TIME BUNCH
OF CLOTHES GOT TO GROW AHEAD,
LISTEN IT WAS EVERYTHING WAS
SUPER-CHEAP THE CYBER MONDAY
LIKE HOLIDAY BLACK FRIDAY AND
THEN WILL YOU.
>> ACTUALLY WHEN AFTER THE SHOW
BEFORE GOING BY EVERYTHING TO
LOOK I WANT TO JUST GET WAY FOR
ALL THE PEOPLE SENT ME LIKE
WHAT THEY WANT FOR CHRISTMAS IS
A SLIGHT EDGE TO
IT WAS ONE HOW IS THAT ONE
PURCHASE BUT ONE MOMENT OF A
PURCHASE BOOKS. I KNOW YOU GUYS
ARE GOING TO BE GETTING ON
CYBER MONDAY WITH MY ART WHICH
SHED CITIZEN QUESTIONS LET US
KNOW, BUT YOU GOTTA ALREADY ARE
WHAT YOU PLAN
ON GETTING THE COMMENTS YOU MAY
HAVE AND WILL ADDRESS AND
THROUGHOUT THE ENTIRE SHOW LIKE
WE SAID LAST WEEK THERE ARE A
LOT
OF GAMING. A VIDEO GAME DEALS
ARE GOING ON TODAY SO FOR TODAY
SOCIABLE WE WANT TO KNOW WHICH
OF THE FALL AND CYBER MONDAY
SALES ARE YOU MOST
EXCITED FOR SO TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS IT IS A THE FOR THIS FOR
THE FIRST ONE IS PLAYSTATION 4
PRO CALL OF DUTY, MODERN
WARFARE BUNDLE FOR $300 X BOX
ONE NEXT AND GEARS OF WAR UPON
THE FULL $349 THE SWITCH LITE
FOR 175 OR THE X BOX ONE S
ALL-DIGITAL FOR A $150 NOW LET
US KNOW WHAT YOU GUYS THINK IT
WILL REVEAL THE RESULTS AT THE
END OF
THE SHOW. I WAS UNDER THE DEAL
THE PLAYSTATION 4 COMES THERE'S
A POSITION FOR ONE OF THE KEY
THE 3 GAS PRICES ARE OWED ON
THE LAST OF US REMASTERED
EDITION AND AND A GOD
OF WAR AND IT WAS LITERALLY
LIKE $299 REALLY SELL A GUY'S
AND LET'S CHECK THAT OUT BUT
COMING UP ON TODAY'S SHOW AS
WELL WE HAVE THE LATEST GAMING
AND ESPORTS UPDATES IN OUR
CHEDDAR E-SPORTS.
>> HEADLINES IN ESPORTS TALENT.
DEAN
WILSON, JOE AND JUST DISCUSS
FULL SAIL UNIVERSITY'S GAMING
AND ESPORTS PROGRAM THEN AFTER
THAT PHASE PLAN B P A BUSINESS
DEVELOP IT. CLINTON SPARKS WILL
DISCUSS BASICALLY BRINGING
HIS MUSIC OVER INTO THE WORLD
OF E-SPORTS ASKED SUPER EXCITED
FOR
THAT ALSO MICHELLE MY ONE OF MY
GOOD FRIEND TOMMY 7 HOSTING
CONTENT CREATOR HIPHOP GAMER
WILL BE HERE IN THE CITY
ATTORNEY TO REVEAL
THE LATEST PLAYSTATION 5
DETAILS PLUS WE'RE BREAKING
DOWN THE SPORTSMAN MISSION
HIGHLIGHT IN THIS WEEK'S
EATING TAPE WHO HAVE WE HAVE A
LOT OF GOOD STUFF TODAY.
YEAH, A LOT OF GOOD STUFF BUT
ALSO A LOT OF GREAT DEALS ON
SUPER
EXCITED BECAUSE OBVIOUSLY WE
HAVE A GUEST LATER ON THIS WEEK
IS IN THE DISCUSSION SOME DEALS
IN TIME FOR CHRISTMAS.
SO GUY THE DEALS ON TO E-SPORTS
ARE NOT OVER BUT LET'S HEAD
INTO 2 CHEDDAR E-SPORTS
HEADLINES POWER ROCKET MORTGAGE
BY QUICKEN LOANS.
HOW YOU GUYS
ARE IS SLEEP
BECAUSE IF YOU MISSED OUT ON
BLACK FRIDAY NOT WORRY BECAUSE
IT'S CYBER MONDAY THAT MEANS IS
PLAYING GREAT SEEMS
TO BE.
>> WE HAD ON GAME SO WE'VE GOT
SOME THE BEST SALES WE FOUND
ONLINE FOR
YOU ALL IN THE MARKET FOR A
PHYSICIAN FOR A SOT HAS A ONE
TERABYTE PRO BUNDLE FLOW.
THE COPY OF OUR WORK FOR FOR
2.99. THOSE MICROSOFT FANS OUT
THERE YOU GET ONE TERABYTE EXPO
WILL TEXTBOOKS ONE X BUNDLE FOR
THE NEW STAR WARS JEDI FALLEN
ORDER
FOR 3 49 MEANWHILE, IF YOU'RE
SHOPPING IN THAT ATTENDED
NEIGHBORHOOD. THERE'S A FEW
DEALS ON SWITCH IS AVAILABLE
GAMESTOP HAS LIGHTS ON SALE FOR
ONE 74. AFTER YOU APPLY IT $25
GIFT CARD AND BEST BUY IS
SELLING THE FIRST
GENERATION SWITCH.
>> BUT THEY WEREN'T ALWAYS THE
DIGITAL DOWNLOAD CODE MARIO
KART 8 DELUXE SAME YOU A CALL
50 BUCKS. IT'S WORTH
NOTING, HOWEVER FOR THAT YOU BE
GETTING THEIR ORIGINAL VERSION
WHICH LACKS A NEW LONGER
LASTING BATTERY LOOKING FOR
GAINS OR ACCESSORIES OUT THERE
DOZENS IF NOT HUNDREDS
OF DISCOUNTS. PRESIDENT
PLATFORM AND MANY RETAILERS ARE
2 MAIN THRUST LIST HERE BUT BE
SURE
TO LOOK.
>> AROUND FOR THAT GAME YOU'VE
BEEN HOLDING OUT FOR FOR A
WHILE SO OUT SOME SAW I SAW
SOME DEALS ON SOME OTHER THINGS
LIKE
FIGHTS 6.
>> SOME VIDEO GAMES BANDAI
NAMCO HAS UP TO
75% OFF AND THEN HE WAS A
LITTLE BIT OF GAME DEALS AND
COPPERFIELD UNBUNDLED IS ON THE
SCENE AND LIKE I MENTIONED
EARLIER WE DO HAVE A GUEST
COMING ON THIS FRIDAY DOES SOME
ADDITIONAL FIELD IN TIME FOR
CHRISTMAS. SO DON'T WORRY EVEN
THOUGH
ITS SIDE MONDAY AND THERE WILL
BE SOME INITIAL DEAL THAT YOU
GUYS CAN PURCHASE THE ENTIRE
MONTH IN TIME FOR THE HOLIDAYS
WILL BE COMING UP AGAIN AND
WASN'T FIGHTS LIKE OF THEM
ACTUALLY NOT LOOKING FOR A
FIGHT 6. ANOTHER'S A DISCOUNT
FOR THAT I'M ACTUALLY 25
DISCOUNT IT MAYBE MORE DEADLY
CHECK AMAZON IT WAS A REALLY
GREAT ADVICE. SOME OF THOSE
REALLY NICE LIKE THEY'RE HUGE.