[Captioning possible by
bill: thank you very much.
Thank you.
Bill: thank you very
much. Thank you. Hi.
Thank you. Hi. Hi.
Hi.
thank you.
Ok.
Thank you. Ok. Ok.
Ok. Ok. All right.
Ok. All right. All right.
All right. All right. Sit down.
All right. Sit down. Thank you.
Sit down. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, ladies and
Thank you very much. Thank you
very much, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much, ladies and
gentlemen. I am totally with you no matter
Gentlemen. I am totally with you no
matter what you're riled up about.
I am totally with you no matter what
you're riled up about. I'm totally with you.
What you're riled up about. I'm totally
with you. Who here is sick about hearing
I'm totally with you. Who here is sick
about hearing about the debt ceiling?
Who here is sick about hearing about the
debt ceiling? Because if there's one more
About the debt ceiling? Because if there's
one more thing that's exciting more than
Because if there's one more thing that's
exciting more than partisan bickering is
Thing that's exciting more than
partisan bickering is accounting.
Partisan bickering is accounting.
This has been going on and has
Accounting. This has been going on
and has reached that awkward moment
This has been going on and has reached that
awkward moment that a pissing contest reaches
Reached that awkward moment that a pissing
contest reaches where everyone is out of piss
That a pissing contest reaches where everyone
is out of piss and now they're just standing
Where everyone is out of piss and now they're
just standing there with their dick in their
And now they're just standing
there with their dick in their hand.
There with their dick in their
hand. It's a little embarrassing.
Hand.
It's a little embarrassing.
yeah, but it's - But it's not
- It's not over.
Yeah, but it's - But it's not - It's
not over. The whole congress has to stay
- It's not over. The whole congress
has to stay there for the whole weekend.
The whole congress has to stay there for the
whole weekend. They have to stay after for the
There for the whole weekend. They
have to stay after for the weekend.
They have to stay after for the
weekend. The tea party republicans are
Weekend. The tea party republicans
are especially pissed off for this.
The tea party republicans are especially
pissed off for this. A lot of them had to cancel
Especially pissed off for this. A lot of them
had to cancel their civil war reenactment.
A lot of them had to cancel their civil war
reenactment. Yeah, their plan is to not pay
Their civil war reenactment. Yeah, their plan
is to not pay our bills and hopes nobody gets
Yeah, their plan is to not pay our bills
and hopes nobody gets too mad about it.
Our bills and hopes nobody gets too mad
about it. Call me crazy, but i think the
Too mad about it. Call me crazy, but i
think the government owes an apology to
Call me crazy, but i think the government
owes an apology to wesley snipes.
Government owes an apology to
wesley snipes. Wasn't that his plan?
Wesley snipes. Wasn't that his
plan? One of the leading tea partiers
Wasn't that his plan? One of the leading
tea partiers is a guy named joe walsh.
One of the leading tea partiers is a guy
named joe walsh. Congressman joe walsh.
Is a guy named joe walsh. Congressman
joe walsh. He went on youtube and wagged
Congressman joe walsh. He went on
youtube and wagged his finger at obama.
He went on youtube and wagged his finger
at obama. Turns he is $117,000 delinquent
His finger at obama. Turns he is
$117,000 delinquent in his child support.
Turns he is $117,000 delinquent in his
child support. Have you no irony, mr.
In his child support. Have
you no irony, mr. Congressman?
Have you no irony, mr. Congressman?
He said his kids don't have a
Congressman? He said his kids
don't have a child support problem.
He said his kids don't have a child support
problem. They have a spending problem.
Child support problem.
They have a spending problem.
you know, if that's their line
as if the only problem is
You know, if that's their line as if the
only problem is spending in washington.
As if the only problem is spending in
washington. John boehner said the other day
Spending in washington. John boehner said
the other day that the democratic plan that
John boehner said the other day that the
democratic plan that was put forward is fake.
That the democratic plan that was put
forward is fake. He wants to save money by
Was put forward is fake. He wants
to save money by ending our wars.
He wants to save money by ending
our wars. Saving money by ending our
Ending our wars. Saving
money by ending our wars?
Saving money by ending our
wars? Have you gone sane?
Wars? Have you gone sane?
The republicans also attached
Have you gone sane? The republicans
also attached 39 writers to the bill
The republicans also attached 39 writers
to the bill repealing environmental
39 writers to the bill repealing
environmental protection law.
Repealing environmental protection
law. Many of them forbade adding
Protection law. Many of them
forbade adding endangered animals.
Many of them forbade adding endangered
animals. Once we get rid of social
Endangered animals. Once we get rid
of social security, the old people will
Once we get rid of social security, the
old people will have to eat something.
Security, the old people will have
to eat something. Sorry, woodpeckers.
Have to eat something. Sorry, woodpeckers.
But you know, i'll tell you the
Sorry, woodpeckers. But you know, i'll
tell you the essence of the problem is
But you know, i'll tell you the essence of
the problem is something i've been saying for
Essence of the problem is something i've been saying for years
- One party has no
Something i've been saying for years
- One party has no brains and the other party has
Years
- One party has no brains and the other party has no balls.
Brains and the other party has no
balls. Is it really so much to ask
No balls. Is it really so much to
ask that to be one party with both?
Is it really so much to ask that to be one
party with both? Listen to this, by midweek the
That to be one party with both? Listen to
this, by midweek the democrats had given to the
Listen to this, by midweek the democrats
had given to the republicans more than they
Democrats had given to the republicans more
than they originally asked for when these
Republicans more than they originally asked
for when these negotiations started and the
Originally asked for when these negotiations
started and the republicans still wouldibility
Negotiations started and the
republicans still wouldibility take it.
Republicans still wouldibility take
it. We are, the democrats getting
Take it. We are, the democrats
getting rid of the bush tax cuts?
We are, the democrats getting rid of the
bush tax cuts? No, that's off the table.
Rid of the bush tax cuts? No, that's off
the table. Deduction on corporation jets?
No, that's off the table. Deduction
on corporation jets? No, off the table.
Deduction on corporation jets? No,
off the table. Ending subsidies for oil
No, off the table. Ending
subsidies for oil companies?
Ending subsidies for oil
companies? Off the table.
Companies? Off the table.
The only thing on the table is
Off the table. The only thing on
the table is the democrats bent over.
The only thing on the table is the democrats
bent over. That's what's on the table.
The democrats bent over.
That's what's on the table.
john boehner's plan, no tax
increases and a trillion
John boehner's plan, no tax increases
and a trillion dollars in cuts.
Increases and a trillion dollars in cuts. Harry reid's plan
- That's the
Dollars in cuts. Harry reid's plan
- That's the democrat's plan, no tax
Harry reid's plan
- That's the democrat's plan, no tax increases, $2 trillion in cuts.
Democrat's plan, no tax increases, $2
trillion in cuts. This makes it really hard for
Increases, $2 trillion in cuts. This makes it
really hard for the white house because if the
This makes it really hard for the white house
because if the democrats don't stand up for
The white house because if the democrats don't
stand up for what they believe in, how can
Democrats don't stand up for what they
believe in, how can obama sell them out?
What they believe in, how can
obama sell them out?
Obama sell them out?
why is he bragging how he is
bending over backwards.
Why is he bragging how he is bending
over backwards. That's not a virtue to me.
Bending over backwards. That's not a
virtue to me. If he bent over more backwards
That's not a virtue to me. If he bent over
more backwards he could work the pole at the
If he bent over more backwards he could
work the pole at the spearmint rhino.
He could work the pole at the spearmint
rhino. Well, one person who will not
Spearmint rhino. Well, one person who
will not be working with the pole at the
Well, one person who will not be working with
the pole at the spearmint rhino is the governor
Be working with the pole at the spearmint rhino
is the governor of new jersey, governor, fat
Spearmint rhino is the governor of new jersey, governor, fat bastard
- I mean governor
Of new jersey, governor, fat bastard
- I mean governor chris cristy had trouble
Bastard
- I mean governor chris cristy had trouble breathing.
Chris cristy had trouble breathing.
He first noticed that there was
Breathing. He first noticed that there
was a problem when he had difficult
He first noticed that there was a problem
when he had difficult inhaling a pizza.
A problem when he had difficult inhaling
a pizza. He was in the supermarket and
Inhaling a pizza. He was in the
supermarket and he felt a tightness in his
He was in the supermarket and
he felt a tightness in his chest.
He felt a tightness in his
chest. And then he realized he had
Chest. And then he realized he
had gotten lodged in the dairy
And then he realized he had
gotten lodged in the dairy case.
Gotten lodged in the
dairy case. No, he's ok.
Case. No, he's ok. The
hospital upgraded his
No, he's ok. The hospital
upgraded his position to gigantic.
The hospital upgraded his position
to gigantic. And the doctors say he's
Position to gigantic. And the doctors
say he's already up and about and taking
And the doctors say he's already up and about
and taking helicopters to travel 20 feet.
Already up and about and taking helicopters
to travel 20 feet. The doctors said to governor
Helicopters to travel 20 feet. The doctors
said to governor cristy, you have to stop eating
The doctors said to governor cristy, you
have to stop eating ice cream out of big
Cristy, you have to stop eating ice cream
out of big five-Gallon tubs and he said
Ice cream out of big
five-Gallon tubs and he said why?
Five-Gallon tubs and he said
why? And the doctor said so i can
Why? And the doctor said
so i can examine you.
And the doctor said so i
can examine you. All right.
Examine you. All right.
We've got a great show.
All right. We've got a great
show. We've got matt kibbe and
We've got a great show. We've got matt
kibbe and margaret hoover and eliot
We've got matt kibbe and margaret
hoover and eliot spitzer is here.
Margaret hoover and eliot spitzer
is here. And a little later bryan
Spitzer is here. And a little later
bryan cranston will be out here.
And a little later bryan cranston will be
out here. But first for 10 years he tried
Cranston will be out here. But first for 10
years he tried to tell the world that bernie
But first for 10 years he tried to tell
the world that bernie madoff was a crook.
To tell the world that bernie madoff was
a crook. His book "no one would lisn. "
Madoff was a crook. His book "no one
would lisn. " His new documentary opening
His book "no one would lisn. " His
new documentary opening august 26.
His new documentary opening
august 26. Harry markopolos.
August 26. Harry markopolos.
>> Thank you for having me.
Harry markopolos. >> Thank you for
having me. Bill: sure, i recognize you
>> Thank you for having me. Bill: sure, i
recognize you from your appearances on "60
Bill: sure, i recognize you from
your appearances on "60 minutes. "
From your appearances on "60
minutes. " You're a whistleower
Minutes. " You're a
whistleower >> iryo be.
You're a whistleower >>
iryo be. I chase bad guys.
>> Iryo be. I chase bad guys.
Bill: there's too little of
I chase bad guys. Bill:
there's too little of that.
Bill: there's too little of
that. How do you think we can make
That. How do you think we can
make the life of the whistleblower
How do you think we can make the life of the
whistleblower more safe and encourage them
The life of the whistleblower
more safe and encourage them more?
More safe and encourage them
more? >> Don frank did that with
More? >> Don frank did that with
section 922, the don frank act.
>> Don frank did that with section 922, the
don frank act. Bill: speak in regular person
Section 922, the don frank act. Bill:
speak in regular person language.
Bill: speak in regular person
language. >> Congress protects
Language. >> Congress
protects whistleblowers.
>> Congress protects whistleblowers.
If they do, they won't get
Whistleblowers. If they
do, they won't get punished.
If they do, they won't get
punished. They get rarded with 10% to
Punished. They get rarded with 10%
to ste. Of whatever the bad guys
They get rarded with 10% to ste. Of whatever
the bad guys bill: i hear that that bill
Ste. Of whatever the bad guys bill: i hear
that that bill you're referring to is dying
Bill: i hear that that bill you're referring
to is dying the death of a thousand cuts
You're referring to is dying the death of
a thousand cuts because they have a million
The death of a thousand cuts because they
have a million lobbyists that are working at
Because they have a million lobbyists that
are working at it and they're at it like chris
Lobbyists that are working at it and they're
at it like chris cristy at porter house steak.
It and they're at it like chris cristy at
porter house steak. >> The s. E.C. Has been very
Cristy at porter house steak. >> The s. E.C.
Has been very aggressive and diligently are
>> The s. E.C. Has been very aggressive and
diligently are solving those cases with me.
Aggressive and diligently are solving those
cases with me. Fahris cristy is. More about how
Solving those cases with me.
Fahris cristy is. More about how no.
Fahris cristy is. More about
how no. As an expert on financial
No. As an expert on financial
things, but is there any
As an expert on financial things, but is
there any connection in your mind between
Things, but is there any connection in your mind between what was going on
- It was
Connection in your mind between what was going on
- It was only a few years ago when we
What was going on
- It was only a few years ago when we were obsessed with bernie
Only a few years ago when we were obsessed
with bernie madoff and this crisis that's
Were obsessed with bernie madoff
and this crisis that's going on?
Madoff and this crisis that's going
on? >> Y, croed accounting is a
Going on? >> Y, croed accounting
is a similar theme between both.
>> Y, croed accounting is a similar theme
between both. Congress can attack the $24
Similar theme between both. Congress can
attack the $24 trillion deficit problem.
Congress can attack the $24 trillion deficit
problem. But they have off-Balance sheet
Trillion deficit problem. But they have
off-Balance sheet liabilitys that are bigger.
But they have off-Balance sheet liabilitys
that are bigger. Medicare is probably $80
Liabilitys that are bigger.
Medicare is probably $80 trillion.
Medicare is probably $80
trillion. >> Unfunded. Illion?
Trillion. >> Unfunded.
Illion? Bill: how many years?
>> Unfunded. Illion? Bill: how many
years? >> You have to look long-Term.
Bill: how many years? >> You have to look
long-Term. You to be budgeted in decades.
>> You have to look long-Term. You to be
budgeted in decades. Bill: we're not going to run
You to be budgeted in decades. Bill:
we're not going to run that up in a year.
Bill: we're not going to run
that up in a year. >> By 2040-
That up in a year. >> By 2040
- Bill: $80 trillion.
>> By 2040
- Bill: $80 trillion. Y, we're in bigger shit than
Bill: $80 trillion. Y, we're
in bigger shit than i thought.
Y, we're in bigger shit than i
thought. You're debbie downer.
I thought. You're debbie downer.
And if we default, i mean, you
You're debbie downer. And if we default,
i mean, you hear this argument on
And if we default, i mean, you hear this
argument on television every day, the t
Hear this argument on
television every day, the t
Television every day, the t
part ss, don't worry about
Part ss, don't worry about
it.
it. But we're fucked, rht, ife
It. But we're fucked, rht, ife default?
But we're fucked, rht, ife
default? The people who seem to know
Default? The people who seem to
know math and have went to college,
The people who seem to know math and have went to college, they seem and read
- They seem
Math and have went to college, they seem and
read - They seem - The thinkers is what i'm
They seem and read - They seem - The thinkers
is what i'm saying, they seem to feel that
- The thinkers is what i'm saying, they seem
to feel that if we default on this, it is a
Saying, they seem to feel that if
we default on this, it is a clamity.
If we default on this, it is a
clamity. >> The u. S. Dollar can quickly
Clamity. >> The u. S. Dollar can
quickly become the american peso.
>> The u. S. Dollar can quickly become the
american peso. That's what the math looks
Become the american peso.
That's what the math looks like.
As far as a triple a rating,
Like. As far as a triple a rating,
there's no way we can have a
As far as a triple a rating, there's no way
we can have a triple a rating not with the
There's no way we can have a triple a
rating not with the congress we have.
Triple a rating not with the congress
we have. Bill: but if we lose that
Congress we have. Bill: but if we
lose that triple a rating worse.
Bill: but if we lose that triple a
rating worse. >> It's going to harm the
Triple a rating worse. >>
It's going to harm the economy.
>> It's going to harm the economy.
Bill: so you're saying we're
Economy. Bill: so you're saying
we're skating on a triple a and we
Bill: so you're saying we're skating on a
triple a and we shouldn't do anything who know
Skating on a triple a and we shouldn't do
anything who know it's not really a triple a.
Shouldn't do anything who know it's not
really a triple a. >> Double-A is bad.
It's not really a triple a. >>
Double-A is bad. A.A. Could be worse.
>> Double-A is bad. A.A. Could
be worse. Bill: i get it it.
A.A. Could be worse. Bill: i get it it.
- I get it.
Bill: i get it it.
bill: so i really enjoyed the
documentary about bernie
Bill: so i really enjoyed the
documentary about bernie madoff.
Documentary about bernie madoff.
I must say there was a lot more
Madoff. I must say there was a
lot more guns involved in that
I must say there was a lot more guns
involved in that documentary than i thought
Guns involved in that documentary than
i thought there would in a documentary
Documentary than i thought there would
in a documentary about an accountant.
There would in a documentary about an
accountant. Tell the people's about the
About an accountant. Tell the people's
about the guns because you feared for
Tell the people's about the guns
because you feared for your life.
Guns because you feared for your
life. >> I did because bernie was
Your life. >> I did because bernie
was stealing from organized crime
>> I did because bernie was stealing from
organized crime if you're crazy enough to steal
Stealing from organized crime if you're crazy
enough to steal from the co william byians,
If you're crazy enough to steal from the co
william byians, well, they have a unique of
From the co william byians, well, they have
a unique of managing their terminations.
Well, they have a unique of managing
their terminations. If he knew i had a team
Managing their terminations. If he knew
i had a team dragging him across two
If he knew i had a team dragging him
across two continents then i have a lot to
Dragging him across two continents
then i have a lot to fear.
Continents then i have a lot to
fear. Bill: do you still fear?
Fear. Bill: do you still fear?
>> No, all the risk turned to
Bill: do you still fear? >> No, all the
risk turned to him when he turned his sorry
>> No, all the risk turned to him
when he turned his sorry butt i
Him when he turned his sorry
butt i
Butt i
bill: right.
Do we know how he's doing in
Bill: right. Do we know
how he's doing in prison?
Do we know how he's doing in
prison? >> I heae's an joying an
Prison? >> I heae's an
joying an active sex life.
>> I heae's an joying an active
sex life. He's the belle of the balm
Active sex life. He's the belle of the balm bill: he hasn't
- Belle of the
He's the belle of the balm bill: he hasn't
- Belle of the ball.
Bill: he hasn't
- Belle of the ball. Bill: he hasn't made a lot of
Ball. Bill: he hasn't
made a lot of enemies.
Bill: he hasn't made a lot of
enemies. >> No one needed the guns more
Enemies. >> No one needed the
guns more yocan' exactly flee to
>> No one needed the guns more yocan'
exactly flee to another country with all those
Yocan' exactly flee to another country
with all those people looking if you.
Another country with all those
people looking if you. Bill: right.
People looking if you. Bill: right.
You mentioned organized crime,
Bill: right. You mentioned organized
crime, it kind of reminded me of
You mentioned organized crime, it kind of
reminded me of whitey bullger, you know that
It kind of reminded me of whitey
bullger, you know that crook from england.
Whitey bullger, you know that crook
from england. He was protected the whole
Crook from england. He was protected
the whole time, it turned out from the
He was protected the whole time,
it turned out from the inside.
Time, it turned out from the inside.
He had those guys on the f. B.I.
Inside. He had those guys on the
f. B.I. He was their informants.
He had those guys on the f. B.I. He was
their informants. It's sort of the same thing
He was their informants. It's sort of
the same thing with bernie and the s. E.
It's sort of the same thing with bernie and the s. E. Cremplet c.
- S.E.C.
With bernie and the s. E. Cremplet c.
- S.E.C. They protected him.
Cremplet c.
- S.E.C. They protected him. >> They're supposed to regulate
They protected him. >> They're supposed
to regulate just like the material mining
>> They're supposed to regulate just
like the material mining industry.
Just like the material mining
industry. The miners were killed.
Industry. The miners were
killed. People on the horizons.
The miners were killed. People on the
horizons. And that's how they do it.
People on the horizons. And that's how
they do it. Bill: is the s. E.C. Better now
Than it was in bush.
>> Mary shapiro is the chairman
Than it was in bush. >> Mary shapiro
is the chairman has clean house.
>> Mary shapiro is the chairman has
clean house. She's enacted all of the
Has clean house. She's enacted all
of the reforms that the attorney
She's enacted all of the reforms that the
attorney general has pointed out in the
Reforms that the attorney general
has pointed out in the madoff case.
General has pointed out in the madoff
case. They're bringing out big cases.
Madoff case. They're bringing out big
cases. Before there was a protected
They're bringing out big cases. Before
there was a protected species on wall street.
Before there was a protected species on
wall street. And now no one's protected on
Species on wall street. And now
no one's protected on wall street.
And now no one's protected on wall
street. Bill: so if we had another
Wall street. Bill: so if we had
another crisis with the banks, would we
Bill: so if we had another crisis
with the banks, would we il tm ogain
They don't deserve it, do they?
Bill: but they say if we d't,
They don't deserve it, do they? Bill: but
they say if we d't, then the clamity would be
Bill: but they say if we d't,
then the clamity would be greater.
Then the clamity would be greater.
>> What shay should have done
Greater. >> What shay should have
done the first time is nationalize
>> What shay should have done the first
time is nationalize these companies.
The first time is nationalize these
companies. Turn them over to the
These companies. Turn them
over to the bondholders.
Turn them over to the bondholders.
Say your bond is worthless.
Bondholders. Say your bond is
worthless. Any liquidity means you have,
Say your bond is worthless. Any liquidity
means you have, the federal reserve will
Any liquidity means you have, the federal
reserve will provide liquidity as far as the
The federal reserve will provide liquidity
as far as the c. E.O. And the chief risk
Provide liquidity as far as the c. E.O.
And the chief risk officer, gone, fired.
C.E.O. And the chief risk officer, gone,
fired. Bill: well, since we're about
Officer, gone, fired. Bill: well, since
we're about to default and since we bailed
Bill: well, since we're about to default and
since we bailed out the banks, what about the
To default and since we bailed out the banks,
what about the banks bailing out us this time?
Out the banks, what about the banks bailing
out us this time? What about the banks lending
Banks bailing out us this time? What about
the banks lending the united states money and
What about the banks lending the united
states money and then we saying to them, we'll
The united states money and then we saying
to them, we'll pay you back when we get it?
Then we saying to them, we'll pay you
back when we get it? >> Amen, brother.
Pay you back when we get it?
>> Amen, brother. Let's do that.
>> Amen, brother. Let's
do that. I like that.
Let's do that. I like that.
Bill: thank you very much.
I like that. Bill: thank you
very much. Harry markopolos.
Bill: thank you very much.
Harry markopolos.
all right.
Let's meet our panel.
All right. Let's meet our
panel. Hey, here they are.
Let's meet our panel. Hey, here they
are. He is the former governor of
Hey, here they are. He is the
former governor of new york.
He is the former governor of new
york. You all know the sheriff of
New york. You all know the sheriff
of wall street, eliot spitzer.
You all know the sheriff of wall street,
eliot spitzer. She isepubcans strategist
Wall street, eliot spitzer. She isepubcans
strategist and author of "american
She isepubcans strategist and author of
"american individualism," margaret hoover
And author of "american individualism,"
margaret hoover is bac wit us.
Individualism," margaret
hoover is bac wit us. Hey,argat.
Is bac wit us. Hey,argat. And
the president and c. E.O. Of
Hey,argat. And the president and
c. E.O. Of freedom worksnd author of
And the president and c. E.O. Of freedom
worksnd author of "give us liberty" matt kibbe.
Freedom worksnd author of "give us
liberty" matt kibbe. How are you doing?
"Give us liberty" matt kibbe.
How are you doing? >> Good.
Bill: this is a good pel
>> Good. Bill: this is a good
pel because we have representation
Bill: this is a good pel because we have
representation of the entire united states
Because we have representation of
the entire united states system.
Of the entire united states system. We have a democrat
- A real
System. We have a democrat
- A real democrat.
We have a democrat
- A real democrat. >> Thank you for saying that.
Democrat. >> Thank you for
saying that. I'm proud of that.
>> Thank you for saying that. I'm proud
of that. Bill: not the kind of pussies
I'm proud of that. Bill: not the kind
of pussies then we have a republican.
Bill: not the kind of pussies then we
have a republican. >> I like the tea party.
Then we have a republican. >> I like
the tea party. I think the tea party has
>> I like the tea party. I think
the tea party has brought enormous -
I think the tea party has brought enormous
- Bill: just like a replica
Brought enormous
- Bill: just like a replica wi nevay a bad word
Bill: just like a replica wi nevay
a bad word against the tea party.
Wi nevay a bad word against the tea
party. And then we have a true tea
Against the tea party. And
then we have a true tea party.
Tea partier.
Bill: i don't know what you
Tea partier. Bill: i don't know
what you have to be a shamed of other
Bill: i don't know what you have to be a
shamed of other than bringing down this world.
Have to be a shamed of other than bringing
down this world. You are contrliverything.
Than bringing down this world. You are
contrliverything. I don't know if that's fair.
You are contrliverything. I don't know if
that's fair. I heard matt laurer say the
I don't know if that's fair. I heard matt
laurer say the other day, do the american
I heard matt laurer say the other day, do
the american people deserve this, you know,
Other day, do the american people
deserve this, you know, what's going on?
People deserve this, you know, what's
going on? And my answer would be the
What's going on? And my answer would
be the people in the tea party deserve
And my answer would be the people in the tea
party deserve it because when i hear it's all
People in the tea party deserve it
because when i hear it's all over the news.
It because when i hear it's all over
the news. When i hear it's a hostage
Over the news. When i hear it's a
hostage situation, your economic terror
When i hear it's a hostage situation,
your economic terror is is that fair?
Situation, your economic terror is is
that fair? >> I don't think that's fair.
Is is that fair? >> I don't think that's
fair. We stepped up in a democratic
>> I don't think that's fair. We
stepped up in a democratic process.
We stepped up in a democratic
process. The government goes to those
Process. The government
goes to those who show up.
The government goes to those who
show up. In 2009 we marched to
Who show up. In 2009 we marched
to washington in peaceful protest
In 2009 we marched to washington in peaceful
protest petitioning our government for
Washington in peaceful protest
petitioning our government for grievances.
Petitioning our government for
grievances. Bill: what about the people who
Grievances. Bill: what about the
people who say, you don't really
Bill: what about the people who say,
you don't really understand how dire this
Say, you don't really understand
how dire this situation is?
Understand how dire this situation
is? It's like a baby who got a hold
Situation is? It's like a baby who got
a hold of a shotgun and we're trying
It's like a baby who got a hold of a shotgun
and we're trying to get it away from the baby.
Of a shotgun and we're trying to get it away
from the baby. >> Here's how i see it, both
To get it away from the baby. >> Here's
how i see it, both parties are sitting in a
>> Here's how i see it, both parties
are sitting in a burning theater.
Parties are sitting in a
burning theater. We yeldire.
Burning theater. We yeldire.
>> I don't want to jump in and
We yeldire. >> I don't want to jump in and be too
- But i think you guys
>> I don't want to jump in and be too
- But i think you guys lit the fire.
Be too
- But i think you guys lit the fire. Let's be real about this.
Lit the fire. Let's be real about this. Many people
- Bill clinton had
Let's be real about this. Many people
- Bill clinton had a budget surplus.
Many people
- Bill clinton had a budget surplus. George bush gave us the
A budget surplus. George bush gave
us the deficit, gave us the recession,
George bush gave us the deficit, gave us
the recession, gave us the recession that led
Deficit, gave us the recession, gave us
the recession that led us over the cliff.
Gave us the recession that led us over
the cliff. It is the inmates running the
Us over the cliff. It is the
inmates running the asylum.
It is the inmates running the
asylum. It is the people running the
Asylum. It is the people
running the polics -
It is the people running the
polics -
Polics -
>> i'm glad you say i'm an old
school democrat.
>> I'm glad you say i'm an old school
democrat. I believe in science -
School democrat. I believe in science
- >> And spending.
I believe in science
- >> And spending. >> And in responsible
>> And spending. >> And
in responsible capitalism.
>> And in responsible capitalism.
>> Leer's what really happened
Capitalism. >> Leer's what really happened
- Here's what really happened.
>> Leer's what really happened
- Here's what really happened. Let's be honest.
- Here's what really happened. Let's be
honest. There was no deficit and george
Let's be honest. There was no
deficit and george bush raised it.
There was no deficit and george bush
raised it. And then it got doubled by
Bush raised it. And then it
got doubled by barack obama.
And then it got doubled by barack
obama. And so here's the reality.
Barack obama. And so here's the
reality. The tea party came to town -
And so here's the reality. The tea party
came to town - It - The debt doubled.
The tea party came to town - It -
The debt doubled. The debt doubled.
It
- The debt doubled. The debt doubled. And the reality is that if the
The debt doubled. And the reality is
that if the tea party hadn't come to town
And the reality is that if the tea party hadn't
come to town the senate would have had a few
Tea party hadn't come to town the senate would
have had a few speeches and the floor and the
The senate would have had a few
speeches and the floor and the
Speeches and the floor and the
>> We changed the conversation.
Bill: did the debt double since
Bill: did the debt double since obama?
obama? >> Not because of the
Obama? >> Not because of the president.
>> Not because of the
president. Four factors.
Bill: really?
The debt is $14 trillion?
Bill: really? The debt
is $14 trillion? >> Yeah.
The debt is $14 trillion? >>
Yeah. >> Here's whataused it
>> Yeah.
>> Here's whataused it
>> we're about to go to 15-
>> We're about to go to 15-
>> Admit that i'm right now.
>> We're about to go to 15
- >> Admit that i'm right now. >> Two wars caused it.
>> Admit that i'm right now. >> Two wars
caused it. The bush tax cut caused it -
>> Two wars caused it. The bush tax
cut caused it - >> The stimulus -
The bush tax cut caused it - >> The
stimulus - >> Please stop one minute.
>> The stimulus
- >> Please stop one minute. The recession that's the
>> Please stop one minute. The recession
that's the consequence of the deregulatory
The recession that's the consequence of the
deregulatory craziness and the stimulus that
Consequence of the deregulatory craziness and
the stimulus that worked - The auto industry -
Craziness and the stimulus that
worked - The auto industry - Bill: 7%.
Worked - The auto industry -
Bill: 7%. >> Bill is exactly right.
Bill: 7%. >> Bill is exactly
right. Bill: the stimulus is 7%.
>> Bill is exactly right. Bill: the
stimulus is 7%. >> Barack obama budget's -
Bill: the stimulus is 7%. >> Barack obama budget's
- An why dide nee it
>> Barack obama budget's
- An why dide nee it >> the debt has doubled.
An why dide nee it >> the debt has
doubled. >> Margaret, you're not looking
>> The debt has doubled. >> Margaret,
you're not looking at causive factors.
>> Margaret, you're not looking
at causive factors. >> No!
At causive factors.
>> No! But elliott -
>> No! But elliott
- Bill: let's move on.
But elliott -
Bill: let's move on.
>> you're patronizing to the
woman on the table.
>> You're patronizing to the woman on
the table. We're talking about numbers.
Woman on the table. We're talking about
numbers. We're talking about a debt that
We're talking about numbers. We're talking
about a debt that has doubled since barack obama
We're talking about a debt that has doubled
since barack obama has been in office.
Has doubled since barack obama
has been in office. That's a fact.
Has been in office. That's a
fact. Bill: it's not a fact.
That's a fact. Bill: it's not a
fact. It's not the right number -
Bill: it's not a fact. It's not the right
number - And also, i'll tell you - In
It's not the right number - And also, i'll
tell you - In 2009 which is bush's budget,
And also, i'll tell you
- In 2009 which is bush's budget, ok, the reason why they had to
2009 which is bush's budget, ok, the reason
why they had to spend some money and again 7%
Ok, the reason why they had to spend some money
and again 7% of the big problem, the reason
Spend some money and again 7% of the big
problem, the reason they had to was because the
Of the big problem, the reason they had to
was because the last guy drove the economy into
They had to was because the last
guy drove the economy into a ditch.
Last guy drove the economy into a
ditch. I'm going to get to my nex
A ditch. I'm going to
get to my nex point.
I'm going to get to my nex point.
This is problem which is the
Point. This is problem which is
the democrats get blamed by the
This is problem which is the democrats get
blamed by the vast majority of americans for
Democrats get blamed by the vast majority
of americans for an ineffectual stimulus bill
Vast majority of americans for an ineffectual
stimulus bill and almost half of it was
An ineffectual stimulus bill and almost
half of it was republican tax cuts.
And almost half of it was
republican tax cuts. It wn't g eugh.
Republican tax cuts. It wn't
g eugh. It s 1/3 of tax cuts.
It wn't g eugh. It s 1/3 of tax
cuts. Bill: but in a $15 trillion
It s 1/3 of tax cuts. Bill: but in a $15
trillion economy or whatever it is, it
Bill: but in a $15 trillion economy or whatever
it is, it was not nearly enough to do the
Economy or whatever it is, it was
not nearly enough to do the job.
Was not nearly enough to do the
job. This is my problem with the
Job. This is my problem
with the democrats.
This is my problem with the
democrats. They sign on to shit that
Democrats. They sign on to
shit that wasn't their idea.
They sign on to shit that wasn't
their idea. I no longer understand this
Wasn't their idea. I no
longer understand this man.
I no longer understand
this man. And i liked him.
Man. And i liked him.
And i voted for him.
And i liked him. And i voted for
him. I just don't understand this
And i voted for him. I just
don't understand this man anymore.
I just don't understand this man
anymore. When he caved on revenues, i
Man anymore. When he caved on
revenues, i thought this was the line in
When he caved on revenues, i thought
this was the line in the sand.
Thought this was the line in the
sand. I thought he would understand,
The sand. I thought he would
understand, that you know, what my
I thought he would understand, that you
know, what my reputation is not good as a
That you know, what my reputation
is not good as a negotiator.
Reputation is not good as a
negotiator. We need some revenues to fix
Negotiator. We need some
revenues to fix this.
We need some revenues to fix this. When he caved on that
- I
This. When he caved on that
- I mean, they own him.
When he caved on that
- I mean, they own him. >> It's worse than that, bill.
Mean, they own him. >> It's worse than
that, bill. I agree with you, he never
>> It's worse than that, bill. I agree with
you, he never should have done the december
I agree with you, he never should have done
the december deal to extend the bush tax
Should have done the december
deal to extend the bush tax cuts.
Deal to extend the bush tax
cuts. That's what's creating the
Cuts. That's what's
creating the deficit.
That's what's creating
the deficit. One second.
Deficit. One second. Once
he agreed to do it, not
One second. Once he agreed to do it,
not back in december to say to the
Once he agreed to do it, not back in december
to say to the republican house and the
Back in december to say to the republican
house and the republican leadership inhe
Republican house and the republican
leadership inhe senate, raise the debt ceiling
Republican leadership inhe senate, raise the
debt ceiling on him now, it was as clear as
Senate, raise the debt ceiling on him now, it
was as clear as the sun coming up the next day,
On him now, it was as clear as the sun coming
up the next day, we were going to get hit by
The sun coming up the next day,
we were going to get hit by this.
We were going to get hit by this.
He gave them a second bite io
This. He gave them a
second bite io the apple.
He gave them a second bite io the
apple. This whole thing should have
The apple. This whole thing should
have been aided ifim geithner
This whole thing should have been
aided ifim geithner negotiated properly.
Been aided ifim geithner negotiated
properly. >> We have to be clear about
Negotiated properly. >> We
have to be clear about this.
>> We have to be clear about this.
The democrats have yet to put a
This. The democrats have yet to
put a plan on the table to deal with
The democrats have yet to put a plan on the
table to deal with the debt or the debt ceiling.
Plan on the table to deal with the debt or
the debt ceiling. Those are talking points.
The debt or the debt ceiling. Those are
talking points. What happened to transparency?
Those are talking points. What happened
to transparency? What happenedo the idea -
What happened to transparency? What happenedo the idea
- Bill: matt, wasn't the grand
What happenedo the idea
- Bill: matt, wasn't the grand bargain, i don't think he
Bill: matt, wasn't the grand bargain, i
don't think he should have linked the debt
Bargain, i don't think he should have
linked the debt ceiling fight with the budget
Should have linked the debt ceiling
fight with the budget fight to begin with.
Ceiling fight with the budget fight to
begin with. The debt ceiling fight is about
Fight to begin with. The debt ceiling
fight is about the past, money we've already
The debt ceiling fight is about
the past, money we've already spent.
The past, money we've already
spent. The budget fight is about the
Spent. The budget fight
is about the future.
The budget fight is
about the future. Ok.
Future. Ok. But he did.
Ok. But he did. Did he
not put on the table a
But he did. Did he not put on the
table a grand bargain with more deficit
Did he not put on the table a grand bargain
with more deficit reduction than even the
Grand bargain with more deficit
reduction than even the republicans?
Reduction than even the republicans?
>> We don't know what it was.
Republicans? >> We don't know what
it was. He floated it to the press.
>> We don't know what it was. He floated
it to the press. >> It was never in writing.
Writing was his budget in
january which was sent to the
Writing was his budget in january
which was sent to the senate.
January which was sent to the
senate. And he couldn't get any
Senate. And he couldn't get
any democrat to vote for it.
And he couldn't get any
democrat to vote for it. 97-0.
Democrat to vote for it. 97-0.
Then he gave a speech which the
97-0. Then he gave a speech
which the c. V.O.An't score.
Then he gave a speech which the c.
V.O.An't score. >> There have bee nber of
C.V.O.An't score. >> There have
bee nber of different plans.
>> There have bee nber of different
plans. You have bole simpson.
Different plans. You have bole
simpson. Bole simpson has been the
You have bole simpson. Bole
simpson has been the pardon -
Bole simpson has been the pardon
- >> Wait.
Pardon
- >> Wait. Because the republicans in the
>> Wait. Because the
republicans in the house refuse.
Because the republicans in the house
refuse. Then you have the gang of six
House refuse. Then you have the gang
of six which was a bipartisan effort.
Then you have the gang of six which was a
bipartisan effort. >> Wasn't barack obama behind
Which was a bipartisan effort. >>
Wasn't barack obama behind that?
>> Wasn't barack obama behind
that? >> Yes, he did in the subtle
That? >> Yes, he did in
the subtle way that the -
>> Yes, he did in the subtle way that the
- >> In the subtle way that the
Way that the
- >> In the subtle way that the president decided to leave the
>> In the subtle way that the president
decided to leave the country in a crisis?
President decided to leave the country
in a crisis? >> That's exactly right.
Country in a crisis? >> That's exactly
right. We have offered as democrats
>> That's exactly right. We have offered
as democrats 3-1 a ratio of cuts to revenue.
We have offered as democrats 3-1 a ratio
of cuts to revenue. That was beyond -
3-1 a ratio of cuts to revenue. That was
beyond - >> Why don't you tell them to
That was beyond
- >> Why don't you tell them to the american people?
>> Why don't you tell them to the
american people? Bill: let me ask this -
The american people? Bill: let me ask this
- Whatever passes, hasn't barack
Bill: let me ask this
- Whatever passes, hasn't barack obama signed his own death
Whatever passes, hasn't barack obama signed
his own death warrant as a candidate for 2012
Obama signed his own death warrant as a
candidate for 2012 because whatever passes, it's
Warrant as a candidate for 2012 because whatever
passes, it's going to strangle this recovery
Because whatever passes, it's going to strangle
this recovery in the crib which i think is
Going to strangle this recovery in the crib
which i think is what you republicans want?
In the crib which i think is what you
republicans want? I don't think you want the
What you republicans want? I don't think
you want the economy to succeed because if
I don't think you want the economy to succeed because if the economy succeeds
- I think
Economy to succeed because if the economy succeeds
- I think you want to kill it because
The economy succeeds
- I think you want to kill it because th is t thwayo hehe
You want to kill it because
th is t thwayo hehe economy.
Th is t thwayo hehe economy.
So why obama said, you know
Economy. So why obama said, you
know what, i'm half in on this
So why obama said, you know what, i'm
half in on this shitty idea of yours.
What, i'm half in on this shitty idea
of yours. Instead of saying months ago,
Shitty idea of yours. Instead of saying
months ago, this is how democrats would
Instead of saying months ago, this
is how democrats would approach this.
This is how democrats would
approach this. Yes, we are in debt.
Approach this. Yes, we are in
debt. But we've been in debt before.
Yes, we are in debt. But we've been in
debt before. And we've been in debt worse.
But we've been in debt before. And we've been
in debt worse. We need to get people working
And we've been in debt worse. We need to
get people working so that more taxpayers are
We need to get people working so that
more taxpayers are getting us out of debt.
So that more taxpayers are getting us out
of debt. That's an alternative approach.
Getting us out of debt. That's an alternative
approach. >> Paul crudeman's article was
That's an alternative approach. >> Paul
crudeman's article was about the stimulus was too
>> Paul crudeman's article was
about the stimulus was too small.
About the stimulus was too
small. >> We will spend more money
Small. >> We will spend
more money that we don'have
Do you know that germany's
vernment spending far excee
vernment spending far excee ours?
Vernment spending far excee ours?
Right now they'reutperforming
Ours? Right now they'reutperforming
us and evebo's sing what
Right now they'reutperforming us and
evebo's sing what are they doing right?
Us and evebo's sing what are they doing
right? Bill: as elliott was saying the
Are they doing right? Bill: as elliott
was saying the republicans spend all this
Bill: as elliott was saying the
republicans spend all this money.
Republicans spend all this money.
Where were the tea baggers when
Money. Where were the tea baggers
when all the money was being spent?
Where were the tea baggers when all
the money was being spent? Crickets.
I ner hrd - And then
suddenly - Sudnly when
I ner hrd - And then suddenly -
Sudnly when blacky mcblackman becomes
Suddenly - Sudnly when blacky
mcblackman becomes president -
Blacky mcblackman becomes president
- >> No, no, no, no, no.
President
- >> No, no, no, no, no. Bill: suddenly the conversation
>> No, no, no, no, no. Bill: suddenly the
conversation turns back to we're spending
Bill: suddenly the conversation turns
back to we're spending tomu money.
Turns back to we're spending tomu
money. >> You are rewriting history.
Tomu money. >> You are
rewriting history. Come on, guys.
>> You are rewriting history.
Come on, guys.
The a pty started under the
bush bailouts.
The a pty started under the bush
bailouts. The $700 billion that bush
Bush bailouts. The $700 billion
that bush bailed out the banks.
The $700 billion that bush bailed out
the banks. That's when you started to see
Bailed out the banks. That's when you
started to see the patriots and the tea party.
That's when you started to see the patriots
and the tea party. Bill: but that's not when the
The patriots and the tea party. Bill:
but that's not when the spending srted.
Bill: but that's not when the spending
srted. What about the other four years
Spending srted.
What about the other four years
>> Go back to your marks -
Bill: where were the tea
>> Go back to your marks
- Bill: where were the tea baggers then?
Bill: where were the tea baggers
then? What about those seven years?
Baggers then? What about those seven
years? >> We were opposing this all
What about those seven years? >>
We were opposing this all along.
>> We were opposing this all along. We were against
- We were
Along. We were against
- We were against medicare part d.
We were against
- We were against medicare part d. We were against the earmarks.
Against medicare part d. We were against
the earmarks. We have attacked republicans
We were against the earmarks. We have
attacked republicans when they have overespn.
We have attacked republicans when
they have overespn. Reblics orspe,
When they have overespn. Reblics
orspe, democrats overspent.
Reblics orspe, democrats
overspent. Bill: much more quietly.
Democrats overspent. Bill: much more
quietly. >> I asked dick, where would
Bill: much more quietly. >> I
asked dick, where would you cut?
>> I asked dick, where
would you cut? M.P.R..
You cut? M.P.R.. Here's the other thing.
M.P.R.. Here's the other
thing. Revenue has gone down.
Here's the other thing. Revenue has gone
down. It's not that spending has gone
Revenue has gone down. It's not that
spending has gone up as much, revenue has gone
It's not that spending has gone up as much, revenue has gone down
- No, no, if you look at
Up as much, revenue has gone down
- No, no, if you look at the percentage revenue down
Down
- No, no, if you look at the percentage revenue down 14.8%.
The percentage revenue down 14.8%.
>> Right because we have 9.7%
14.8%. >> Right because
we have 9.7% unemployment.
>> Right because we have 9.7% unemployment.
You can't pay your taxes if you
Unemployment. You can't pay your
taxes if you don't have a job.
You can't pay your taxes if you don't
have a job. >> You can't cut off this blood
Don't have a job.
>> You can't cut off this blood
supp of money into the
Supp of money into the
economy.
Supp of money into the economy.
Let's stop talking about that.
Economy. Let's stop talking about
that. I want to ask about the story
Let's stop talking about that. I want
to ask about the story was this week.
I want to ask about the story was this
week. This clip from the movie "the
Was this week. This clip
from the movie "the town. "
This clip from the movie "the
town. " Did you see "the town"?
Town. " Did you see "the town"?
What a terrific movie, ben
Did you see "the town"? What a
terrific movie, ben affleck's movie.
What a terrific movie, ben affleck's
movie. And as sort of a motivation for
Affleck's movie. And as sort of a
motivation for their troops, the republicans
And as sort of a motivation for their troops,
the republicans showed at their meeting, i
Their troops, the republicans showed at
their meeting, i think it was tuesday morning
Showed at their meeting, i think it was
tuesday morning trying to get votes a clip from
Show the clip that they used as
motivation.
motivation. >> I need your help.
Motivation. >> I need your help.
I can't tell you what it is.
>> I need your help. I can't tell you
what it is. You could never ask me about it
I can't tell you what it is. You
could never ask me about it later.
You could never ask me about it
later. >> What's cal going to take?
Later. >> What's cal going to
take? Bill: the republican party,
>> What's cal going to take? Bill: the
republican party, we're going to hurt some
Bill: the republican party,
we're going to hurt some people.
We're going to hurt some people.
And alan west from florida
People. And alan west from florida
said, you know, you had me at
And alan west from florida said, you
know, you had me at "hurt some people. "
Said, you know, you had me at "hurt
some people. " I'll drive the car.
"Hurt some people. " I'll drive the
car. Aside from the fact that the
I'll drive the car. Aside from the fact
that the republicans keep using people
Aside from the fact that the republicans
keep using people ke ben affleck, bruce
Republicans keep using people ke ben
affleck, bruce springstein, tom petty, people
Ke ben affleck, bruce springstein, tom
petty, people who don't like them in their
Springstein, tom petty, people who don't
like them in their music and then these people
Who don't like them in their music and then
these people have to sue them or call them
Music and then these people have to sue them
or call them up anday please don't use my
Have to sue them or call them up anday
please don't use my song, pleas don't use my
Up anday please don't use my
song, pleas don't use my movie.
Song, pleas don't use my
movie. We don't like you.
Movie. We don't like you.
Weapon don't agree with you.
We don't like you. Weapon don't agree
with you. But i guess what else would
Weapon don't agree with you. But
i guess what else would they use?
But i guess what else would they
use? It's not that much from "walker
They use? It's not that much
from "walker texas ranger".
It's not that much from "walker
texas ranger".
Texas ranger".
i don't know what i'm asking
here.
I don't know what i'm asking
here. Are liberals making too big,
Here. Are liberals making too
big, something out of nothing?
Are liberals making too big, something out
of nothing? >> Imagine if we had done that?
Something out of nothing? >> Imagine if we
had done that? If i had ever used lines like
>> Imagine if we had done that? If i had
ever used lines like that it would have been
If i had ever used lines like
that it would have been craziness.
That it would have been craziness.
Then you would have hadhe fox
Craziness. Then you would have hadhe
fox news machine building up this
Then you would have hadhe fox news machine
building up this enormousnger aut loo how
News machine building up this enormousnger
aut loo how democrats manipulate the
Enormousnger aut loo how
democrats manipulate the public.
Democrats manipulate the public.
You were right, bill, this is
Public. You were right, bill, this
is an insane way to motivate our
You were right, bill, this is an
insane way to motivate our troops.
An insane way to motivate our
troops. And it's anthetical to what we
Troops. And it's anthetical
to what we believe in.
And it's anthetical to what we believe
in. Bill: let me read the quotes
Believe in. Bill: let me read the
quotes from debbie wasserman shultz.
Bill: let me read the quotes from debbie
wasserman shultz. She said the gentleman from
From debbie wasserman shultz. She said
the gentleman from florid repsenthousds of
She said the gentleman from florid
repsenthousds of medicare beneficiaries as do i
Florid repsenthousds of medicare beneficiaries
as do i is supportive of this plan.
Medicare beneficiaries as do i is supportive
of this plan. Unbelievable for a member from
Is supportive of this plan. Unbelievable
for a member from south florida.
Unbelievable for a member from south
florida. In other words, she was saying,
South florida. In other words, she was
saying, you're from florida where all
In other words, she was saying, you're from
florida where all the old people live and you
You're from florida where all the old people
live and you want to cut off their medicare.
The old people live and you want to cut off
their medicare. But she said, this is not a big
Want to cut off their medicare. But she said, this is not a big
- To me this is not outside of
But she said, this is not a big
- To me this is not outside of politics.
- To me this is not outside of
politics. Here's alan west's response,
Politics. Here's alan west's
response, you want a personalightim
Here's alan west's response, you
want a personalightim happy to oblige.
You want a personalightim happy
to oblige. You are the vile person.
bill: i will raise you -
>> These characters happen in
Bill: i will raise you
- >> These characters happen in politics all the time.
>> These characters happen in politics
all the time. I'm not condoning them.
Politics all the time. I'm not condoning
them. You can't characterize the
I'm not condoning them. You can't
characterize the entire rublin pty a a
You can't characterize the entire rublin pty a a single
- And guess what?
Entire rublin pty a a single
- And guess what? Guess what?
Single
- And guess what? Guess what? They use those letters for
Guess what? They use those
letters for fundraisering and their
They use those letters for fundraisering
and their cawthernare piling high -
Fundraisering and their cawthernare piling high
- Bill: you arehe most vile and
Cawthernare piling high
- Bill: you arehe most vile and despicable.
Bill: you arehe most vile and
despicable. >> This is not what the debate
Despicable. >> This is not
what the debate is about.
>> This is not what the debate is
about. Bill: one side thinks and talks
Is about. Bill: one side
thinks and talks like this.
Bill: one side thinks and talks like
this. >> That is so untrue, bill.
Like this. >> That is so
untrue, bill. That's not fair.
>> That is so untrue, bill. That's
not fair. >> You're cherry picking her
That's not fair. >> You're
cherry picking her club.
>> You're cherry picking her
club. She's been going for harry
Club. She's been going for harry west.
She's been going for harry west.
Bill: with language like that?
West. Bill: with language
like that? >> Absolutely.
Bill: with language like that? >>
Absolutely. Bill: after this clip, the
>> Absolutely. Bill: after this clip,
the republicans made a motivational
Bill: after this clip, the republicans made
a motivational reel that would fire us up.
To show next week at their
meet
To show next week at
their meet >> cut that off.
Meet >> cut that off. That's not funny.
>> Cut that off. That's
not funny. >> Guess wha
That's not funny. >> Guess
wha now thiis hpening.
Excu me.
What are you doing?
Excu me. What are you
doing? >> You're hurrying me!
What are you doing? >>
You're hurrying me! No!
>> You're hurrying me! No! Squeal!
No! Squeal! Squeal!
Squeal! Squeal! >> Ahh!
Squeal! >> Ahh! >> It
rubs its lotion o its
>> Ahh! >> It rubs its lotion o
its skin or else it gets the hose
>> It rubs its lotion o its skin
or else it gets the hose again.
Skin or else it gets the
hose again. >> Trust me.
Again. >> Trust me. >> For god's sake.
>> Trust me. >> For god's
sake. >> I'll do my best!
>> For god's sake. >>
I'll do my best! >> Please.
>> I'll do my best! >>
Please. Faster, faster, bambi!
>> Please. Faster,
faster, bambi! Go fast!
Faster, faster, bambi!
Go fast! Keep runng
Go fast! Keep runng keepunni!
Keep runng
keepunni!
Keepunni!
bill: all right, let's bring
our gust.
Bill: all right, let's bring our
gust. He's an emmy award-Winning
Our gust. He's an emmy award-Winning
star, frombreang badryan
He's an emmy award-Winning star,
frombreang badryan cranston.
Star, frombreang badryan
cranston. Look at that.
Cranston. Look at that. Hollywood star.
Look at that. Hollywood
star. The hollywood elite.
Hollywood star. The hollywood
elite. >> Sorry to interrupt this ba
The hollywood elite. >> Sorry
to interrupt this ba canali.
>> Sorry to interrupt this ba
canali. Bill: i want to congratulate
Canali. Bill: i want to
congratulate you on your three emmys.
Bill: i want to congratulate you on
your three emmys. You sun of a bitch.
You on your three emmys. You sun of
a bitch. I like your show because of
You sun of a bitch. I like your show
because of course it's about drugs, one of
I like your show because of course it's
about drugs, one of my lifelong hobbies.
Course it's about drugs, one of my
lifelong hobbies. You as a meth dealer, meth
My lifelong hobbies. You as a meth
dealer, meth maker, it's such a perfect met
You as a meth dealer, meth maker, it's such
a perfect met for for america, i think so.
Maker, it's such a perfect met for for
america, i think so. Do you think so?
For for america, i think so. Do
you think so? Why do you think so?
Do you think so? Why do you think
so? >>Hy do you i think you say
Why do you think so? >>Hy do
you i think you say is correct.
>>Hy do you i think you say is
correct. You know, i think it's a happy
Is correct. You know, i think it's
a happy accident that our show really
You know, i think it's a happy accident that
our show really sort of took a look at the
Accident that our show really sort of took
a look at the inadequacies of the health care
Sort of took a look at the
inadequacies of the health care system.
Inadequacies of the health care
system. Perhaps the nonrespect to pay
System. Perhaps the nonrespect to
pay the teachers and their salaries
Perhaps the nonrespect to pay the teachers and
their salaries and my character having to have
The teachers and their salaries and my character
having to have a second job to make ends meet.
And my character having to have a second
job to make ends meet. Bill: drama is great,
A second job to make ends meet. Bill: drama
is great, especially crime drama when you
Bill: drama is great, especially crime
drama when you understand why the criminal
Especially crime drama when you understand
why the criminal became the criminal.
Understand why the criminal became
the criminal. This is something "the
Became the criminal. This is something
"the godfather" did brilliantly.
This is something "the godfather" did
brilliantly. Heid. Derstood why don did what
Godfather" did brilliantly. Heid. Derstood
why don did what and we understand why you did
Heid. Derstood why don did what
and we understand why you did it.
And we understand why
you did it. You had bills.
It. You had bills. >> I had bills, bill.
You had bills. >> I had bills,
bill. It was the perfect storm.
>> I had bills, bill. It was the
perfect storm. There were all kinds of
It was the perfect storm. There were all
kinds of elements that came together for
There were all kinds of elements that came
together for this character than made him
Elements that came together for this character
than made him make this drastic, irrational
This character than made him make this drastic,
irrational decision, especially for men.
Make this drastic, irrational decision,
especially for men. He didn't want to go out, dying
Decision, especially for men. He didn't want
to go out, dying from cancer and leaving his
He didn't want to go out, dying from cancer
and leaving his family penniless, so he chose
From cancer and leaving his family penniless,
so he chose to do the first bold move he
Family penniless, so he chose to do the first
bold move he ever did in his life and that's
To do the first bold move he ever did in
his life and that's to use his chemistry
Ever did in his life and that's to use his
chemistry background, make crystal meth.
To use his chemistry background, make
crystal meth. Make money for his life and go.
Background, make crystal meth. Make money for
his life and go. Bill: did you ever do meth?
Make money for his life and go.
Bill: did you ever do meth? >> No.
Bill: did you ever do
meth? >> No. Bill: i did.
>> No. Bill: i did. In college.
Bill: i did. In college. >> Really?
In college. >> Really? Bill:
i knew one kid who didn't
>> Really? Bill: i knew one kid who
didn't read one page of the book for
Bill: i knew one kid who didn't read one page
of the book for the entire semester and study
Read one page of the book for the entire
semester and study one night on meth and aced the
The entire semester and study one
night on meth and aced the test.
One night on meth and aced the
test. Now the kids do ritalin.
Test. Now the kids do ritalin.
But in my day it was crystal
Now the kids do ritalin. But
in my day it was crystal meth.
But in my day it was crystal
meth. I will never forget that
Meth. I will never forget
that burning sensation as you
I will never forget that burning
sensation as you snorted it.
Burning sensation as you snorted
it. It must be worse than having a
Snorted it. It must be
worse than having a baby
It must be worse than having a
baby they say no man can understand
Baby they say no man can
understand of having a baby.
They say no man can understand of
having a baby. Snort some crystal meth.
Of having a baby. Snort some crystal
meth. >> That's certainly the message
Snort some crystal meth. >> That's certainly
the message we want to send for all you
>> That's certainly the message we want to
send for all you college students around the
We want to send for all you
college students around the country.
College students around the
country. >> He's so funny.
Country. >> He's so funny.
>> Did you find yourself
>> He's so funny. >> Did you find
yourself becoming addicted to it?
>> Did you find yourself becoming
addicted to it? Was it hard for you to -
Becoming addicted to it? Was it hard for you to
- Bill: no, because it hurt so
Was it hard for you to
- Bill: no, because it hurt so much.
Bill: no, because it hurt so
much. But no, because it was a -
Much. But no, because it was a
- You'd be up for three days and
But no, because it was a
- You'd be up for three days and then you'd have to take a break
You'd be up for three days and then
you'd have to take a break from it.
Then you'd have to take a break
from it. Yes, i guess kids would get
From it. Yes, i guess kids would
get into trouble because you know
Yes, i guess kids would get into trouble
because you know when you're super tired then
Into trouble because you know when you're
super tired then the stupid ones would say, you
When you're super tired then the stupid ones
would say, you know what would solve that -
The stupid ones would say, you know what would solve that
- More meth.
Know what would solve that
- More meth. I just masturbated more hours
More meth. I just masturbated more
hours because you couldn't sleep and
I just masturbated more hours because you
couldn't sleep and you really couldn't do
Because you couldn't sleep and
you really couldn't do anything.
You really couldn't do
anything. Aren't you glad -
Bill: meth is a bad drug
because it's good at first.
Bill: meth is a bad drug because it's
good at first. Well, lots of drugs are like
Because it's good at first.
Well, lots of drugs are like that.
Here's our introductory offer.
That. Here's our introductory
offer. >> That enticement.
Here's our introductory offer. >> That
enticement. You buy into it and all of a
>> That enticement. You buy
into it and all of a sudden -
You buy into it and all of a sudden
- Bill: now you have new insight
Sudden
- Bill: now you have new insight into your character.
Bill: now you have new insight into your
character. >> They told me that crystal
Into your character. >> They told me that
crystal meth creates a euphoric feeling
>> They told me that crystal meth
creates a euphoric feeling into the brain.
Meth creates a euphoric feeling into
the brain. And it creates its own dopea
Into the brain. And it creates its
own dopea mean and it's the most
And it creates its own dopea mean and
it's the most wonderful, beautiful high.
Mean and it's the most wonderful,
beautiful high. Did you have that?
Wonderful, beautiful high. Did
you have that? Bill: i don't know.
Did you have that? Bill:
i don't know. I neverid i
Bill: i don't know. I neverid
i >> but then after a while your
I neverid i >> but then after a
while your brain stops producing the
>> But then after a while your
brain stops producing the dopamine.
Brain stops producing the dopamine.
Bill: probably the worst drug
Dopamine. Bill: probably the
worst drug in the world, horrible,
Bill: probably the worst drug
in the world, horrible, horrible.
In the world, horrible,
horrible. It's a great met for for
Horrible. It's a great met for
for america because it's eating
It's a great met for for america because
it's eating away at the healand much like
America because it's eating away at
the healand much like publan policies.
Away at the healand much like publan
policies. Let's talk about that.
Publan policies. Let's talk about
that. You'll be interested in this
Let's talk about that. You'll be interested
in this too because i read your book
You'll be interested in this too because i
read your book about your grandfather, herbert
Too because i read your book about your
grandfather, herbert hoover who i did not know in
About your grandfather, herbert hoover who i
did not know in his day was referred to as the
Hoover who i did not know in his day was
referred to as the great humanitarian.
His day was referred to as the great
humanitarian. And you mentioned health care.
Great humanitarian. And you mentioned
health care. It seems like that era of
And you mentioned health care. It seems like
that era of republican would be interested
It seems like that era of republican would
be interested in health care because they
Republican would be interested in health
care because they were interested in doing big
In health care because they were interested
in doing big things for this country.
Were interested in doing big things for this country. When herbert hoover was
- What
Things for this country. When herbert hoover was
- What was his job?
When herbert hoover was - What was
his job? He was head of the food -
Was his job? He was head of the food
- >> He was the secretary of
He was head of the food
- >> He was the secretary of commerce but he was also the
>> He was the secretary of commerce but
he was also the head of the american relief
Commerce but he was also the head of
the american relief administration.
Head of the american relief
administration. Bill: relief administration.
Administration. Bill: relief
administration. He saved the lives of 10
Bill: relief administration. He saved
the lives of 10 million russians -
He saved the lives of 10 million russians
- 10 million russians per day.
Million russians
- 10 million russians per day. Bill: and this was when they
10 million russians per day. Bill: and
this was when they were filthy comeies.
Bill: and this was when they were
filthy comeies. Can you see us doing that
Were filthy comeies. Can
you see us doing that today?
Can you see us doing that today?
Because compassion was part of
Today? Because
compassion was part of it.
Because compassion was part of it. I don't know
- I you can d
It. I don't know
- I you can d those big things if you don't
I don't know
- I you can d those big things if you don't have compassion.
Those big things if you don't have
compassion. >> We'd be on the reciprocating
Have compassion. >> We'd be on
the reciprocating end, right?
>> We'd be on the reciprocating end,
right? We'd be the one getting the
End, right? We'd be the
one getting the food.
We'd be the one getting the food.
>> You cannot do great things
Food. >> You cannot do great
things without resources.
>> You cannot do great things without resources.
- And without in a growing
Without resources.
- And without in a growing economy without capitalists,
- And without in a growing economy without capitalists, these people
-
Burns.
>> he did big things, but it
was also because of individual
>> He did big things, but it was
also because of individual leadership.
Was also because of individual
leadership. Bill: what's wrong with his
Leadership. Bill: what's wrong
with his sideburns, they're kind of
Bill: what's wrong with his
sideburns, they're kind of cool.
Sideburns, they're kind of
cool. >> What did i just say?
Cool. >> What did i just say?
I said they were saw some.
>> What did i just say? I said they were
saw some. >> We can be compassionate but
I said they were saw some. >> We can be compassionate but the question is
- Who pays?
>> We can be compassionate but the question is
- Who pays? Does government pay?
The question is
- Who pays? Does government pay? And when he led these efforts
Does government pay? And when he led
these efforts it was 22/3 paid by private
And when he led these efforts it was 22/3 paid by private money
- 2/3 paid by private
It was 22/3 paid by private money
- 2/3 paid by private money.
Money
- 2/3 paid by private money. That's what missing, we can
Money. That's what missing, we
can have compassion but libalism
That's what missing, we can have compassion
but libalism is that government has to
Have compassion but libalism is that
government has to provide the dough.
Is that government has to provide the
dough. Government has to pay for it
Provide the dough. Government
has to pay for it all.
Government has to pay for
it all. There's a balance.
All. There's a balance. We
can be compassionate but we
There's a balance. We can be compassionate
but we can be compassionate, it's upon
We can be compassionate but we can be
compassionate, it's upon us to be compassionate.
Can be compassionate, it's upon us to be
compassionate. And the government doesn't
Us to be compassionate. And the government
doesn't always have to flip the bill.
And the government doesn't always have
to flip the bill. >> I cut budgets.
Always have to flip the bill. >> I cut
budgets. But what bill is saying is so
>> I cut budgets. But what
bill is saying is so critical.
But what bill is saying is so
critical. There was no vision.
Critical. There was no vision.
We could not put a man on the
There was no vision. We could not
put a man on the moon right now.
We could not put a man on the moon
right now. We can not get our energy
Moon right now. We can not
get our energy policy past.
We can not get our energy policy
past. We cannot educate our kids.
Policy past. We cannot educate our
kids. We cannot build infrastructure.
We cannot educate our kids. We cannot build
infrastructure. We are now becoming a country
We cannot build infrastructure. We are now
becoming a country that is falling behind because
We are now becoming a country that is falling
behind because the only emphasis is cut taxes.
That is falling behind because the
only emphasis is cut taxes. >> Come on.
The only emphasis is cut
taxes. >> Come on. >> It is.
>> Come on. >> It is. >> That's absurd!
>> It is. >> That's absurd!
>> Listen to the debate.
>> That's absurd! >> Listen to the
debate. Bill: not just cut taxes but
>> Listen to the debate. Bill: not just cut taxes but they're back to
- I saw a
Bill: not just cut taxes but they're back
to - I saw a quoterom john boehner last -
They're back to - I saw a quoterom john
boehner last - >> We can't put a man on the
Quoterom john boehner last
- >> We can't put a man on the moon because all we're doing is
>> We can't put a man on the moon because all
we're doing is talking about cutting taxes.
Moon because all we're doing is talking about
cutting taxes. >> They'veot somhing going.
Talking about cutting taxes. >> They'veot
somhing going. You two are going tond u
>> They'veot somhing going. You
two are going tond u tonight.
You two are going tond u tonight.
There's nothing hotter than a
Tonight. There's nothing hotter than a conservative hot lady
- Right?
There's nothing hotter than a conservative
hot lady - Right? Bill: let mead ts quo-
Conservative hot lady - Right?
Bill: let mead ts quo- Shutp.
Bill: let mead ts quo-
Shutp.
>> You're all john boehner
taed up.
>> You're all john boehner taed
up. >> You're looking good there,
Taed up. >> You're
looking good there, eliot.
>> You're looking good there,
eliot. >> Who invited this guy?
Eliot. >> Who invited
this guy? Bill: exactly.
>> Who invited this guy? Bill:
exactly. Gog to f things?Ed how are we
Bill: exactly. Gog to f things?Ed
how are we his revenue numbers that we
Gog to f things?Ed how are we his revenue
numbers that we thought we can reach based o a
His revenue numbers that we thought we can
reach based o a flatter tax code with lower
Thought we can reach based o a flatter
tax code with lower rates an a broaderase.
Flatter tax code with lower rates an a
broaderase. This would produce more taxes.
Rates an a broaderase. This would
produce more taxes. This is the old voodoo
This would produce more taxes. This is the
old voodoo economics, the old we cut and
This is the old voodoo economics, the
old we cut and it grows otherwise known as
Economics, the old we cut and it
grows otherwise known as maceans
It grows otherwise known as
maceans that is so discredited.
Maceans that is so discredited. And i think
- What we're
That is so discredited. And i think
- What we're trying to say is that this idea
And i think
- What we're trying to say is that this idea in the republican will not go
Trying to say is that this idea
in the republican will not go away.
In the republican will not go
away. That somehow the american
Away. That somehow the american
economy is a chained beast.
That somehow the american economy is a
chained beast. If we only let off the chains
Economy is a chained beast. If we only
let off the chains we let off the chains.
If we only let off the chains we let off
the chains. Yes. Revenues are the lowest in
With a stick hoping it will
blurp out a lite
With a stick hoping it will blurp
out a lite and it's just not going to
Blurp out a lite and it's
just not going to happen.
And it's just not going to happen.
>> Our tax code code is a crazy
Happen. >> Our tax code code is
a crazy quilt of special interest
>> Our tax code code is a crazy
quilt of special interest provisions.
Quilt of special interest provisions.
What we want to see a cross the
Provisions. What we want to see
a cross the board, cut the rates -
What we want to see a cross the board, cut the rates
- Bill: let's cut theriva jet
Board, cut the rates - Bill:
let's cut theriva jet owners -
Bill: let's cut theriva jet owners
- >> Here's the thing, on the
Owners
- >> Here's the thing, on the show, i would say to dick army
>> Here's the thing, on the show, i would
say to dick army to all the republican members
Show, i would say to dick army to all the
republican members of congress, name the loophole
To all the republican members of congress,
name the loophole you're going to close.
Of congress, name the loophole you're
going to close. And they wouldn't do it.
You're going to close. And they wouldn't
do it. >> The flat tax gets rid of all
And they wouldn't do it. >> The
flat tax gets rid of all that.
>> The flat tax gets rid of all
that. >> The republicans in congress
That. >> The republicans in
congress were unwilling to do it.
>> The republicans in congress were unwilling
to do it. John boehner is unwilling to do
Were unwilling to do it. John
boehner is unwilling to do that.
John boehner is unwilling to do
that. The president said we would do.
That. The president said we would
do. Bowl simpson said we would do
The president said we would do.
Bowl simpson said we would do it.
Bowl simpson said we would
do it. The gang of six -
It. The gang of six
- >> Thereo leglati.
The gang of six - >> Thereo
leglati. This is all - I want to see
>> Thereo leglati. This is all
- I want to see it.
This is all
- I want to see it. The american people want to see
It. The american people want to
see what these ideas actually are.
The american people want to see what these ideas
actually are. >> Bole simpson is the pardon.
What these ideas actually are. >> Bole simpson is the pardon.
- Paridon.
>> Bole simpson is the pardon.
- Paridon. >> Tax rates matter.
There is a reason why john
>> Tax rates matter. There is a reason
why john kerry registers his vote in
There is a reason why john kerry registers
his vote in rhode island instead of
Kerry registers his vote in rhode island
instead of massachusetts because rates
Rhode island instead of
massachusetts because rates matter.
Massachusetts because rates
matter. They change behavior and
Matter. They change behavior and
behavior undermines our ability
They change behavior and behavior
undermines our ability to create jobs.
Behavior undermines our ability to
create jobs. It undermines people's
To create jobs. It undermines
people's willingness to invest in the
It undermines people's willingness
to invest in the economy.
Willingness to invest in the
economy. If we punh creative
Economy. If we punh creative
production, we won't get any -
If we punh creative
Production, we won't get any -
>> but marginal rates are at a
historic low.
>> But marginal rates are at a
Historic low.
Let me finish.
Back in december, the argument
Let me finish. Back in december, the
argument for extending the bush tax cuts
Back in december, the argument for extending
the bush tax cuts was extend it, you will release
For extending the bush tax cuts was extend it,
you will release this huge $2 trillion pile of
Was extend it, you will release
this huge $2 trillion pile of cash.
This huge $2 trillion pile
of cash. It hasn't happened.
Cash. It hasn't happened.
Lowering the marginal rates did
It hasn't happened. Lowering
the marginal rates did thg.
Bill: i have one more issue
that's not economics.
Bill: i have one more issue that's not
economics. I have to get to this because
That's not economics. I have to get to
this because violent religious extremists
I have to get to this because violent religious
extremists were in the news this week, one
Violent religious extremists were in
the news this week, one from each side.
Were in the news this week, one from
each side. There's a guy we found out a
From each side. There's a guy we
found out a muslim soldier, a muslim
There's a guy we found out a muslim
soldier, a muslim american was planning up of
Muslim soldier, a muslim american was
planning up of blowing forthood the same place
American was planning up of blowing forthood the same place that major hasan
- And then we
Blowing forthood the same place that major hasan
- And then we had anders breivik who
That major hasan
- And then we had anders breivik who succeeded in his terrorist
Had anders breivik who succeeded
in his terrorist attack.
Succeeded in his terrorist
attack. They refuse to call anders
Attack. They refuse to call anders
breivik a christian terrorist
They refuse to call anders breivik a
christian terrorist but that's what he was.
Breivik a christian terrorist but that's
what he was. He's a christian terrorist.
But that's what he was. He's a christian
terrorist. He wanted to start a christian
He's a christian terrorist. He wanted to
start a christian onslaught against the muslims
He wanted to start a christian onslaught against the muslims and it reminds me that
- This
Onslaught against the muslims and it reminds me that
- This is not a problem with the
And it reminds me that
- This is not a problem with the muslim religion.
Is not a problem with the muslim
religion. It's a problem with religion.
Muslim religion. It's a problem with
religion. And christianity is perfectly
It's a problem with religion. And christianity
is perfectly capable of coming out of its
And christianity is perfectly capable of
coming out of its dormant phase and once again
Capable of coming out of its dormant phase
and once again becoming the blood-Lusty
Dormant phase and once again becoming the
blood-Lusty religion under the crusades.
Becoming the blood-Lusty religion under
the crusades. Bill o'reilly and they're in
Religion under the crusades. Bill o'reilly
and they're in just as much denial as the
Bill o'reilly and they're in just
as much denial as the muslims.
Just as much denial as the
muslims. He said no one believing in
Muslims. He said no one believing
in jesus commits mass murder.
He said no one believing in jesus commits
mass murder. Pin head, wt do you think t
Jesus commits mass murder. Pin head,
wt do you think t crusades were?
Pin head, wt do you think t
crusades were?
Crusades were?
What do c tnk t entire
16th cturyn eureas?
What do c tnk t entire 16th cturyn
eureas? What do you think the
16th cturyn eureas? What do
you think the quision was?
What do you think the quision
was? The ku klux klan was a
Quision was? The ku klux
klan was a christian religion.
The ku klux klan was a christian
religion. But see that look on your
Christian religion. But
see that look on your face.
But see that look on your
face. >> You can call this guy a
Face. >> You can call this guy
a christian extremists but the
>> You can call this guy a christian extremists
but the difference between him and the
Christian extremists but the
difference between him and the
Difference between him and the
islamist supremacist.
Islamist supremacist.
He isn't connected to a global
Islamist supremacist. He isn't connected
to a global terror network who's trying -
He isn't connected to a global terror network who's trying
- Bill: no.
Terror network who's trying
- Bill: no. It denies -
Bill: no. It denies
- >> And major has -
It denies - >> And major has
- Bill: you don't need to be in
>> And major has
- Bill: you don't need to be in the club.
Bill: you don't need to be in the
club. >> There's a difference that we
The club. >> There's a difference
that we know between islamic supremacy
>> There's a difference that we know between
islamic supremacy and what you're calling
Know between islamic supremacy and
what you're calling christian extremism.
And what you're calling christian
extremism. You're blaming it on the
Christian extremism. You're
blaming it on the religion.
You're blaming it on the
religion. The bloodiest murder is
Religion. The bloodiest
murder is atheism.
The bloodiest murder is
atheism. What was communism?
Atheism. What was communism?
30 milon pple die in cna
What was communism? 30 milon pple
die in cna in the great leap forward.
30 milon pple die in cna in the great
leap forward. 20 million people died in
In the great leap forward. 20 million
people died in stallen's purr jess.
20 million people died in
stallen's purr jess. That was athsm.
Stallen's purr jess. That was
athsm. It killed 50 million people.
That was athsm. It killed 50 million
people. Bill: religion has killed more
It killed 50 million people. Bill: religion has killed more people
- That is bull shit.
Bill: religion has killed more
people - That is bull shit.
People - That is bull shit.
>> i'm worried that we're on
the same side.
>> I'm worried that we're on
the same side. It's fanaticism.
The same side. It's
fanaticism. It is not religion.
It's fanaticism. It is not religion.
Fanaticism in any ideolog and
It is not religion. Fanaticism in any
ideolog and lackfolerance is when you
Fanaticism in any ideolog and
lackfolerance is when you get dangerous.
Lackfolerance is when you get
dangerous. Bill: but far from, you know,
Get dangerous. Bill: but far from,
you know, far from restraining people
Bill: but far from, you know, far from
restraining people religion is what gives people
Far from restraining people religion is
what gives people license to commit crazycts
Religion is what gives people
license to commit crazycts because -
License to commit crazycts because
- >> So does ideology.
Because
- >> So does ideology. What do you think the great
>> So does ideology. What do you think
the great leap forward in china was?
What do you think the great leap
forward in china was? It's a license.
Leap forward in china was? It's a
license. Bill: it didn't give them a
It's a license. Bill: it
didn't give them a license.
Bill: it didn't give them a
license. It gave them an army.
License. It gave them an army.
And also a lot of these places
It gave them an army. And also a lot of
these places it really was a state religion.
And also a lot of these places it
really was a state religion. North korea.
It really was a state religion. North
korea. I know you would say it's an
North korea. I know you would
say it's an atheist country.
I know you would say it's
an atheist country. It's not.
Atheist country. It's not.
The deer leader is the god.
It's not. The deer leader is the
god. They think that when he was
The deer leader is the god. They think
that when he was born, winter turned into
They think that when he was
born, winter turned into spring.
Born, winter turned into spring.
They said the first time he
Spring. They said the first time
he played golf he had 11 holes in
They said the first time he
played golf he had 11 holes in one.
Played golf he had 11 holes
in one. That is religion.
One. That is religion. I'm sorry.
That is religion. I'm sorry. Hitler
- A god
I'm sorry. Hitler
- A god >> i have another theory by the
Hitler
- A god >> i have another theory by the way.
>> I have another theory by the
way. Maybe this guy is just bad shit
Way. Maybe this guy
is just bad shit crazy.
Maybe this guy is just bad shit
crazy. Crazy is not an ideology.
Crazy. Crazy is not an ideology.
Bill: no, but religion gaves
Crazy is not an ideology. Bill: no,
but religion gaves crazy a platform.
Bill: no, but religion gaves crazy a
platform. >> No, but it is the lack of
Crazy a platform. >> No, but it
is the lack of tolerance, bill.
>> No, but it is the lack of tolerance, bill. I mean, that is
- Is when you
Tolerance, bill. I mean, that is
- Is when you refuse to accept alternative
I mean, that is
- Is when you refuse to accept alternative views and you are so deeply
Refuse to accept alternative views and you
are so deeply engrained in your own view tha
Else.
That's when you get the
Else. That's when you get the crazies.
crazies. Bill: whatives peoe the
Crazies. Bill: whatives peoe
the license to act that way?
Bill: whatives peoe the license
to act that way? >> Ideology.
License to act that way? >> Ideology.
It gives people to say my god
>> Ideology. It gives people to say
my god is a bigger dick than your god
It gives people to say my god is a bigger
dick than your god and maybe you should die for
Is a bigger dick than your god
and maybe you should die for it.
And maybe you should die for
it. Anyway, we've got to go.
It. Anyway, we've got to go.
Not go but say goodbye to the
Anyway, we've got to go. Not go but
say goodbye to the panel whi was ver
Not go but say goodbye to the
panel whi was ver
Panel whi was ver
entertaining.
Entertaining.
But it is time fornew res,"
Entertaining. But it is
time fornew res," everybody.
But it is time fornew res,"
everybody.
Everybody.
all right.
New rule, if you're going to
All right. New rule, if you're going
to have a big gay marriage weekend
New rule, if you're going to have a big gay
marriage weekend that showcases gay marriage to
Have a big gay marriage weekend that showcases
gay marriage to the rest of the world, let the
That showcases gay marriage to the rest of
the world, let the good-Looking ones go first.
The rest of the world, let the good-Looking
ones go first. This photo doesn't say, it's
Good-Looking ones go first. This photo
doesn't say, it's time to re-Evaluate our
This photo doesn't say, it's time to
re-Evaluate our defition of marriage.
Time to re-Evaluate our defition of
marriage. It says there's a special at
Defition of marriage. It says
there's a special at super cuts.
It says there's a special at super
cuts. New rule, john boehner and
Super cuts. New rule, john boehner
and harry reid must stop appearing
New rule, john boehner and harry
reid must stop appearing together.
Harry reid must stop appearing
together. This doesn't look like a
Together. This doesn't look
like a bipartisan approach to a
This doesn't look like a bipartisan
approach to a complex problem.
Bipartisan approach to a complex
problem. It looks like aefore d
Out to michelle bachman.
Whenever you start to stress
Out to michelle bachman. Whenever you
start to stress out over the rigors of
Whenever you start to stress out
over the rigors of campaigning.
Out over the rigors of campaigning.
Just remember the advice of
Campaigning. Just remember the advice
of your husband, that you are good
Just remember the advice of your husband,
that you are good enough, you're smart eughnd
Your husband, that you are good enough, you're
smart eughnd doggone it, people like you.
Enough, you're smart eughnd doggone it,
people like you. New rule, the makers of the
Doggone it, people like you. New rule, the
makers of the movie "final destination 5"
New rule, the makers of the movie "final
destination 5" must be locked in a room until
Movie "final destination 5" must be locked
in a room until they learn what the word
Must be locked in a room until they
learn what the word "final" means.
They learn what the word "final"
means. New rule, your state can not
"Final" means. New rule, your state
can not officially commemorate an alien
New rule, your state can not officially
commemorate an alien abduction.
Officially commemorate an alien
abduction. Sorry, new hampshire, i know
Abduction. Sorry, new hampshire,
i know you think you saw something
Sorry, new hampshire, i know you think
you saw something strange that you couldn't
You think you saw something strange that
you couldn't explain, but trust me, those
Strange that you couldn't explain,
but trust me, those were aliens.
Explain, but trust me, those
were aliens. They were minorities.
Were aliens. They were minorities.
And finally, since no one is
They were minorities. And finally, since
no one is truly happy living a lie and
And finally, since no one is truly happy
living a lie and denying who they really are, i
Truly happy living a lie and denying who they
really are, i want to direct this rule at a
Denying who they really are, i want to direct
this rule at a certain group of people and say
Want to direct this rule at a certain group of people and say to them
- New rule, it's time
Certain group of people and say to them
- New rule, it's time to stop fighting it and just
To them
- New rule, it's time to stop fighting it and just come out of the closet.
To stop fighting it and just come out of
the closet. And the group i'm talking about
Come out of the closet. And the group i'm
talking about is the american public and the
And the group i'm talking about is the american
public and the love that they're denying is
Is the american public and the love that
they're denying is their love of socialism.
Love that they're denying is
their love of socialism.
Their love of socialism.
now i know that there are few
words that america more toxic
Now i know that there are few words that
america more toxic than socialism and big
Words that america more toxic than socialism
and big government spending is about as
Than socialism and big government spending
is about as popular as casey anthony at a
Government spending is about as popular
as casey anthony at a chuck e. Cheese.
Popular as casey anthony at a chuck
e. Cheese. Yes, americans say they hate
Chuck e. Cheese. Yes, americans say
they hate socialism but when it comes to
Yes, americans say they hate socialism but
when it comes to social security, medicare,
Socialism but when it comes to social
security, medicare, unemployment, fannie mae and
Social security, medicare, unemployment,
fannie mae and freddie mac, corporate welfare,
Unemployment, fannie mae and freddie mac,
corporate welfare, bailouts and farm subsidies,
Freddie mac, corporate welfare, bailouts and
farm subsidies, what we reayay t socialism
Bailouts and farm subsidies, what we reayay t socialism is
- I can't quit you.
What we reayay t socialism is
- I can't quit you. Americans don't want less
Is
- I can't quit you. Americans don't want less spending on health care.
Americans don't want less spending on
health care. By almost 2-1, they want more.
Spending on health care. By almost 2-1,
they want more. Only 7% of americans are
By almost 2-1, they want more. Only 7% of
americans are willing to do away with social
Only 7% of americans are willing to do
away with social security and medicare.
Willing to do away with social security
and medicare. And even 6% of tea party
Security and medicare. And even 6% of
tea party members say those programs are
And even 6% of tea party members say
those programs are worth the cost.
Members say those programs are worth
the cost. Yet 91% of them say they want
Worth the cost. Yet 91% of them say
they want smaller government with few
Yet 91% of them say they want
smaller government with few services.
Smaller government with few services.
They're like the guy that went
Services. They're like the guy that
went to prison that says, sure i
They're like the guy that went to prison
that says, sure i gargle with balls once in a
To prison that says, sure i gargle with
balls once in a while and i love ass play but
Gargle with balls once in a while and i love
ass play but you know who i can't stand -
remember this guy, the keep
your government hands off my
Remember this guy, the keep your
government hands off my medicare guy?
Your government hands off my
medicare guy? He's not ay lone.
Medicare guy? He's not ay lone.
One survey 40% of people who
He's not ay lone. One survey 40% of
people who ged medicare say they have not
One survey 40% of people who ged medicare
say they have not used a government program.
Ged medicare say they have not
used a government program. Really?
Used a government program. Really?
Who do you think paid for that
Really? Who do you think
paid for that hip replacement?
Who do you think paid for that
hip replacement? Your secret santa?
Hip replacement? Your secret
santa? The actor and not very bright
Your secret santa? The actor and not
very bright person craig t. Nelson once
The actor and not very bright person craig
t. Nelson once said about hitting some rough
Person craig t. Nelson once said about
hitting some rough spots in his life that quote
Said about hitting some rough spots in his
life that quote "i've been on welfare and food
Spots in his life that quote "i've been on
welfare and food stamps, but anybody help me
"I've been on welfare and food
stamps, but anybody help me out?
Stamps, but anybody help me out? No. "
Out? No. " And take michelle and marcus
No. " And take michelle and marcus
bachman or as i would like to
And take michelle and marcus bachman or as
i would like to think about them, america's
Bachman or as i would like to think about
them, america's indoor palins, yes, the
Think about them, america's indoor palins,
yes, the bachman's tireless speeches of
Indoor palins, yes, the bachman's tireless
speeches of cutting the government tit.
Bachman's tireless speeches of cutting
the government tit. Their farm takes farm
Cutting the government tit.
Their farm takes farm subsidies.
Their counciling clinic takes
Subsidies. Their counciling
clinic takes medicaid.
Their counciling clinic takes
medicaid. And their mortgage was
Medicaid. And their mortgage
was underwritten by freddy mac.
And their mortgage was underwritten by
freddy mac. She was an i. R.S. Agent.
Underwritten by freddy mac. She was an
i. R.S. Agent. And marcus hates government
She was an i. R.S. Agent. And marcus hates
government employees because sailors are
And marcus hates government employees
because sailors are so rough.
Employees because sailors are so
rough. But come on, if hypocrisy was
So rough. But come on, if hypocrisy
was uranium, they could power the
But come on, if hypocrisy was
uranium, they could power the planet.
Uranium, they could power the planet.
And that's what's so hard about
Planet. And that's what's so hard
about being a closetted lover of big
And that's what's so hard about being
a closetted lover of big government.
Being a closetted lover of big
government. You have to lie to yourself.
Government. You have to lie to
yourself. But that's why i'm here tonight
You have to lie to yourself. But that's why
i'm here tonight with a special message for all
But that's why i'm here tonight with
a special message for all you deniers.
With a special message for all
you deniers. It gets better.
You deniers. It gets better.
Yes, there are millions of
It gets better. Yes, there are millions
of people in the world just like
Yes, there are millions of people in the
world just like you in nice places lie
People in the world just like you in
nice places lie switzerland and sweden.
You in nice places lie switzerland and
sweden. They enjoy high standards of
Switzerland and sweden. They enjoy high
standards of living and freedom and they're
They enjoy high standards of living
and freedom and they're socialists.
Living and freedom and they're
socialists. Studies show they're happier
Socialists. Studies show they're
happier than we are and that's not
Studies show they're happier than we are
and that's not surprising because the only
Than we are and that's not surprising
because the only difference between american
Surprising because the only difference
between american socialism and european
Difference between american socialism and
european socialism is european socialism
Socialism and european socialism
is european socialism works.
Socialism is european socialism works. For their tax dollars
- For
Works. For their tax dollars
- For their fax dollars europeans get
For their tax dollars
- For their fax dollars europeans get full health care coverage,
Their fax dollars europeans get full health
care coverage, pension, long, paid vacations,
Full health care coverage, pension, long,
paid vacations, maternity leave, and free
Pension, long, paid vacations, maternity
leave, and free transportation that doesn't
Maternity leave, and free transportation
that doesn't smell like pee.
Transportation that doesn't smell
like pee. Where as our tax dollars go
Smell like pee. Where as our tax
dollars go towards military bases in
Where as our tax dollars go towards
military bases in germany, subsidies to oil
Towards military bases in germany, subsidies
to oil companies, building bridges to
Germany, subsidies to oil companies, building
bridges to nowhere, wars and putting half
Companies, building bridges to nowhere, wars
and putting half of cheech and chong in prison.
Nowhere, wars and putting half of cheech and
chong in prison. They get universal health care.
Of cheech and chong in prison. They get universal
health care. We get a blue angels fly over
They get universal health care. We get a
blue angels fly over at the fiesta bowl.
We get a blue angels fly over at
the fiesta bowl. They get paid ma
At the fiesta bowl. They get
paid ma northwesternity leave.
They get paid ma northwesternity leave. We
- Paid ma ternity leave.
Northwesternity leave. We
- Paid ma ternity leave. We get the octomom.
We
- Paid ma ternity leave. We get the octomom. Even their paranoid racist
We get the octomom. Even their
paranoid racist loaners look like speed
Even their paranoid racist loaners look
like speed and ours look like porky pig.
Loaners look like speed and ours
look like porky pig. All right.
And ours look like porky pig.
All right. That's our show.
You can see me at the britt
That's our show. You can see me
at the britt festival on august 6.
You can see me at the britt festival
on august 6. I want to thank my guests.
Festival on august 6. I want to thank
my guests. Don't forget to watch us on
I want to thank my guests. Don't
forget to watch us on "overtime. "
Don't forget to watch us
on "overtime. " On hbo. Com.
"Overtime. "
On hbo. Com.
Captioned by the
national captioning institute
Captioned by the national captioning
institute - Www. Ncicap. Org-